###B.B. King
###The Thrill is Gone
The thrill is gone

The thrill is gone away
The thrill is gone baby
The thrill is gone away
You know you done me wrong baby
And you'll be sorry someday
The thrill is gone

It's gone away from me
The thrill is gone baby
The thrill is gone away from me
Although, I'll still live on
But so lonely I'll be
The thrill is gone

It's gone away for good
The thrill is gone baby
It's gone away for good
Someday I know I'll be open armed baby
Just like I know a good man should
You know I'm free, free now baby

I'm free from your spell
Oh I'm free, free, free now
I'm free from your spell
And now that it's all over
All I can do is wish you well

###B.B. King
###Three O'Clock Blues
Now here it is three o' clock in the mornin'
Can't even close my eyes
Oh, three o' clock in the mornin', baby
Can't even close my eyes
Well, I can't find my baby
Lord, and I can't be satisfied

Lord, I've looked around me
Whoa, my baby can't be found
Whoa, looked all around me, people
Whoa, my baby can't be found
Well, if I don't find my baby
I'm goin' down to the boilin' ground, that's where the mens hang out

Well, I'm bound to find her
Yeah
Come here, baby

Well, goodbye, everybody
Lord, I believe this is the end
Oh, goodbye, everybody
Lord, I believe this is the end

Well, you can tell my baby
To forgive me for my sins

###B.B. King
###Rock Me Baby
Rock me baby, rock me all night long
Rock me baby, honey, rock me all night long
I want you to rock me baby,
like my back ain't got no bones

Roll me baby, like you roll a wagon wheel
I want you to roll me baby, like you roll a wagon wheel
Want you to roll me baby,
you don't know how it makes me feel

Rock me baby, honey, rock me slow
Yeah, rock me pretty baby, baby rock me slow
Want you to rock me baby,
till I want no more

###B.B. King
###Everyday I Have The Blues
Everyday
Everyday I have the blues
Everyday
Everyday I have the blues
When you see me worryin' woman, honey, it's you I hate to lose

Nobody loves me
Nobody seems to care
Yes, nobody loves me
Nobody seems to care
Speaking of worries and trouble darling, you know I've had my share

Everyday, everyday, everyday, everyday
Everyday
Everyday I have the blues
When you see me worryin' woman, honey, it's you I hate to lose

Every day, everyday I have the blues
Every day, everyday I have the blues 
When you see me worryin' woman, baby, it's you I hate to lose

###B.B.King
###Let The Good Times Roll
Hey, everybody, let's have some fun
You only live but once
And when you're dead you're done, so
Let the good times roll, let the good times roll
I don't care if you're young or old
Get together, let the good times roll

Don't sit there mumblin', talkin' trash
If you wanna have a ball
You gotta go out and spend some cash, and
Let the good times roll, let the good times roll
I don't care if you're young or old
Get together, let the good times roll


Hey Mr. Landlord, lock up all the doors
When the police comes around
Just tell 'em that the joint is closed
Let the good times roll, let the good times roll
I don't care if you're young or old
Get together, let the good times roll

Hey tell everybody
Mr. King's in town
I got a dollar and a quarter
Just rarin' to clown
But don't let nobody play me cheap
I got fifty cents more that I'm gonna keep, so

Let the good times roll, let the good times roll
I don't care if you're young or old
Get together, let the good times roll

No matter whether rainy weather
Birds of a feather gotta stick together
So get yourself under control
Go out and get together and let the good times roll

###B.B. King
###Paying the Cost To Be The Boss
You act like you don't want to listen
When I'm talking to you
You think you outta do baby
Anything you want to do
You must be crazy baby
You just gotta be outta your mind
As long as i'm payin' the bills woman
I'm payin' the cost to be the boss

I'll drink if i want to
And play a little poker too
Don't you say nothing to me
As long as I'm taking care of you
As long as I'm workin baby
And payin' all the bills
I don't want no mouth from you
About the way I'm supposed to live
You must be crazy woman
Just gotta be outta your mind
As long as i foot the bills
I'm payin' the cost to be the boss

Now that you got me
You act like you ashamed
You don't act like my woman
You just usin' my name
I tell you I'm gonna have all the money
And i don't want no back-talk
Cause if you don't like the way I'm doin'
Just pick up your things and walk
You gotta be crazy baby
You must be outta your mind
As long as I'm payin' the bills woman
I'm payin' the cost to be the boss

###B.B. King
###You Upset Me Baby
Yes, she's thirty-six in the bust, twenty-eight in the waist
Forty-four in the hip, she got real crazy legs
You upset me baby, yes, you upset me baby
Well, like being hit by a fallen tree
Woman, what you do to me

Well, she's not too tall, complexion is fair
Man she knocked me out the way she wears her hair
You upset me baby, yes, you upset me baby
Well, like being hit by a fallen tree
Woman, what you do to me, yes

Well, she's not too tall, complexion is fair
Man she knocked me out the way she wears her hair
You upset me baby, yes, you upset me baby
Well, like being hit by a fallen tree
Woman, what you do to me

Well I, tried to describe her, it's hard to start
Better stop now because I got a weak heart
You upset me baby, yes, you upset me baby
Well, like being hit by a fallen tree
Woman, what you do to me

###B.B. King
###Sweet Sixteen
When I first met you, baby
Baby, you were just sweet sixteen
When I first met you, baby
Baby, you were just sweet sixteen
You just left your home then, woman
Ah, the sweetest thing I'd ever seen

But you wouldn't do nothing, baby
You wouldn't do anything I asked to
You wouldn't do nothing for me, baby
You wouldn't do anything I asked to
You know you ran away from your home, baby
And now you wanna run away from old B. too

You know I loved you, baby
I loved you before I could call your name
You know I loved you, baby
Baby I loved you, I love you before I could call your name
Well, it seems like everything I do now baby
Everything I do is in vain

My brother's in Korea, baby
My sister's down in New Orleans
Brother's in Korea baby
My sister's down in New Orleans
You know I'm having so much trouble woman
Baby, I wonder, what in the world is gonna happen to me

You know I love you
and I'll do anything you tell me to
You know I love you
and I'll do anything you tell me to
Well, there ain't nothing in the world, woman
Babe, it ain't nothing
Nothing in the world I wouldn't do it for you

You can treat me mean, baby
But I'll keep on loving you just the same
You can treat me mean baby
But I'll keep on loving you just the same
But one of these days, baby
You're gonna give a lot of money
To hear someone call my name

Yes, sweet sixteen baby... sweet sixteen...
Yes, the sweetest thing baby
The sweetest thing I ever seen
You know I'm having so much trouble, woman
Baby I wonder
Yes I wonder
Baby I wonder
Oh, I wonder what in the world's gonna happen to me

###B.B. King
###Don't Answer The Door
Woman, I don't wanna a soul
Hangin' around my house when I'm not at home

Oh, I don't want a soul, baby
Hangin' around my house when I'm not at home
I don't want you to answer the door for nobody, baby
Oh, when you're home and you know you're all alone

I don't want your sister coming by
Because the little girl she talk too much
If she wanna come either visit us
Tell her to meet us Sunday down at the church

'Cause I don't want a soul, baby
Hangin' around my house when I'm not at home
Yes, I don't want you to answer the door for nobody, baby
Oh, when you're home and you know you're all alone

If your mother wanna visit us
Tell her I get home 'bout the break a day
And that's too late that visit anybody, baby
So tell her to please stay away

'Cause I don't want a soul, baby
Hangin' around my house when I'm not at home
Yes, I don't want you to open the door for anybody, baby
Oh, when you're home and you know you're all alone

Now if you feel a little sick, baby
And you know you're home all alone
I don't want the doctor at my house, baby
You just suffer till I get home

'Cause I don't want a soul, baby
Hangin' around my house when I'm not at home
Yes, I don't want you to open the door for nobody, baby
Yeah, when you're home all alone

###B.B. King
###Why I Sing the Blues
Everybody wants to know
Why I sing the blues
Yes, I say everybody wanna know
Why I sing the blues
Well, I've been around a long time
I really have paid my dues

When I first got the blues
They brought me over on a ship
Men were standing over me
And a lot more with a whip
And everybody wanna know
Why I sing the blues
Well, I've been around a long time
Mm, I've really paid my dues

I've laid in a ghetto flat
Cold and numb
I heard the rats tell the bedbugs
To give the roaches some
Everybody wanna know
Why I'm singing the blues
Yes, I've been around a long time
People, I've paid my dues

I stood in line
Down at the County Hall
I heard a man say, "We're gonna build
Some new apartments for y'all"
And everybody wanna know
Yes, they wanna know
Why I'm singing the blues
Yes, I've been around a long, long time
Yes, I've really, really paid my dues

Now I'm gonna play Lucille.

My kid's gonna grow up
Gonna grow up to be a fool
'Cause they ain't got no more room
No more room for him in school
And everybody wanna know
Everybody wanna know
Why I'm singing the blues
I say I've been around a long time
Yes, I've really paid some dues

Yeah, you know the company told me
Guess you're born to lose
Everybody around me, people
It seems like everybody got the blues
But I had 'em a long time
I've really, really paid my dues
You know I ain't ashamed of it, people
I just love to sing my blues

I walk through the cities, people
On my bare feet
I had a fill of catfish and chitterlings
Up and down Beal Street
You know I'm singing the blues
Yes, I really
I just have to sing my blues
I've been around a long time
People, I've really, really paid my dues

Now Father Time is catching up with me
Gone is my youth
I look in the mirror everyday
And let it tell me the truth
I'm singing the blues
Mm, I just have to sing the blues
I've been around a long time
Yes, yes, I've really paid some dues

Yeah, they told me everything
Would be better out in the country
Everything was fine
I caught me a bus uptown, baby
And every people, all the people
Got the same trouble as mine
I got the blues, huh huh
I say I've been around a long time
I've really paid some dues

One more time, fellows!

Blind man on the corner
Begging for a dime
The rollers come and caught him
And throw him in the jail for a crime
I got the blues
Mm, I'm singing my blues
I've been around a long time
Mm, I've really paid some dues

Can we do just one more?

Oh I thought I'd go down to the welfare
To get myself some grits and stuff
But a lady stand up and she said
"You haven't been around long enough"
That's why I got the blues
Mm, the blues
I say, I've been around a long time
I've really, really paid my dues

Fellows, tell them one more time.

Ha, ha, ha. That's all right, fellows.
Yeah!

###Muddy Waters
###Long Distance Call
You say you love me, darling
Please, call me on the phone sometime
You say you love me, darling
Please, call me on the phone sometime
When I hear your voice
Ease my worried mind

One of these days
I'm gonna show you how nice a man can be
One of these days
I'm gonna show you just how nice a man can be
I'm gonna buy you a brand new Cadillac
If you only speak some good words about me

Hear my phone ringing
Sound like a long-distance call
Hear my phone keep ringing
Sound like a long-distance call
When I picked up my receiver
The party said "another mule kicking in your stall"

###Muddy Waters
###Mannish Boy
Ooh, yeah, ooh, yeah

Everythin', everythin', everytin's gonna be alright this mornin'
Ooh yeah, whoa
Now when I was a young boy, at the age of five
My mother said I was, gonna be the greatest man alive
But now I'm a man, way past 21
Want you to believe me baby,
I had lot's of fun
I'm a man
I spell mm, a child, n
That represents man
No be, O child, Y1
That mean mannish boy
I'm a man
I'm a full grown man
I'm a man
I'm a natural born lovers man
I'm a man
I'm a rollin' stone
I'm a man
I'm a hoochie coochie man

Sittin' on the outside, just me and my mate
You know I'm made to move you honey,
Come up two hours late
Wasn't that a man
I spell mm, a child, n
That represents man
No be, O child, Y1
That mean mannish boy
I'm a man
I'm a full grown man
Man
I'm a natural born lovers man
Man
I'm a rolllin' stone
Man-child
I'm a hoochie coochie man

The line I shoot will never miss
When I make love to a woman,
She can't resist
I think I go down,
To old Kansas Stew
I'm gonna bring back my second cousin,
That little Johnny Cocheroo
All you little girls,
Sittin' out at that line
I can make love to you woman,
In five minutes time
Ain't that a man
I spell mm, a child, n
That represents man
No be, o' child, Y1
That mean mannish boy
Man
I'm a full grown man
Man
I'm a natural born lovers man
Man
I'm a rollin' stone
I'm a man-child
I'm a hoochie coochie man
Well, well, well, well
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry
Don't hurt me, don't hurt me child
Don't hurt me, don't hurt, don't hurt me child
Well, well, well, well

Yeah

###Muddy Waters
###I Am Your Hoochie Coochie Man
The gypsy woman told my mother 
Before I was born 
I got a boy child's comin' 
He's gonna be a son of a gun 
He gonna make pretty women's 

Jump and shout 
Then the world wanna know 
What this all about 
But you know I'm him 
Everybody knows I'm him 
Well you know I'm the 
Hoochie coochie man 
Everybody knows I'm him 

I got a 
Black cat bone 
I got a 
Mojo 
Too 
I got the 

Johnny Concheroo 
I'm gonna mess with you 
I'm gonna make you girls 
Lead me by my hand 
Then the world will know 
The hoochie coochie man 
But you know I'm him 
Everybody knows I'm him 
Oh you know I'm the hoochie coochie man 

Everybody knows I'm him 
On the seventh hours 
On the seventh day 
On the seventh month 
The seven doctors say 
He was born for good luck 

And that you'll see 
I got seven hundred dollars 
Don't you mess with me 
But you know I'm him 
Everybody knows I'm him 
Well you know I'm the hoochie coochie man 
Everybody knows I'm him

###Muddy Waters
###Rollin' And Tumblin'
Rollin' And Tumblin'

Well, I rolled and I tumbled, cried the whole night long
Well, I rolled and I tumbled, cried the whole night long
Well, I woke up this mornin', didn't know right from wrong

Well, I told my baby, before I left that town
Well, I told my baby, before I left that town
Well, don't you let nobody, tear my barrelhouse down

Well, ahh, mmm-hmmm, owww, oww ooo, aww, oww, oh
Aaa, mmm-hmmm, oww, oh oh oh owww, oww ooo, aww, oww, oh

Well, if the river was whiskey, and I was a divin' duck
Well, if the river was whiskey, and I was a divin' duck
Well, I would dive to the bottom, never would I come up

Well, I could a had a religion, this bad old thing instead
Well, I could a had a religion, this bad old thing instead
Well, all whiskey and women, would not let me pray

###Muddy Waters
###My Home Is The Delta
Well, my home's in the delta
Way out on that farmer's road
Now you know I'm leaving Chicago
And people, I sure do hate to go

Now you know I'm leaving here in the morning
Won't be back no more
Well, I know my little baby
This girl don't know what a shape I'm in

You know I haven't had no lovin'
Boy, you know, in God-knows-when
Now you know I just been sittin' here thinkin'
Wondering where in the world she benn

Look out

Well, I feel like cryin'
But you know, the tears won't come down
I feel like cryin'
But you know, the tears won't come down
Ah, you know I got a funny feelin'
I'm gonna have to leave your town

Hm-mm-mm have mercy

Hm-mm-mm
Ah, you know I just been sittin' here thinkin'
Wondering where in the world she been

###Muddy Waters
###Rolling Stone
Well, I wish I was a catfish,
Swimmin in a oh, deep, blue sea
I would have all you good lookin women,
Fishin, fishin after me
fishin after me
fishin after me
Sure 'nough, a-after me
Sure 'nough, a-after me
Oh 'nough, oh 'nough, sure 'nough

I went to my baby's house,
And I sit down oh, on her steps
She said, "C'mon in now, Muddy
You know, my husband just now left
Sure 'nough, he just now left
Sure 'nough, he just now left
Oh Lord, oh well, oh well

Well, my mother told my father,
Just before hmmm, I was born,
"I got a boy child's comin',
Gonna be, he gonna be a rollin' stone,
Sure 'nough, he's a rollin' stone
Sure 'nough, he's a rollin' stone"
Oh well he's a, oh well he's a, oh well he's a

Well, I feel, yes I feel,
Feel that I could lay down oh, time ain't long
I'm gonna catch the first thing smokin',
Back, back down the road I'm goin'
Back down the road I'm goin'
Back down the road I'm goin'
Sure 'nough back, sure 'nough back

###Muddy Waters
###Trouble No More
Don't care how long you gone
I don't care how long you staying
But, good kind treatment
Gonna bring you home someday
But someday baby
You ain't gonna trouble poor me anymore

You just keep on betting
That the dice won't pass
Well you know, darling
You are living too fast
But someday, baby
You ain't gonna trouble poor me anymore

I'm gonna tell everybody
In your neighborhood
That you's a sweet little girl
But, you don't mean me no good
But someday baby
You ain't gonna trouble poor me anymore

Well, I know you're leavin
Well, you call that gone
Well, without love
You can't stay long
But someday baby
You ain't gonna trouble poor me anymore

Well, goodbye baby
Come on, shake my hand
I don't want no woman
You can have a man
But someday baby
You ain't gonna trouble poor me anymore

###Muddy Waters
###Forty Days and Forty Nights
Forty days and forty nights
Since my baby left this town
Sunshinin' all day long
But the rain keep comin' down
She's my life I need her so
Why she left I just don't know

Forty days and forty nights
Since I set right down and cried
Keep rainin' all the time
But the river is runnin' dry
Lord help me it just ain't right
I love that girl with all-a my might

Forty days and forty nights
Since my baby broke my heart
Searchin' for her in a while
Like a blind man in the dark
Love can make a poor man rich
Or break his heart I don't know which

Forty days and forty nights
Like a ship out on the sea
Prayin' for her each night
That she would come back-a home to me
Life is love and love is right
I hope she come back home tonight

###Muddy Waters
###Louisana Blues
m goin' down in Louisiana,
Baby, behind the sun.
I'm goin' down in Louisiana,
Baby, behind the sun.
Well, you know I just found out
My trouble just begun.

###Muddy Waters
###Still A Fool
Well, now, there's two, there's two trains running
Well, they ain't never, no, going my way
Well, now, one run at midnight and the other one
Running just 'fore day
It's running just 'fore day
It's running just 'fore day
Oh Lord, sure 'nough they is
Oh well

Mm mm, ho ho
Somebody help me, ho, with these blues
Well, now, she's the one I'm loving, she's the one
I do hate to lose
I do hate to lose
I do hate to lose
Oh Lord, sure 'nough I do
Oh well

I been crazy, yes, I been a fool
I been crazy, oh, all of my life
Well I done fell in love with a
With another man's wife
With another man's wife
With another man's wife
Oh Lord, sure 'nough I done
Oh well

Lord, she's so long and tall
Till she weep like a willow tree
Well, now, they say she's no good, but she's all right
She's all right with me
She's all right, she's all right
She's all right, she's all right

###Robert Johnson
###Cross Road Blues
Went to the crossroad, fell down on my knees
I went to the crossroad, fell down on my knees
Asked the Lord above "Have mercy, now save poor Bob, if you please"

Yeoo, standin' at the crossroad, tried to flag a ride
Ooo eeee, I tried to flag a ride
Didn't nobody seem to know me, babe, everybody pass me by

Standin' at the crossroad, baby, risin' sun goin' down
Standin' at the crossroad, baby, eee, eee, risin' sun goin' down
I believe to my soul, now, poor Bob is sinkin' down

You can run, you can run, tell my friend Willie Brown
You can run, you can run, tell my friend Willie Brown
That I got the crossroad blues this mornin', Lord, babe, I'm sinkin' down

And I went to the crossroad, mama, I looked east and west
I went to the crossroad, baby, I looked east and west
Lord, I didn't have no sweet woman, ooh well, babe, in my distress

###Robert Johnson
###Kindhearted Woman Blues
I got a kindhearted woman, do anything in this world for me
I got a kindhearted woman, do anything in this world for me
But these evil-hearted women, man, they will not let me be

I love my baby, my baby don't love me
I love my baby, my baby don't love me
But I really love that woman, can't stand to leave her be

Ain't but the one thing, makes Mister Johnson drink
I's worried about how you treat me, baby, I begin to think
Oh, babe, my life don't feel the same
You breaks my heart, when you call Mister So-and-So's name

She's a kindhearted woman, she studies evil all the time
She's a kindhearted woman, she studies evil all the time
You well's to kill me, as to have it on your mind

###Robert Johnson
###Hell Hound On My Trail
 got to keep movin', I got to keep movin'
Blues fallin' down like hail, blues fallin' down like hail
Hmmm-mmm, blues fallin' down like hail, blues fallin' down like hail

And the days keeps on worryin' me
There's a hellhound on my trail, hellhound on my trail
Hellhound on my trail

If today was Christmas Eve, if today was Christmas Eve
And tomorrow was Christmas Day
If today was Christmas Eve, and tomorrow was Christmas Day
Aw, wouldn't we have a time, baby?

All I would need my little sweet rider just
To pass the time away, huh-huh
To pass the time away

You sprinkled hot foot powder, mmm
Mmm, around my door, all around my door
You sprinkled hot foot powder
All around your daddy's door, hmm-hmm-hmm

It keep me with ramblin' mind, rider
Every old place I go, every old place I go

I can tell the wind is risin', the leaves tremblin' on the tree
Tremblin' on the tree
I can tell the wind is risin', leaves tremblin' on the tree
Hmm-hmm hmm-mmm

All I need's my little sweet woman
And to keep my company, hey, hey, hey
My company

###Robert Johnson
###Love In Vain
And I followed her to the station, with her suitcase in my hand,
And I followed her to the station, with her suitcase in my hand.
Well, it's hard to tell, it's hard to tell, when all your love's in vain,
All my love's in vain.

When the train rolled up to the station, I looked her in the eye,
When the train rolled up to the station, and I looked her in the eye.
Well, I was lonesome, I felt so lonesome, and I could not help but cry.
All my love's in vain.

When the train, it left the station, there was two lights on behind,
When the train, it left the station, there was two lights on behind,
Well, the blue light was my blues, and the red light was my mind.
All my love's in vain.

Uumh, Willie Mae, Uumh, Willie Mae, Uumh uumh, all my love's in vain.

###Robert Johnson
###Come On In My Kitchen
Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm
Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm

You better come on in my kitchen
Well, it's goin' to be rainin' outdoors
Ah, the woman I love, took from my best friend
Some joker got lucky, stole her back again
You better come on in my kitchen
It's goin' to be rainin' outdoors

Oh, she's gone, I know she won't come back
I've taken the last nickel out of her nation sack
You better come on in my kitchen
It's goin' to be rainin' outdoors
Oh, can't you hear that wind howl?
Oh, can't you hear that wind would howl?
You better come on in my kitchen
Well, it's goin' to be rainin' outdoors

When a woman gets in trouble, everybody throws her down

Lookin' for her good friend, none can be found
You better come on in my kitchen

Babe, it's goin' to be rainin' outdoors
Wintertime's comin', it's gon' be slow
You can't make the winter, babe, that's dry, long, so
You better come on in my kitchen, 'cause it's goin' to be rainin' outdoors

###Robert Johnson
###Me And The Devil Blues
Early this morning
When you knocked upon my door
Early this morning, ooh
When you knocked upon my door
And I said "hello Satan
I believe it's time to go"

Me and the Devil
Was walkin' side-by-side
Me and the Devil, ooh
Was walking side-by-side
I'm going to beat my woman
Until I get satisfied

She said "you don't see why
That I will dog her 'round"
Now baby you know you ain't doin' me right, now
She say "you don't see why, hoo
That I would dog her 'round"
It must-a been that old evil spirit
So deep down in the ground
You may bury my body
Down by the highway side

Baby, I don't care where you bury my body when I'm dead and gone
You may bury my body, hoo
Down by the highway side
So my old evil spirit
Can get a Greyhound bus and ride

###Robert Johnson
###Ramblin' On My Mind
I got ramblin', I got ramblin' on my mind
I got ramblin', I got ramblin' all on my mind
Hate to leave my baby, but you treats me so unkind

I got mean things, I got mean things all on my mind
Little girl, little girl, I got mean things all on my mind
Hate to leave you here, babe, but you treats me so unkind

Runnin' down to the station, catch the first mail train I see
I think I hear her comin' now
Runnin' down to the station, catch the old first mail train I see
I got the blues about Miss So-and-So and the child got the blues about me

And I'm leavin' this mornin', with my arm' fold' up and cryin'
And I'm leavin' this mornin', with my arm' fold' up and cryin'
Hate to leave my baby, but she treats me so unkind

###Robert Johnson
###Terraplane Blues
And I feel so lonesome, you hear me when I moan
And I feel so lonesome, you hear me when I moan
Who been drivin' my Terraplane for you since I been gone?

I'd said I flash your lights, mama, you horn won't even blow
Somebody's been runnin' my batteries down on this machine
I even flash my lights, mama, this horn won't even blow
Got a short in this connection, hoo well, babe, it's way down below

I'm goin' heist your hood, mama, I'm bound to check your oil
I'm goin' heist your hood, mama, mmm, I'm bound to check your oil
I got a woman that I'm lovin', way down in Arkansas

Now, you know the coils ain't even buzzin', little generator won't get the spark
Motor's in a bad condition, you gotta have these batteries charged
But I'm cryin', please, please don't do me wrong
Who been drivin' my Terraplane now for you since I been gone?

Mr. highway man, please don't block the road
Please, please don't block the road
'Cause she's reachin' a cold one hundred and I'm booked and I got to go

Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm
You, you hear me weep and moan
Who been drivin' my Terraplane now for you since I been gone?

I'm gon' get down in this connection, keep on tanglin' with your wires
I'm gon' get down in this connection, oh well, keep on tanglin' with these wires
And when I mash down on your little starter, then your sparkplug will give me fire

###Robert Johnson
###Drunken Hearted Man
I’m a drunken hearted man
my life seem so misery
I’m the drunken hearted man
my life seem so misery
And if I could change my way of livin’
it t’would mean so much to me

I been dogged and I been driven
eve’ since I left my mother’s home
I been dogged and I been driven
eve’ since I left my mother’s home
And I can’t see no reason why
that I can’t leave these no-goods womens alone

My father died and left me
my poor mother done the best that she could
My father died and left me
my poor mother done the best she could
Every man likes that game you call love
but it don’t mean no man no good
Now, I’m the drunken hearted man
and sin was the cause of it all
spoken: Oh, play ’em now
I’m a drunken hearted man
and sin was the cause of it all
And the day that you get weak for no-good women
that’s the day that you bound to fall

###Robert Johnson
###Last Fair
It's the last fair deal goin' down, 
last fair deal goin' down
It's the last fair deal goin' down, good Lord,
on that Gulfport Island Road

Eh, Ida Belle, don't cry this time 
Ida Belle, don't cry this time 
If you cry about a nickel, you'll die 'bout a dime 
She wouldn't cry, but the money won't mine

I love the way you do, 
I love the way you do 
I love the way you do, good Lord, 
on this Gulfport Island Road

My captain's so mean on me, 
my captain's so mean on me 
My captain's so mean on me, good Lord, 
on this Gulfport Island Road

Camp A, B, and C 
Camp A, B, and C 
Camp A, B, and C, good Lord, 
on that Gulfport Island Road

Ah, this last fair deal goin' down, 
It's the last fair deal goin' down 
This' the last fair deal goin' down, good Lord, 
on this Gulfport Island Road

I'm workin' my way back home, 
I'm working my way back home 
I'm workin' my way back home, good Lord, 
on this Gulfport Island Road

And that thing don't keep ringin' so soon 
That thing don't keep ringin' so soon 
And that thing don't keep ringin' so soon, good Lord, 
on that Gulfed-and-Port Island Road

###Howlin’ Wolf
###Spoonful
It could be a spoonful of coffee
It could be a spoonful of tea
But one little spoon of your precious love
Is good enough for me

Men lie about that spoonful
Some cry about that spoonful
Some die about that spoonful
Everybody fight about a spoonful
That spoon, that spoon, that spoonful

It could be a spoonful of water
To save you from the desert sand
But one spoon of love1 from my forty-five
Will save you from another man
Men lie about that spoonful
Some cry about that spoonful
Some die about that spoonful
Everybody fight about a spoonful
That spoon, that spoon, that spoonful
That spoon, that spoon, that spoonful

It could be a spoonful of sugar
It could be a spoonful of tea
But one little spoon of your precious love
Is good enough for me
Men lie about that spoonful
Some cry about that spoonful
Some die about that spoonful
Everybody fight about a spoonful
That spoon, that spoon, that spoonful
That spoon, that spoon, that spoonful
That spoon, that spoon, that spoonful
That spoon, that spoon, that spoonful

###Howlin’ Wolf
###Smokestack Lightnin'
Ah-oh, smokestack lightnin'
Shinin', just like gold
Why don't ya hear me cryin'?
A-whoo-hooo, oooo
Whooo
Whoa-oh, tell me, baby,
What's the, matter with you?
Why don't ya hear me cryin'?
Whoo-hooo, whoo-hooo
Whooo
Whoa-oh, tell me, baby,
Where did ya, stay last night?
A-why don't ya hear me cryin'?
Whoo-hooo, whoo-hooo
Whooo
Whoa-oh, stop your train,
Let her, go for a ride
Why don't ya hear me cryin'?
Whoo-hooo, whoo-hooo
Whooo
Whoa-oh, fare ya well
Never see, a you no more
A-why don't ya hear me cryin'?
Oooo, whoo-hooo, whoo-hooo
Whooo
Whoa-oh, who been here baby since,
I-I been gone, a little, bitty boy?
Girl, be on
A-whoo-hooo, whoo-hooo
Whooo

###Howlin’ Wolf
###The Red Rooster
Well, I got a little red rooster
Too lazy to crow for day
Well, I got a little red rooster
Too lazy to crow for day

Keep everything in the barnyard
Upset in every way
Well, the dogs begin to bark
Hound begin to howl

Well, the dogs begin to bark
Hound begin to howl
Oh, watch out, strange kind people
Little red rooster is on the prowl

Oh, if you see my little red rooster
Please drag him home
Well, if you see my little red rooster
Please drag him home

There no peace in the barnyard
Since the little red rooster been gone
I got a little red rooster
Too lazy to crow for day

Oh, I got a little red rooster
Too lazy to crow for day
Keep everything in the barnyard
Upset in every way

###Howlin’ Wolf
###I Asked For Water
Oh, I asked her for water, oh, she brought me gasoline
Oh, I asked her for water, oh, she brought me gasoline
That's the troublingest woman
That I ever seen

Oh, the church bell tollin', oh, the hearse come driving slow
Oh, the church bell tollin', oh, the hearse come driving slow
I hope my baby
Don't leave me no more

Oh, tell me baby, oh, when are you coming back home?
Oh, tell me baby, oh, when are you coming back home?
You know I love you, baby
But you've been gone too long

###Howlin’ Wolf
###Back Door Man
I am, a back door man
I am, a back door man
Well the, men don't know, but the little girls understand

When everybody's tryin' to sleep
I'm somewhere making my, midnight creep
Yes in the morning, when the rooster crow
Something tell me, I got to go

I am, a back door man
I am, a back door man
Well the, men don't know, but little girls understand

They, take me to the doctor, shot full o' holes
Nurse cried, please save the soul
Killed him for murder, first degree
Judge's wife cried, let the man go free

I am, a back door man
I am, a back door man
Well the, men don't know, but little girls understand

Stand out there, cop's wife cried
Don't take him down, rather be dead
Six feets in the ground
When you come home you can eat, pork and beans
I eats mo' chicken, any man seen

###Howlin’ Wolf
###Wang Dang Doodle
 ell Automatic Slim , tell Razor Totin' Jim
Tell Butcher Knife Totin' Annie, tell Fast Talking Fanny
A we gonna pitch a ball, a down to that union hall
We gonna romp and tromp till midnight
We gonna fuss and fight till daylight
We gonna pitch a wang dang doodle all night long
All night long, All night long, All night long

Tell Kudu-Crawlin' Red, tell Abyssinian Ned
Tell ol' Pistol Pete, everybody gonna meet
Tonight we need no rest, we really gonna throw a mess
We gonna to break out all of the windows,
we gonna kick down all the doors
We gonna pitch a wang dang doodle all night long
All night long, All night long, All night long

Tell Fats and Washboard Sam, that everybody gonna to jam
Tell Shaky and Boxcar Joe, we got sawdust on the floor
Tell Peg and Caroline Dye, we gonna have a time
When the fish scent fill the air, there'll be snuff juice everywhere
We gonna pitch a wang dang doodle all night long
All night long, All night long, All night long

###Howlin’ Wolf
###How Many More Years
How many more years?
Have I got to let you dog me around
How many more years?
Oh, I got to let you dog me around
I'd soon rather be dead
Sleeping six feet in the ground

I'm gonna fall on my knees
I'm gonna raise up my right hand
I'm gonna fall on my knees
I'm gonna raise up my right hand
Say, I'd feel much better, darlin'
If you'd just only understand

I'm goin' upstairs
I'm gonna bring back down my clothes
I'm goin' upstairs
I'm gonna bring back down my clothes, do them all
If anybody ask about me
Just tell 'em I walked out on

###Howlin’ Wolf
###Goin' Down Slow
Man
You know I done enjoyed things that kings and queens will never have
In fact, kings and queens can never get
And they don't even know about
And good times, mmm-mmm

I have had my fun
If I never get well no more
I have had my fun
If I never get well no more
Oh, my health is fading, oh
Oh, yes I'm going down slow

Now lookit here
I did not say I was a millionaire
But I said I have spent more money than a millionaire
'Cause if I had kept all the money then I had already spent
I would've been a millionaire a long time ago
And women, great googly-moogly!

Please write my mama
Tell her the shape I'm in
Please write my ol' mother
Tell her the shape I'm in
Tell her to pray for, oh
Forgive me for my sins

###Howlin’ Wolf
###Moanin' At Midnight
Well, somebody knocking on my door
Well, somebody knocking on my door
Well, I'm so worried, don't know where to go

Well, somebody calling me, calling on my telephone
Well, somebody calling me, over my telephone
Well, keep on calling, tell them I'm not at home

Well, don't not worry, Daddy has gone to bed

###Howlin’ Wolf
###Shake For Me
Sure look good, but it don't mean a thing to me
Sure look good, but it don't mean a thing to me
I got a hip-shaking woman, shake like a willow tree

You better wait baby, you got back a little too late
You better wait baby, you got back a little too late
I got a cool-shaking baby, shake like jello on a plate

When my baby walk, you know she's fine and mellow
When my baby walk, you know she's fine and mellow
Every time she stops, her flesh it shake like Jello

Oh, shake it baby, shake it for me
Oh, shake lil' baby, shake it for me
Oh, shake it little baby, shake like a willow tree


###John Lee Hooker
###Boogie Chillen'
Well, my mama, she didn't 'low me just to stay out all night long, oh Lord
Well, my mama didn't 'low me just to stay out all night long
I didn't care what she didn't 'low--I would boogie-woogie anyhow

When I first came to town, people, I was walkin' down Hastings Street
Everybody was talkin' about the Henry Swing Club
I decided I drop in there that night
When I got there, I say, "Yes, people"
They was really havin' a ball
Yes, I know
Boogie Chillen'

One night I was layin' down
I heard mama and papa talkin'
I heard papa tell mama let that boy boogie-woogie
It's in him and it got to come out
And I felt so good
Went on boogiein' just the same

###John Lee Hooker
###Crawlin' King Snake
You know I'm a crawlin' king snake, baby, and I rules my den
You know I'm a crawlin' king snake, baby, and I rules my den
I don't want you hangin' around my mate; wanna use her for myself

You know you caught me crawlin', baby, when the, when the grass was very high
I'm just gonna keep on crawlin' now, baby, until the day I die
Because I'm a crawlin' king snake, baby, and I rules my den
Don't want you hangin' around my mate; wanna use her for myself

You know I'm gon' crawl up to your window, baby
Wanna crawl up to your door; you got anything I want, baby?
Wanna crawl up on your floor
Because I'm a crawlin' king snake, baby, and I rules my den

You know you caught me crawlin', baby, when the, when the grass was very high
I'm just gonna keep on crawlin' now, baby, until the day I die
Because I'm a crawlin' king snake, baby, and I rules my den

###John Lee Hooker
###Dimples
I love the way you walk
I love the way you walk
I'm crazy 'bout your walk
I love the way you walk
You my babe I got my eyes on you

I like the way you switch
I like the way you switch
I like the way you switch
I like the way you switch
You my babe I got my eyes on you

You got dimples in your jaw
You got dimples in your jaw
You got dimples in your jaw
You got dimples in your jaw
You my babe I got my eyes on you

Well, I see you every day
Well, I see you every day
If you need to look
Well, I see you every day
Well, I see you every day
You my babe I got my eyes on you

###John Lee Hooker
###I'm In The Mood
I'm in the mood baby, I'm in the mood for love
I'm in the mood baby, I'm in the mood for love
I'm in the mood, I'm in the mood, baby, I'm in the mood for love
I said night time is the right time, to be with the one you love
You know when night come baby, God know, you're so far away
I'm in the mood, I'm in the mood baby, I'm in the mood for love
I'm in the mood, in the mood, baby, in the mood for love
I said yes, my mama told me, to leave that girl alone
But my mama didn't know, God know, girl was puttin' down
I'm in the mood, I'm in the mood baby, in the mood for love
I'm in the mood, I'm in the mood, baby, in the mood for love

###John Lee Hooker
###One Bourbon, One Scotch, One Beer
One bourbon, one scotch, and one beer
One bourbon, one scotch, and one beer
Hey, mister bartender, come here
I want another drink and I want it now

My baby she gone, she been gone two night
I ain't seen my baby since night before last
One bourbon, one scotch, and one beer

And then I sit there, gettin' high, mellow
Knocked out, feeling good, and by the time
I looked on the wall at the old clock on the wall
By that time it was ten thirty, daddy

I looked down the bar at the bartender
He said, "Now what do you want Johnny?"
One bourbon, one scotch, and one beer

Well, my baby she gone, she been gone two night
I ain't seen my baby since night before last
I wanna get drunk till I'm off of my mind
One bourbon, one scotch, and one beer

And I sat there, gettin' high, stoned
Knocked out, and by the time
I looked on the wall at the old clock again
And by that time it was a quarter to two
Last call for alcohol, I said
Hey, mister bartender, what do you want?"

One bourbon, one scotch, and one beer
One bourbon, one scotch, and one beer
One bourbon, one scotch, and one beer

###John Lee Hooker
###Hobo Blues
When I first thought to hobo'in, hobo'in
I took a freight train to be my friend, oh Lord
You know I hoboed, hoboed, hoboed, hoboed
Hoboed a long, long way from home, oh Lord

Yes, my mother followed me that mornin', me that mornin', boy
She followed me down to the yard, oh yeah
She said, "My son he's gone, he's gone, he's gone
Yes, he's gone in a poor some wear, oh yeah"

Yes, I left my dear old mother, dear old mother
I left my honor, need a crime, oh Lord
Take care of my child
Take care, take care of my child

###John Lee Hooker
###One Of These Days Things Gonna Change
One of these days,
Things gonna change
One of these days
Tings gonna change
You'll try not baby
Afterwhile gonna be mine, gonna be mine
One of these days
I'm old and lonely baby
Cry Cry Crying
Wont be long long
Things gonna change

Sometime, in the middle of the night
And you're so long, and so long and so long
Tings gonna change, things gonna change
Change change change
Tings gonna change,

Further on up the road baby, things gonna change
Change change change
Change change change
Change baby
You'll try not to leave
But after while Gonna be mine
My time my time baby

Things gonna change
Change change change
Change change change
Things gonna change
Yes it is
Things gonna change
Change change change
Change change change

Change change change
Change change change

Things gonna change
Things gonna change
Things gonna change
Things gonna change change change change
Things gonna change

###John Lee Hooker
###Baby Lee
Baby Lee, don't do me like you do
Baby Lee, don't do me like you do
I love you, baby; you never treat me right

Takin' you downtown, you carried me through the mill
Takin' you downtown, baby, you carried me through the mill
Now you wanna treat me, and treat me like a child

Baby Lee, please, don't do me wrong
Baby Lee, please, don't do me wrong
I love you, gal; I just can't stand your way

Baby Lee, you know you ain't treat me right
Baby Lee, you know you ain't treat me right
You take all my money, wanna treat me like a child

###John Lee Hooker
###Burnin' Hell
Everybody talk about it 
Burning Hell 
Ain't no heaven, I know 
Ain't no Burning Hell 
Where I die I go 
Can't nobody tell

I am going, Deacon Jones
I went down to the church house
I got down on my bended knee
I prayed, I prayed all night, I prayed
Deacon Jones, pray for me

I went down to the church house
I got down on my knee
I begged, Deacon Jones to pray for me
He said, son, here my hand

Ain't no heaven
Ain't no Burning Hell

Ain't no heaven, Ain't no heaven, no Burning Hell
When I die, where I go, nobody know

No Burning Hell
Ain't no burning, no Burning Hell
When I die, in my grave, nobody know where I'm going
Ain't no heaven, ain't no hell
When I die, nobody tell

Hey hey, Hey hey
Deacon Jones, pray for me

I don't believe, I don't believe in no heaven
I don't believe in no hell
When I die, where I go, nobody know

###John Lee Hooker
###Whiskey and Wimmen'
Whiskey and wimmen almost wrecked my life
Whiskey and wimmen almost wrecked my life
Were'nt for whiskey and wimmin, I'd have money today

Nightlife, nightlife, nightlife
Ain't no good, ain't no good for me
I had a good start, but wimmen and whiskey tore it down

Whiskey and wimmen ain't no good for me
Whiskey and wimmen ain't no good, ain't no good for me
I had a lot of money and big fine car, but I lost everything I had
Aww I did

###Buddy Guy
###First Time I Met The Blues
The first time I met the blues
People, you know I was walkin', I was walkin' down through the woods
Yes, the first time, the first time I met you, blues
Blues you know I was walkin', I was walkin' down through the woods
Yes, I've watched my house burnin' blues
Blues, you know you done me, you done me all the harm that you could

The blues got after me
People, you know they ran me from tree to tree
Yes, the blues got after me
Blues, you know you ran me, ran me from tree to tree
Yes, you should-a heard me beg ya, blues
Ah, blues, don't murder me

Yes, good mornin', blues
Blues, I wonder, I wonder what you're doin' here so soon
Yes, good mornin', good mornin', good mornin', mister blues
Blues, I wonder, I keep wonderin' what you're doin' here so soon
Yes, you know you'll be with me every mornin', blues
Every night and every noon
Oh, yeah

###Buddy Guy
###Damn Right I've Got the Blues
You damn right, I've got the blues,
From my head down to my shoes
You damn right, I've got the blues,
From my head down to my shoes

I can't win, cause I don't have a thing to lose

I stopped by my daughters house
You know I just want to use the phone
I stopped by my daughters house
You know I just want to use the phone

You know my new grand baby came to the door
And said, granddaddy you know ain't no one at home

I said now look out

You damn right, I've got the blues,
From my head down to my shoes
You damn right, I've got the blues,
From my head down to my shoes

You know I can't win, now people, cause I don't have a thing to lose

Alright

You damn right, I've got the blues,
You damn right, I've got the blues,
You damn right, I've got the blues,
You damn right, I've got the blues,
Yeah

###Buddy Guy
###Stone Crazy
Woman you must be stone down crazy
Either you're going to lose your mind
Yes I said baby you must be stone crazy
Either you're going to lose your mind
Yes I wanna know how could you treat me so dirty baby
You must think my little heart is made of iron

Lord as I sit here in my dark room
Tears rolling down from my eyes
Yes I sit, I sit here in my dark room
Tears rolling all down from my eyes
Yes you know my little baby looked at me and said daddy
Ooh, God knows you're the hurted child

Oh yeah
Somebody come and get me

Yes I think I'm going back down south
People where the weather suits my clothes
Yes I said I'm going back down south
People where the weather suits my clothes
Yes you know playing around in this big city so long man
Ooh, 'til I'm almost just done froze

Darling you must be stone crazy
Or either you're going to lose your mind
Yes I said woman you must be stone down crazy
Either you're going to lose your mind
Yes I wanna know how could you treat me so low down and dirty
You must be think my little heart is made of iron

Wow as I sit here in my dark room
Tears rolling all down my eyes
Yes I sit, I sit right here right here in my dark room
Tears rolling all down from my eyes
Yes you know my little girl looked at me and said
Ooh, my daddy is a hurted child

Oh, look-a here now
Somebody come here

Lord I believe I'm going back down south
Where the weather suits my clothes
Yes I believe I'm going back down south
People where the weather suits my clothes
Yes you know that I've played around in these big cities so long man
Oh, 'till I'm almost done froze

###Buddy Guy
###Ain't No Sunshine
Ain't no sunshine when she gone
It's not warm when she's away
Ain't no sunshine when she's gone
She's always gone too long
Anytime she goes away

Wonder this time where he's gone
Wonder if he's gone to stay
Ain't no sunshine when he's gone
This house just ain't no home
Anytime he goes away

I know, I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know

I know, I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know

I think I should leave the young thing alone
'Cause ain't no sunshine when she gone

Ain't no sunshine when she gone
Only darkness everyday
Ain't no sunshine when she gone
This house just ain't no home
Anytime she goes away

Anytime she goes away
Anytime she goes away
Anytime she goes away
Anytime she goes away

Anytime he goes away
Anytime she goes away
Anytime she goes away
Anytime she goes away

###Buddy Guy
###Feels Like Rain
Down here the river, meets the sea
And in the sticky heat I feel ya' open up to me
Love comes out of nowhere baby, just like a hurricane
And it feels like rain
And it feels like rain

Lying here, underneath the stars right next to you
And I'm wondering who you are and
How do you do?
How do you do, baby?
The clouds roll in across the moon
And the wind howls out your name
And it feels like rain
And it feels like rain

We never going to make that bridge tonight baby
Across lake Ponchartrain
And it feels like rain
And it feels like rain

So batten down the hatch baby
And leave your heart up your sleeve
It looks like we're in for stormy weather,
That ain't no cause for us to leave
Just lay here, in my arms
Let it wash away the pain
And it feels like rain
And it feels like rain

###Buddy Guy
###Wear You Out
I had a '54 Stratocaster
They said it wouldn't last me my whole life
I ripped and tore and banged that thing
Until it couldn't play one more night

I'm gonna wear you out
Yes I'm gonna wear you out
I ain't slowing down
Until I wear you out

I had a seventy something El Dorado
I said it ain't never gonna stop
100,000 miles and 69 days
I felt that engine drop

I'm gonna wear you out
I'm gonna wear you out
I ain't slowing down
Until I wear you out

Well they say she'd been through many men
Said she couldn't be satisfied
Said she felt the ground move twice
Before I even hit my stride

I'm gonna wear you out
Yes I've been around
I ain't slowing down
Until I wear you out

I'm gonna wear you out
I'm gonna wear my guitar out
I ain't slowing down
Until I wear you out
Because I think I'm going to
Got to got got to
Wear you out
I'm gonna wear you out
It's going down
Until I wear you out

###Buddy Guy
###Key Don't Fit
My key don't fit your lock
When I come to your door
No, I said, my key won't fit your lock
When I try to put it in your door
You know I got a funny, funny feeling
You don't want me around no more

I left a message last Monday
Just like the Monday before
By the time I've got to Friday
Lord knows I had left five or six more
Now my key don't fit your lock
But I try to stick it in your door

I saw you on the street this morning
Walking with that other man
I could tell him in holding
Much more than your little hand
Now there's talk all over neighborhood
He's thinking about steeping in

My key don't fit your lock
When I try to put it in your door
I said, my key won't fit your lock
When I try to walk it in your door
I got this funny, funny feeling
You don't want me around no more

###Buddy Guy
###One Room Country Shack
Sittin' here, thousand miles from nowhere
People, I'm in my one room country little shack
I'm sittin' here, thousand miles from nowhere
People, I'm in my own, own one room country little shack

All my worries and companion
Is a old, is a old eleven foot cotton sack

I'm gonna leave, oh, early in the mornin'
People, because I'm 'bout to go out of my mind
I'm gonna leave you early in the mornin'
People because, just because I'm 'bout to go out of my mind

I'm gonna find me some kind of good woman
Even if she's dumb, deaf, crippled or blind

Play your piano [Incomprehensible]
Yeah, yeah
Lord, you make me feel so good this morning, do it again
Have mercy, have mercy on me, have mercy on me
Alright, yes, yes, yes, oh Lord, have mercy

You don't know
You don't know how, how I feel
Lord, have mercy down in this cotton field

You don't know
People, people, you don't know how I feel
Have mercy in this cotton field

I know you're out there havin' a good time
Why don't you, why don't you make connection with me
And give me some good deal?
Let me have a little bit of Otis Spann, please

So many ways
So many ways you can get the blues
So many ways
So, so many ways you can get the blues

Yes, when you're down here on one of these cotton fields
Lord, you ain't got nothing to lose

###Buddy Guy
###My Time After A While
It's your time now baby
Ohh but it's gonna be mine after awhile
I said it's your time right now baby
Lord but it's gonna be mine after awhile
You know you know if things don't change
I'm gonna move on down

She stayed out last night
And do you know she just walked in 
The girl is gettin' ready
She's going back out again
I said just wait one minute
Just before you go
She didn't even look at me
She just turned and walked out the door

It's your time, it's your time, it's your time right now
Oh, I gotta, I gotta, I gotta feelin'
Oh, it's gonna, it's gonna, it's gonna be my time after awhile

I got a look through my window
And guess what I seen
My baby sat with another man
In a long black limosine

I said it's your time, it's your time
Yes you know I, you know I got that feelin' woman 
Baby it's gonna be my time after awhile

I just wanna talk to my baby:
And here's what I wanna say
Go ahead on and mistreat me
But every every dog got his day wow

Somebody better come here and get me baby
I just want to talk to my baby

###Buddy Guy
###Every Girl I See
You look good and you look good
You look good and you look good

Every girl I see are looking good to me
Every girl I see are looking good to me

You know the pretties girl that I've ever seen
Was a girl right here, looking like a queen
And how she looks, no words can tell,
Because all of those girls, you know they sure look well

Every girl I see are looking good to me
Every girl I see are looking good to me

And the girl I see had an angel's face
She has so mush charm and suit in laze
And what shall do, I don't know
Cause I've never felt like this before

Every girl I see are looking good to me
Every girl I see are looking good to me
Solo

Well I do anything to make that bit
You know I get exited when I see that chick
My heart gets happy and I'm full of faith
Because all of these girls, are tending mean

Every girl I see are looking good to me
Every girl I see are looking good to me

I can't put you down from no-one else
You know you look so good, I can't control myself
I'm going crazy; you know I'm not so blame
You all look lovely, pretty little thing

Every girl I see are looking good to me
Every girl I see are looking good to me

###Freddie King
###Hide Away
I don't want you to be no slave
I don't want you to work all day
I don't want your money too
I just want to make love to you
love to you
love to you
love to you

I don't want you to wash my clothes
I don't want you to keep our home
I don't want you to be true
I just want to make love to you
love to you
love to you
love to you

I can tell by the way you switch and walk
I can tell by the way you baby talk
I can see by the way you treat your man
I can love you baby until it's a crying shame

I don't want you to cook my bread
I don't want you to make my bed
I don't want you cause I'm sad and blue
I just want to make love to you
love to you
love to you
love to you

I can tell by the way you switch and walk
I can tell by the way you baby talk
I can see by the way you treat your man
I can love you baby until it's a crying shame

I don't want you to cook my bread
I don't want you to make my bed
I don't want you cause I'm sad and blue
I just want to make love to you
love to you
love to you
love to you

Let me make love to you
Let me make love to you
Let me make love to you

###Freddie King
###Big Legged Woman
I love the tip, I love the top, I love you better than a hog loves slop
'Cause you're a big legged woman, with a short short miniskirt
Promise me darlin', you'll never make me feel like dirt

Just like the vine, goes around the stump, you are mine, call me sugar lump
'Cause you're a big-legged woman, with a short short miniskirt
Promise me darlin, you'll never make me feel like dirt

I've told you once, I've told you twice, we go together, like fried beans and rice
'Cause you're a big legged woman, with a short short miniskirt
Promise me darlin, you'll never make me feel like dirt

Ashes to ashes and dust to dust, you mess with my woman, I'm gonna hurt you first
'Cause she's a big-legged woman, with a short short miniskirt
Promise me darlin, you'll never make me feel like dirt

###Freddie King
###See See Baby
See-see baby
See what you have done, Lordy mama
No need to worry
See-see baby
See what you have done
Yes, you've told me a lie
Now you man have come

That man you got, don't love you
Yes, he told me so, Lordy mama
No need to worry
The man don't love you, yes he told me so
He's just only jivin' you, baby
He in love with the girl next do'

Oh, an I love yo teasin'
An' the way you carries on, oh Lordy mama
No need to worry
I love yo teasin'
An the way you carries on
Yes, you told me a lie
Little girl, you know that's wrong.

###Freddie King
###I Love The Woman
I love the woman
And learned a lesson that I can't forget
Yes!
I loved the woman
And learned a lesson that I can't forget
Yes!
She's mean an she's evil
And now my life is in a solid mess

Yeah!

She wakes me in the mo'nin
A-before the break of day
Tellin' me to get up an go out
Now an earn myself some pay

How she scolds me like an orphan
Now and treats me like a clown
Ah and when I need some lovin'
That woman can't be found

I love the woman
And learned a lesson that I can't forget
Yes!
She's mean an she's evil
And now my life is in a solid mess.

###Freddie King
###Christmas Tears
I hear sleigh bells ring
I haven't heard a word from you in years
I hear sleigh bells ringin'
But I haven't heard a word from you in years
I hear choirs singin'
And I'm just sittin' here cryin' Christmas tears


Everybody's singin' "Merry Christmas"
As they watch the starry sky filled with reindeer
Everybody's singin' "Merry Christmas"
As they watch the starry sky filled with reindeer
I'm smilin' on the outside
But on the inside I'm cryin' Christmas tears

You been gone such a long, long time
But it's Christmas and I can't get you off of my mind
Seems like you been gone a hundred years or more
But if you were here with me now
I'd hang "Merry Christmas" on my door

I need ya darling
Kiss and hold me tight
I need ya darling
On a lonely Christmas night
And as I sit and think of the lonely years
I can't help but cry, oh, Christmas tears
Oh, Christmas tears

###Freddie King
###Woman Across The River
Across the river a good woman cried
All because a foolish man had lied
She gave up all she had to show how much she cared
But the man told so many lies, now another man is over there

That woman across the river
Sweet woman across the river, she was mine

Word got around that he had jilted her
And men came running came running from near and far
How could I be such a fool, I'll never, never, never know
That the man, he's got to know, he's a lucky so and so

That woman across the river
I met her one day, about a week ago
She said, "I don't even want to talk to you
'Cause I don't love you any more"

That woman across the river

###Freddie King
###Lowdown In Lodi
Just about a year ago, I set out on the road
Seekin' my fame and fortune, lookin' for a pot of gold
Things got bad, and things got worse, I guess you will
Know the tune
Oh Lord, stuck in Lodi again

Rode in on the Greyhound, I'll be walkin' out if I go
I was just passin' through, must be seven months or more
Ran out of time and money, looks like they took my
Friends
Oh Lord, I'm stuck in Lodi again

The man from the magazine said I was on my way
Somewhere I lost connections, ran out of songs to play
I came into town, a one night stand, looks like my plans
Fell through
Oh Lord, stuck in Lodi again

If I only had a dollar, for every song I've sung
And every time I've had to play while people sat there
Drunk
You know, I'd catch the next train back to where I live
Oh Lord, stuck in Lodi again
Oh Lord, I'm stuck in Lodi again

###Freddie King
###Same Old Blues
Morning rain, keeps on falling
Like the tears that fall from my eyes
As I sit in my room staring out at the gloom
That's the rain in the same, same old blues


I can't help, I can't help but thinking
When the sun, used to shine in my back door
Now the sun, is turned to rain
All my laughter, turned to pain
it's the pain of the same old blues

Sunshine, sunshine is all you see now
But it all, looks like clouds to me
But as I sit in my room staring out at the gloom
It's the rain, it's the same old blues, yeah

Yes, it's the rain, it's the same old blues
Yes, it's the rain, it's the same old blues

###Freddie King
###Goin' Down
'Cause I am goin' down
All the way down
Well hey there, Father, there is just one other thing
I have a simple request
I hear you know God, could you give him a nod in my direction
I would be in your debt
Perhaps there is something that we could work out

I notice your breathing is starting to change
We could go in the back, behind all these shacks
And these bibles and get out of this cage
There was this boy who

Tore my heart in two
I had to lay him
Eight feet underground
And all I need is someone to save me
'Cause I am goin' down

And what I need is someone to save me
'Cause God, I'm goin' down
All the way down
I didn't wanna do it Father
But I caught him with another woman
In the bed I made

And so I put him in a grave
And now there's no one left around
To get me off when I wanted to drag
The next day on the television
They identified him by the circumcision

That I made and now I'm on the run but wait
Why did I have to go and kill him
When he was the best I ever had?
All I need is someone to save me
'Cause I am goin' down
And what I need is something to save me
'Cause God, I'm goin' down
All the way down
I'm going down
All the way down

###Freddie King
###My Feeling For The Blues
I know you heard about the blues
But I would like to give you
My feeling of the blues

So if you just sit down just for a few minutes
And listen to me
I'll give you my feeling of the blues
Because I think I got it

###Albert King
###Born Under A Bad Sign
Born under a bad sign
Been down since I began to crawl
If it wasn't for bad luck, you know I wouldn't have no luck at all

Hard luck and trouble is my only friend
I been on my own ever since I was ten
Born under a bad sign
Been down since I began to crawl
If it wasn't for bad luck, I wouldn't have no luck at all

I can't read, haven't learned how to write
My whole life has been one big fight
Born under a bad sign
I been down since I began to crawl
If it wasn't for bad luck, I said, I wouldn't have no luck at all

That ain't no lie
You know if it wasn't for bad luck I wouldn't have no kind o' luck
If it wasn't for real bad luck, I wouldn't have no luck at all

You know wine and women is all I crave
A big legged woman is gonna carry me to my grave
Born under a bad sign
I been down since I begin to crawl
If it wasn't for bad luck, I wouldn't have no luck at all

Yeah, my bad luck boy
Been havin' bad luck all of my days, yes

###Albert King
###Cross Cut Saw
I'm a cross cut saw, just drag me 'cross your log
I'm a cross cut saw, just drag me across your log
I cut your wood so easy for you, you can't help but say 'Hot dog!'

I've got a double-bladed axe, that really cuts good
I'm a cross cut saw, just bury me in the wood

I'm a cross cut saw, just drag me 'cross your log
I cut your wood so easy for you, you can't help but say 'Hot dog!'

Some call me wood-choppin' Sam
Some call me wood-cuttin' Ben
Last girl I cut the wood for, want me back again

I'm a cross cut saw, just drag me 'cross your log
I cut your wood so easy for you, you can't help but say 'Hot dog!'

###Albert King
###The Very Thought Of You
The very thought of you
And I forget to do
The little ordinary things
That everyone ought to do

I'm living in a kind of daydream
I'm happy as a king
And foolish though it may seem
To me that's everything

The mere idea of you
The longing here for you
You'll never know how slow
The moments go till I'm near to you

I see your face in every flower
Your eyes in stars above
It's just the thought of you
The very thought of you, my love

###Albert King
###I'll Play The Blues For You
If you're down and out and you feel real hurt
Come on over to the place where I live
And all your loneliness I'll try to soothe
I'll play the blues for you

Don't be afraid come on in
You might run across some of your old friends
All your loneliness I gotta soothe
I'll play the blues for you

I got no big name and I ain't no big star
I play the blues for you on my guitar
All your loneliness I'll try to soothe
I 'll play the blues for you

###Albert King
###Don't Throw Your Love On Me So Strong
Hey baby,
Don`t throw your love on me so strong.

Hey baby,
Don`t throw your love on me so strong.

Yeah,
Your love is like a faucet,
You can turn it off and on.
Hey baby,
I like
What you been puttin` down.

Hey baby,
I like
What you been puttin` down.
Oh, but you can search
The whole world over
And no love like yours
Can be found.

Well, someday baby,
Baby when you change your mind.
Well, someday baby,
Baby when you change your mind.
You can search
The whole world over
For me
And I`ll be hard to find.

###Albert King
###Laundromat Blues
You been meetin' your man, baby
Down at the local laundromat
I say, you been meetin' your man, baby
Down at the local laundromat
I've done got wise
An' daddy ain't goin' for that

Early every mornin'
You grab your old blouse or two
Yeah, you get up early in the mornin'
An' you grab your old blouse or two
Oh, you know you're right down to the laundry
While your man is waitin' on you

You better hear my warnin'
I'm gettin' madder everyday
Yeah, you better hear my warnin'
I'm gettin' madder everyday
I don't want you to get so clean, baby
You just might wash your life away

Ya hear?
Well, alright

I know you don't know it, baby
But things look bad for you
The laundry's gonna trap you, darlin'
An' one more, one more dress will do

###Albert King
###Oh, Pretty Woman
Oh pretty woman she's the rising sun
Says all your cheap paint and powder ain't gonna help you none
She's a pretty woman right down to the bone
So you just might as well still leave your skin alone

Pretty woman
What's the matter with you
Can't make you love me, no matter what I do

Oh pretty woman what you trying to do
You kept on foolin' around till I got stuck on you
So you just drop that mess and come down off your throne
Stop using my poor heart as a stepping stone

Pretty woman
What's the matter with you
Can't make you love me, no matter what I do

Oh pretty woman that's all right for you
Now you just go on doing what you want to do
But someday when you thing you've got it made
You get in water deep enough so you can't wade

Pretty woman
What's the matter with you
Can't make you love me, no matter what I do

###Albert King
###Breakin' Up Someones Home
Laying round home alone
On a rainy night like this
Starving for your love
Hungry for just one kiss

Heavy rains up ahead
On my window pane
Beats so loud and clear
Words just spelled your name

I got nowhere to turn to
Tired of being alone
I feel like breaking up
Somebody's home

I know it's useless
Hanging on when
You belong to someone else

Can't control the feeling
Cause after all
I didn't make myself, yeah

Last night, I cried so hard
I believe I caught a chill
Can't control the vibration
My heart just won't stand still

I got nowhere to turn to
Tired of being alone
I feel like breaking up
Somebody's home, yeah, yeah

I know you hear me talking
I'm getting awful lonesome here

I know it's useless
Hanging on when you
Belong to someone else

Can't control the vibration
Cause after all
I didn't make myself

Got nowhere to turn to
Tired of being alone
Feel like breaking up
Somebody's home, yeah

###Albert King
###Cadillac Assembly Line
Goin' to Detroit, Michigan
Girl, I can't take you
Hey, I'm goin' to Detroit, Michigan
Girl, you got to stay here behind

Goin' to get me a job
On the Cadillac assembly line

I'm tired of whoopin' and hollerin'
Up and down the Mississippi road
Hey, I'm tired of whoopin' and hollerin'
Pickin' that nasty cotton

Gonna catch me a bus up North
I won't have to keep sayin' yes, sir, boss

Goin' to Detroit, Michigan
Girl, I can't take you
Hey, I'm goin' to Detroit, Michigan
Girl, you got to stay here behind

Goin' to get me a job
On the Cadillac assembly line

Well, girl, if you'll be alright
And keep your blue jeans zipped up tight
When I make my first check
I'll put you on the Delta jet, hey hey

I'm gonna send for you, darlin'
Won't you come on home

###Albert King
###That's What The Blues Is About
Oh you come home one eve'nin'
To nothin' but the four walls
And then ya find your phone been disconnected
You can't even make no call
Ya hung out for your baby, oh, an'she's not there
You look in the closet, buddy, an'you find it's all bare

Oh, that's what the blues is people
That's what the blues is all about
Well that's a hard pill to have to swallow, um!
When you find what the blues is all about

Now listen to this:

I went out to my backyard
Ya know I whistled for my dog [3 whistle sounds]
He ran up under the house, people
Like he didn't even know me at all
Now I hadn't fed him in two or three days
An' he was lookin' kinda thin
Oh, when your dog turn his back on ya, buddy
You know ya haven't even got a friend

That's the blues, people
That's what the blues is all about
Oh it's a hard pill to swallow, um!
When ya find out what the blues is all about

Oh, look out!
Uh!
Oh no!
I think I got 'em!

I went out to my mail box
I got a bunch-a bills that I can't pay
I guess my wife been out shoppin' again
While I been at work all day

I see the man comin' with his tools
Now is he gonna cut off my water?
You know they got my gas yesterday
An' they comin' right back for the lines tomorrow

Ah, that's what the blues is people
That's what the blues is all about
Well that's a hard pill to swallow, buddy
Oh, when you find out what the blues is all about

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Baby Please Don't Go
Baby, please don't go
Baby, please don't go
Baby, please don't go, down to New Orleans
You know I love you so
Before I be your dog
Before I be your dog
Before I be your dog
I get you way'd out here, and let you walk alone
Turn your lamp down low
Turn your lamp down low
Turn your lamp down low
I beg you all night long, baby, please don't go
You brought me way down here
You brought me way down here
You brought me way down here
'Bout to Rolling Forks, you treat me like a dog
Baby, please don't go
Baby, please don't go
Baby, please don't go, back the New Orleans
I beg you all night long
Before I be your dog
Before I be your dog
Before I be your dog
I get you way'd out here, and let you walk alone
You know your man down gone
You know your man down gone
You know your man down gone
To the country farm
With all the shackles on

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Mojo Hand
I'm goin' to Louisiana and get me a mojo hand
I'm goin' to Louisiana and get me a mojo hand
I'm gonna fix my woman so she can't have no other man

Cold ground was my bed last night, rocks was my pillow too
Cold ground was my bed last night, rocks was my pillow too
I woke up this morning, I'm wondering, what in the world am I gonna do?

I lay down thinking, buy me a mojo hand
I lay down thinking, buy me a mojo hand
I did wanna fix my woman so she can't have no other man

But don't let your woman fix you like mine fixed me
Don't let your woman, boy, fix you like mine fixed me
She make a fool about her, about as a fool can be

Now, can't a woman act funny when she got another man?
Can't a woman act funny when she got another man?
You know, she won't look straight at you
And she's always raisin' sand, sand

Well, I'm going tomorrow but I won't be gone long
I'm going tomorrow but I won't be gone very long
I'm gonna get me a mojo hand, I'm gonna bring it back home

That's what I'm gonna do

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Bring Me My Shotgun
Woah, go bring me my shotgun
Oh I'm gonna start shootin again
Go bring me my shotgun
You know I just got to start shootin' again
You know I'm gonna shoot my woman
Cause she's foolin' around with too many men

Yes bring me my shotgun
Yes man and a pocket full of shells
Yes go bring me my shotgun
Yes man and a pocket full of shells
Yeah you know I'm gonna kill that woman
I'm gonna throw her her in that old deep dug well
Hide her from everybody they won't know where she at

That woman said Lightnin' you can't shoot me
She said now you just dare to try
I don't take a dare from nobody
She said Lightnin' you can't shoot me
She said yes and you dare to try
I said the only reason I don't shoot you little woman
My double barrel shotgun, it just won't fire

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Have You Ever Loved A Woman
Have you ever loved a woman
Man, better than you did yourself
Have you ever loved a woman
Oh, man better than you did yourself
Have you ever tried to give 'em a good home
Same time she act a fool and left
That's what happened to me!

Don't think cause you're pretty baby
Little girl ain't got every man in town
Please don't think cause you're good looking Yeah!
Woman, that you got every man in town
Yeah you know you ain't doin' nothin'
Yeah, but tearin' your reputation down
But that's your business

Have mercy
You know I don't want you
If you little girl don't want poor me
Don't want you
Little girl if you don't want poor me
Better quit your puttin' on and let poor Lightin' know
Go ahead on and let me be
Yeah sure, one more time boy, drop down)

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Black Ghost Blues
Black ghost, black ghost
Please stay away from my door
Black ghost, black ghost
Will you please stay away from my door

Yeah, you know you worry po' Lightnin' so now
I just can't sleep no more

Yeah, you know I go to dreaming first night
Black ghost is all po' Lightnin' can see
I go to dreaming first night,
Black ghost is all po' Lightnin' can see

You know that's why I begin to wonder
Why you keeps on worryin' me

Black ghost is a picture
And the black ghost is a shadow too
Whoa, black ghost is a picture
And the black ghost is a shadow too

You just can see him but you can't hear him talkin'
Ain't nothin' else that a black ghost can do

Black ghost blues

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Jailhouse Blues
Well I wouldn't mind staying in jail, but I've gotta stay there so long
Well I wouldn't mind staying in jail, but I've gotta stay there so long
You know it seem like all my friends, you know they done shook hands and gone
Thirty days in jail, with my back turned to the wall

Thirty days in jail, with my back turned to the wall
Yes you know some other skinner [?] must be kickin' in my stall
Hey mister jailer please, will you please bring me the key
Hey mister jailer, will you please sir bring me the key

I just want you to open the door, cause this ain't no place for me

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###My Starter Won't Start This Mornin'
My starter won't start this mornin'
Boy and my motor won't even turn
My starter won't start this mornin'
Boy and my motor won't even turn
You know I've been runnin' with a fast, trashy womens
Now they'll call my little car to ruin
Yes my starter won't start this mornin'
Somethin' must be wrong with my little machine
You know my starter won't start this mornin'
Somethin' must be wrong with my little machine
Mechanic say "Your car's all right like
You just been burnin' bad gasoline

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Automobile Blues
I seen you drivin' 'round
In your brand new automobile
I see you drivin' 'round
Babe, in your brand new automobile
You're lookin' happy baby with your handsome
Your handsome driver at the wheel

Well, come on, get me
Baby, let's go and have some fun
I just wanna see
Baby, well that new car run
Everything will be alright
Long about the break of dawn
In your brand new automo

Come on, get me
Baby, let's go and have some fun
I just wanna see
Oh, baby, well that new car run
Everything will be alright, be alright
Long about the break of dawn

I seen you drivin' 'round
Babe, in your brand new automobile
I seen you drivin' 'round
Man, in your brand new automobile
You're lookin' happy with your handsome driver
Than in your automobile

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Coffee Blues
This is the 'Coffee Blues', I likes a certain brand
Maxwell's House, it's good till the last drop
Just like it says on the can, I used to have a girl
Cookin' a good Maxwell House, she moved away
Some said to Memphis and some said to Leland

But I found her, I wanted her to cook me
Some good Maxwell's House, you understand?
If I can get me just a spoonful of Maxwell's House
Do me much good as two or three cups this other coffee

I've got to go to Memphis, bring her back to Leland
I wanna see my baby 'bout a lovin' spoonful, my lovin' spoonful
Well, I'm just got to have my lovin', I found her

Good mornin', baby, how you do this mornin'?
Well, please, ma'am, just a lovin' spoon, just a lovin' spoonful
I declare, I got to have my lovin' spoonful
My baby packed her suitcase and she went away
I couldn't let her stay for my lovin', my lovin' spoonful
Well, I'm just got to have my lovin'

Good mornin', baby, how you do this mornin'?
Well, please, ma'am, just a lovin' spoon, just a lovin' spoonful
I declare, I got to have my lovin' spoonful

Well, the preacher in the pulpit, jumpin' up and down
He laid his Bible down for his lovin'
Ain't Maxwell House all right?
Well, I'm just got to have my lovin'

###Lightnin' Hopkins
###Happy Blues For John Glenn
People, I was sittin' this mornin' with this on my mind
Said there ain't no livin' man who gone around the world three times
John Glenn done it, yes he did
He did it, I'm talkin' about him only did it for fun

Half a million dollars made him feel so well
He got to eatin' his lunch and couldn't hardly tell
He said, "I feel all right", John Glenn said it
Everybody was laughin' and dipped in the gritty

It was a million prayer went up, prayin' that he would land
I looked at a school house full of men and they didn't know what to say
But they said, "Let him come back, God, please let him land
You know that's the onliest man ever did it and You're the helpin' hand"
I'm gonna turn out to be one [Incomprehensible]

I see him when he left but I didn't see him when he land
But I know he was doin' all right when they said, "It is okay
To give him a great big hand, he'll be in on the ship, they say he's on deck”
His mother say, “I know my son gonna make it
It ain't never been no mistake”

You know I gonna tell you somethin', this ain't lyin'
You know that man must had on his mind flyin'
It ain't nobody will take that for his tryin' unless they gonna build him
His own self airplane and they gonna go flyin'

They told him, "Don't worry, this is true", you may miss me
For a few minutes but I'll be back to see about you, he did
Yes he did, yes, when he done it
Didn't know [Incomprehensible] helicopter

You know they tested that boy's body, they even test his heart
They know he was all right when he was gettin' to start
I mean he's made it, he went around the world three times
You know he went and got him an airplane
And he made up and had it on his mind

That's what he had on his mind
He didn't have no kid and he didn't have no digs
He just had it on his mind flyin'

###T-Bone Walker
###They Call it Stormy Monday
They call it stormy Monday, but Tuesday's just as bad
They call it stormy Monday, but Tuesday's just as bad
Wednesday's worse, and Thursday's also sad

Yes the eagle flies on Friday, and Saturday I go out to play
Eagle flies on Friday, and Saturday I go out to play
Sunday I go to church, then I kneel down and pray

Lord have mercy, Lord have mercy on me
Lord have mercy, my heart's in misery
Crazy about my baby, yes, send her back to me

###T-Bone Walker
###Mean Old World
This is a mean old world,
Baby to live in by yourself.
This is a mean old world,
Baby to live in by yourself.
Can't get the woman you love,
Cause you know she's lovin someone else.

Well I drink to keep from worryin
Baby and I smile to keep from cryin'.
Yes I drink to keep from worryin
And you know I smile to keep from cryin.
That's to keep the public from knowin
Just what I have on my mind.

###T-Bone Walker
###T-Bone Shuffle
Let your hair down baby
Let's have a natural ball
Let your hair down baby
Let's have a natural ball
Cause when you're not happy
It ain't no fun at all

You can't take it with you
That's one thing for sure
You can't take it with you baby
That's one thing for sure
There's nothing wrong with ya baby
That a good T-Bone shuffle can't cure

Have fun while ya can
Fate's an awful thing
Have fun while ya can
Fate's an awful thing
You can't tell what might happen
That's why I love to sing

###T-Bone Walker
###Bobby Sox Blues
Bobby Sox, baby, I've got to let you go
Bobby Sox, baby, I've got to let you go
You've got a head full of nothin'
But stage, screen and radio

You chase autographs every night
You write fan mail through the day
You keep your great big head in the scrapbook
Yes, and you throw the cookbook away

Bobby Sox, baby, I've got to let you go
You've got a head full of nothin'
But stage, screen and radio

Now you treat me like a stranger
You don't have a word to say
I ask you if you love me
You say, "What would Frankie say?"

Yes, Bobby Sox, baby, I've got to let you go
You've got a head full of nothin'
But stage, screen and radio

###T-Bone Walker
###Alimony Blues
It's a cold-blooded world
When a man has to pawn his shoes
It's a cold-blooded world
When a man has to pawn his shoes
That's the fix I'm in today
I swear I've been abused
Yes, the woman is a devil
She will trick you if she can
Yes, the woman is a devil
She will trick you if she can
She will tell you that she love you
An work out some other plan
Got those alimony blues
An I sure got to pay some dues
Got those alimony blues
An I sure got to pay some dues
And if I run short of cash
It's the road camp, I've got to choose.

###T-Bone Walker
###I Want A Little Girl
I want a little girl, call my own.
She must be someone who's all alone now.
Say, I want a little girl 
To fall in love with me, oh yeah.

I want a little girl, but she may not look
Just like a picture in a story book.
If she can cook chicken, yeah, 
She'll suit me to a T.

And she don't have to wave her hair
Or even wear fancy clothes, 
I wouldn't even care.
She don't wear nylon hose, oh no.

I want a little girl 
To love a lot.
You know that I'd give 
Her everything I got.
I want a little girl 
To fall in love with me.

###T-Bone Walker
###Love Is Just A Gamble
Love is Just a gamble.
Say just what you wanna say.
Love is Just a gamble.
Say just what you wanna say.
Its nice to see if your a winner,
If you lose its debt that's hard to pay.

Can't you see love is a gamble.
It makes headlines in the news.
Can't you see love is a gamble.
It makes headlines in the news.
I've always been unlucky,
All I ever did in life was lose.

Whoa took a gamble on romance.
Just when I thought I had it won.
Took a gamble on romance.
Just when I thought I had it won.
She told me goodbye pretty papa,
I was only havin fun.

###T-Bone Walker
###The Hustle Is On
Times is hard, baby and the hustle is really on
Times is hard, baby, the hustle is really on
Prices are high now darlin', and all the good jobs are gone

Sorry to say, baby, things ain't what they used to be
Sorry to say, baby, things ain't what they used to be
Better get yourself a job now, baby, I'm tired of you worrying me

Well, you made a lot of money, baby, but you never saved a dime
Yes, you made a lot of money, baby, but you never saved a dime
If you save yours now, mama, that ain't no fault of mine

Times is hard baby and the hustle is really on
Times is hard baby, the hustle is really on
Prices are high now darlin', and all the good jobs are gone

###T-Bone Walker
###West Side Baby

I've got a west side baby
She lives way across town

I've got a west side baby
She lives way across town
And when I'm with my baby
I don't want a soul around

Now she's kind of tall and legged
She's always dressed swell
She sets my soul on fire
When she rang my front door bell

I've got a west side baby
She lives way across town
And when I'm with my baby
I don't want a soul around

Now Monday morning early
Someone bang upon my door
I knew it wasn't my baby
'Cuz she's never knocked before

So I lay in bed and wondered
Wno could the caller be
I thought it was insurance man
'Cuz he's been hurting for me

Crazy about my west side baby
She lives way across town
And when I'm with my baby
I don't want a soul around

###T-Bone Walker
###Glamour Girl
Glamour girl, glamour girl.
I'm cutting out on you
You just a play type of baby.
And I ain't got no use for you.

Seven days you play the races.
Seven nights you stay out late.
Your always caught in funny places.
Every guy you think is great.

Glamour girl, glamour girl
I find you'll never do.
You just a play type of baby.
And I ain't got no use for you.

Twelve o clock is rising hour.
You think that's a crime.
You better find a better place for charlie
Cause I'm through feeding ya mine.

Glamour girl, glamour girl
I find you'll never do.
You just a play type of baby.
And I ain't got no use for you.

Now the fastest train that's leavin
Is much to slow for me.
Now the fastest train that's leavin
Is much to slow for me.
When all these years I tried to believe you,
That was just a foolin me.