###Autopsy
###Gasping for Air

Tightening grip around the neck
Gasping for air that isn't there
Feeling life's source draining away
Slowly slipping to God you pray

Eyes popping out, as the face turns blue
Crushed windpipe, swallowing in blood
Hopeless thoughts, loss of breath
Loss of life, strangled to death

Digging the grave in which you will lie
Buried head deep and left to die
Body paralyzed beneath the sand
Tide comes in asphyxiation

Watrlogged corpse, Back from the dead
Rips the eyeballs from his head
Snapping neck, blood pours down
Decapitated body rotting away

Gasping for air
Gasping for air

###Autopsy
###Ridden with Disease

Stricken with a horrible disease
Mankind falls victim to doom
Festering plague spreads across the earth
Rotting death, morbid curse

Skin begins to rot
Deaden and peel away
Bones collapse
From advanced decay
Slow and painful death
No more blood to bleed
No end to the cadavers
Ridden with disease

Faces decomposing
Screaming in pain and despair
Becoming one with the earth
Flesh deteriorates until bones are bare

Skin begins to rot
Deaden and peel away
Bones collapse
From advanced decay
Slow and painful death
No more blood to bleed
No end to the cadavers
Ridden with disease

###Autopsy
###Slaughterday

Darkened day
Torturous ways
Live only to die
Slaughterday

Cast into flames
Stoned to death
Law of the lords
Uncontrollable hoard

Headless bodies on the ground
War machine leaves no life behind
Blood soaks deep into the earth
Sadistic race
Rip out your heart

Strung up
Cannibals eat your flesh
Cooked
Survival of the fittest

Peel your flesh from the bone
Souless body left alone

###Autopsy
###Hole in the Head

Repulsive parasites feeding on your mind
Shrieking demons
Within your skull they fly
See the colors so bright and brilliant
The hunger starts
It's brain matter you want

Voices so twisted command you
Don't try to resist it
Give in to the belief
That bliss is within reach
So destroy the wicked in your eyes
And feast

Fuel the creatures in your head
The answer is in the slaughtered dead

State of mind unbalancing
Distorted sick reality
Must achieve immortality

It's god again
He speaks
About the tasks you must complete
Tripping hard
Your brain is shorted out
You must believe
Cranial chaos
Blurs of violence
Keep the cravings fed
Are they coming in or out
This hole inside your head

###Autopsy
###Skullptures

Creative juices flowing
And it's graveyard raiding time again
Engulfed by darkness
Digging for my art
Which is my only friend
Stuffing in potato sacks
The ones that suit my special need
Burial was but in vain
They still come back with me
Hacksawing away at rigor mortified cadavers
Set aside the right limbs
To consruct my latest skullpture
Maggots into flies
They buzz before my eyes, breed in my hair
I turn my corpses into art
It is my life, nothing compares

The smell gets my mind in gear
Helps me decide which parts go where
Forearm sewed with stitches thick
Onto someone's sliced off dick
Woman's face removed with care
Still attached to scalp and hair
put it on my face and stare
And think of what comes next

Kneecap pried off with screwdriver nailed to foot
Decorated with toenails
Now I look at the pair of breasts I've severed
On my tray
Sew the two together
Flesh is brittle and grey

Another masterpiece is now complete
A mass of arms and legs and hands and feet
Stomach draped about drained of their bile
Skull atop the rotten sting pile

###Autopsy
###Tortured moans of agony

Tortured moans of agony
I love to hear your feeble cries
Begging to be put to death
Extremely slow and cruel demise
Teeth pulled slowly one by one
Mangled jaws, Bloody gums
My love grows each time you bleed
The mutilation has just begun
Eyeballs sliced along the lids
Fluids running down your face
Try to scream through shredded lips
Your severed tongue I now shall taste
Slash your bowels and rip your throat
Tear your stomach open wide
Fuck the gash I cum for you
Semen blends with blood inside

###Autopsy
###Deliver me from sanity

Haunted by reality
I cannot bear the pain
Called by unearthly screaming
Sickened by the sane

Deliver me from sanity
My eyes have seen to much
The very skin around my bones
Is horrid to the touch

A tortured specimen of filth
I grovel on the floor
Something's wrong inside my head
I'm not insane but I might be dead

Deliver me from sanity
My eyes have seen to much
The very skin around my bones
Is horrid to the touch

I see reflections on the wall
But there's no mirror there
This place is dark and sick and cold
Why can't my mind be spared

I dig the eyes out of my skull
My mind is tearing at the seams
Self inflicted lunacy
At last fills all my waking dreams

###Autopsy
###Bridge of Bones

I didn't find this place, it called to me
A reeking from the other side of stone
Underground in hiding as I was
Was that a whisper? But I'm here alone

There lay a hole in the ground
A hidden portal in the floor
A putrid breeze was seeping out
Against all sense I set out to explore

Through the passage I did climb
Down to a chamber vast as hell itself
Had I lost my mind or did I really see
An abysmal chasm with a bridge of bones
Before me?

A nauseating reddish light filled the gloom
Transfixed I walked up to the bridge bizarre
Horrified I realized the truth
The skulls and legs and arms looked so familiar

In shock I scrambled back up
To the bleakness of the moor
The winds were foul, the bones were gone
I reeled in sickening horror
The abomination of a bridge
Must be the morbid key
I had to go down again and face insanity

A dark descent beneath the earth
And hell was waiting there
I stepped onto the skeletal span
And walked across in terror
I reached the other side
To see a coffin standing bare
And then the voices faded in
Grotesque beyond compare

The box was open, death was near
I heard the casket's calling clear
My victims screaming in my head
I stepped inside and closed the lid

###Autopsy
###Feast of the Graveworm

Midnight violence, the scene of the kill
A life slain to rest where the blood has been spilled
Discarded cadaver, no heartbeat is left
Teeming with maggots that feed on the flesh

The street is the graveyard, the dumpster the tomb
Forgotten and rotten beneath a red moon

A life once strong is worm food now
Conniving wretch has been cut down

Neck twisted sickly, eyes stare into space
A squirming mass erodes limbs and face
Feeding and eating, nauseating display
No coffin, no funeral, just life stripped away

A portrait of putrefaction, life beyond the grave
A coward soiled and bloated with maggots in his face

Discarded cadaver, no heartbeat is left
Teeming with maggots that feed on the flesh
The street is the graveyard, the dumpster the tomb
Forgotten and rotten beneath a red moon

###Autopsy
###Keeper of Decay

Roadkill, guts are spilled
A flattened form of death
A heavenly delight
Death is sweet
Scoop up the meat
Intact or mashed-it matters not

I bring home my new surprises
Open my door, the odour rises
One that makes me feel so good
I feel so fucking high

I smile at my pride and joy on my walls
My pets
Nailed up high and low
By the throat
Intestinal wreath
Rancid beef

My newest tacked up with the rest
I sit back and watch it rot
Breathe deep
Close my eyes
Fantasize that i am one of them

###Vader
###The Wrath

Temple of hate a place accursed by the Gods
the walls all in blood of tormented to death
putrid face of Demon gutting sacrifice in light of full moon
come in! eternal flame will brand your soul

Demon's eye in blood red sky
you will suffer, you have to die
prophecy of certain death
no escape - you're a victim of the unholy wrath

Screams from depths of mind
cry of mutilated souls
tyrant drops from scratched wounds of God

Virus of hatred invades the brains of tyrants
throwing into fire they create the endless violence
priests of war, creatures of the crime
merciless dictators, the lords of human fright

Bloody judgement
endless judgement
slowly agony will be your atonement
living in fear - dying in pain
no escape - you are the sacrifice

###Vader
###Black Sabbath

What is this that stands before me?
Figure in black which points at me
Turn around quick, and start to run
Find out I'm the chosen one
Oh nooooo!

Big black shape with eyes of fire
Telling people their desire
Satan's sitting there, he's smiling
Watches those flames get higher and higher
Oh no, no, please help me!

Is it the end my friend?
Satan's coming 'round the bend
People running 'cause they're scared
The people better go and beware!
No, no, please no!

###Vader
###The Crucified Ones

Mortal crosses standing in the row,
Seem to reach up to the burning sky,
Damned souls grouping on the dark,
Going round the stretched arms.
Bodies, faces,
Unnaturally bended in pain,
Lifeless eyes staring at the space,
Persecution of the dying has begun.
Here's the place of alteration,
Where life turns into other form,
Dark ritual of demons procreation,
Hear the cries - of the crucified ones.
Throbbing fleshes in the rhythm of thunder,
Blasphemy in light of raving bolts,
Nailed hands greeting angry gods,
Coming fourth to feast in blood.
Bodies, faces,
Unnaturally changed in lust,
Purple fluids streams on the wood,
Like tears of dying cross
Here's the place of the alteration,
Where gods turn into temporal form,
Dark ritual of demons procreation,
Come on! Leave your life and join the dead in hell.
Masters of forgotten arts,
Deign to look at your servant,
Acceptance my greatest sacrifice,
Send revenge on bastard's seed!
O come to me!
I beg thee, open wide the gates,
All fiends of fiends,
From the deep sleep of dark abyss arrive!
Pazuzu, the evil one,
Lord, who feeds on angels cries!
Bless the damned, curse the blessed, crucify them.

###Vader
###Final Massacre

Warriors with hate inflict destruction,
Comes true the awful prediction,
Still alive corpses lie in the street,
Spitting the blood to the God,
Dying in flames dammed mob,
Screaming with pain: This can't be, oh God",
Maybe they will understand he was never,
But will be too late, so die forever.
Circling in the sky the demons now descend,
To raise their slaughter of mankind till its end,
The final massacre of people on the earth,
Pain cracks their minds, everywhere is Death.
False Gods in their temples tremble with fear,
They know the death is now so near,
Unearthly Armageddon burns with flames of doom,
Poisoned seed flung into virgin's womb.
Circling in the sky the demons now descend,
To raise their slaughter of mankind till its end,
The final massacre of people on the earth,
Pain cracks their minds, everywhere is Death.
Merciless angels fly over head,
It's no time for your imploring pleads,
Commit suicide with horror in your eyes,
Bleeding with scars, pride world now dies.
Warriors with hate inflict destruction,
Comes true the awful prediction,
Still alive corpses lie in the street,
Spitting the blood to the God,
Dying in flames dammed mob,
Screaming with pain: This can't be, oh God",
Maybe they will understand he was never,
But will be too late, so die forever.
Different Armageddon came true under our eyes,
Dust comes down when the time came for sunrise,
The final massacre, winds destroy the earth,
Impaled heads notify, that winner is the Death.

###Vader
###Carnal

I tasted the fever of Your existence
seems like cold grain to my mouth
I stand aside, I stay away
transmuting my quicksilver blood

that I may see
that I may touch
insipid are the describing words
the self needs no vulgar praise

This worship has no supplications
my rite is to live and do
things naked, pure, of honest lust
the throbbing vortex feeds on it all

Sleep is the best of possible prayers
the winged eyes are blessed to see
downtrodden deception of every torment
transpierced hymens my lust adores

Many images yet one raw flesh
animal steps I love to tread
an ideal point where Time is Space
memory giant sores this journey must heal

Lady of Mourning and her monsters
lay down the scythes for here I come
joyful and priapic my baby soul
a new-born one, ten million years old

###Vader
###Foetus God

Foetus god descends in silence
a bastard deity for us to believe
blasphemy of gen collage
in backward sombre involution

Foetus god abortion of the Diine
latent rape of wet, lewd womb
man-made myth to blunt in mind
the vilest offence of five senses

Undone miracles never to come
invalid rise of slave thought
the only light its dawn can shed
is from burnt wisdom and shimmering greed

Thine is not the Kingdom
no trace of strength I see
no Mercy to expect
a seed of claws upon your lips

As pure wit turns into effusions
we, snakes of Truth, ex and devour
gods manifested in twisted images
astrally hunted in shadow and soul

Sweet holy shiftless godsend meat
I bet you listen to this psalm of me

Sweet holy shiftless godsend meat
I bet you listen to this psalm of me
little by little, one by one
the thorns become the real crown

Thine is not the Kingdom
no trace of strength I see
no Mercy to expect
a seed of claws upon your lips

###Vader
###Xeper

A scarab beetle which toils through its phases
From an egg through a larva to the protector of the dawning Sun
Out of the Unmanifest into the Matrix of Manifestation
One word which opens the gates to the worlds

Knowledge-not information-grants transformative power
There are as many left hand paths as there are us-stars
The extension of existence to a further level of Being
By powers of the Set that releases from thrall

I have come into being
I have come into being

Meaning can only come from the individual
In the moments of divine clairvoyance and intensification of Being
The utterance of the word which ripples through the fabric of the world
And gives insight and strength to those who want to become

I have come into being
I have come into being

A scarab beetle which toils through its phases
From an egg through a larva to the protector of the dawning Sun
Out of the Unmanifest into the Matrix of Manifestation
One word which opens the gates to realities

I have come into being

###Vader
###Litany

Hateful as it may be percieved, 
"Litany" can be different things for different people.
Choose your own enemy and conquer your hatred. 
Love is the Law, Love under Will.

Fury, hatred, bondage, pain
Anger, blindness, boredom, strain
Slavery, loathing, frenzy, tension
Phobias, fierceness, madness, grudge
Distress, pressure, burden, acid
Disgust, rage, malice, spite
Grossness, rancor, venom, grief
Panic, terror, violence, death

This is what you mean to me

Murder, shash, burn, destroy
Tear, erase, slaughter, scar
Drown, garrote, strangle, slay
Hang, bury, torture, finish
Deafen, blister, mire, flay
Repel, poison, corrupt, damn
Sacrifice, wipe, ravage, singe
Crush, forget, harm, impale

This is what I'll do to you

Cruel, false, mindless, plain
Evil, brutish, perverse, sly
Forceful, stupid, shallow, mute
Cowardly, jealous, gloomy, rank
Tainted, cheap, thoughtless, sick
Vindictive, savage, rotten, gross
Dreadful, useless, envious, dumb
Sleazy, lowly, mocking, sham

This is what you'll always be

###Vader
###The Nomad

Another land, another sea
The road that never ceases
To lie ahead and beckon still
Though legs and feet are weary

Another woman, another man
The lust that never ceases
To fill the greed for pain and revel
Though body yield for fatigue

Another me, yet still the same
Another me, yet you will know me
Another me, yet I have never left
Another me to find the way back home

Another grail, another god
The quest that never ceases
To quench the yearning for the Aleph
Though mind and soul are tired

Another life, another death
The circle that never breaks
To stop this journey set for me
By no-one but myself

###Vader
###The Sea came in at last

A massive blue calendar
Charting the age of apocalypse
The occupant marks the nodes
Maps the lines of terror

Across the city that keeps shifting
Spectral bicycles speed and ride
The fog devours and spits
New geography of the mind

Prostitution in memories
Secret desires without redemption
The past implodes on itself
The return to the womb begins

The sea came in at last
To claim all that is hers
The sea came in at last
To flood all sorrow and pain

###Carcass
###Fermenting Innards

Your pulverized torso languishes in its pool of pus
Minced, cancerous viscera - gore seeps from the guts
My fetid fetish is to excavate the moulding rot
I drool my gastric juices as I chomp on you blood-clots

Fermenting innards, bubbling with rot
Alcoholic pus, dissolves the wooden box

I gouge into the chest's cavity to rip out the intestines
Slivering soft entrails to release the foaming secretions
I suck up the concoction and eat the decay
With cankered disgorgement I excrete my gurgling prey

Bile, chyme and blood in the offal effervesce
I eviscerate the bowels and drink the clotted cess

###Carcass
###Feast on dismembered carnage

Bodies dismembered, corpses desecrated
Carcasses liquidized and minced with hatred
Brains are splattered, strewn limbs and heads
Blood has been spurted as the arteries were shredded

Eyes have been impaled, flayed skin in strips
Intestines and guts from the body have been ripped
Stench of sweet blood, bones have been crunched
Festering gore is eaten for lunch

Parasitic carnivorous carrion, your gastrointestinal tract, 
your prey's cremator
Bloody neo-cannibalistic, bloodfeed masticator
Rigor sanguined fleshfeast, gourging on festered entrails and warm meat
Devouring cold offal, necro-sentient mortis feed

Mutilated organs, the meat-cleaver is raised
Falls to mash the head and rip up the face
Throats slit with vengeance, flesh stripped to the bone
Your death is terrible, painful and slow

Drooling palate
Terrible odorous mess
The repulsive stench
Of roasting flesh

Sterile carnage, dried sanguined personae desecration
Scooping out the entrails, violent entrail emancipation
The taste of violent gorge hot on your breath
Digesting the succulent corpse in your succous death

###Carcass
###Heartwork

Works of art, painted black
Magniloquent, bleeding dark
Monotonous palate, murky spectrum, grimly unlimited
Food for thought, so prolific
In contrasting shades, forcely fed
Abstraction, so choking, so provocative

A canvas to paint, to degenerate
Dark reflections - degeneration
A canvas to paint, to denigrate
Dark reflections, of dark foul light

Profound, aesthetic beauty
Or shaded, sensary corruption
Perceptions, shattered, splintered, mirroring
In deft taints, diluted, tinted
Spelt out, in impaired colour
Denigrating, going to paints to pain - not a pretty picture

Works of heart bleeding dark
Black, magniloquent art
Monotonous palate, murky spectrum, grimly unlimited
Prolific food for thought
Contrasting, fed with force
Abstraction, so choking, so provocative

Bleeding works of art
Seething work so dark
Seering words from the heart

###Carcass
###Embodiment

I bow down your precious icon, deity of self suppression
This effigy of flesh, corporeal christi, nailed
In submission to this false idol, seeking deliverance
From this spiritual hierarchy, downward spiralling, a corrupt throne
Of repression and guilt

Our will be done
Thy kingdom burn

On my knees, before this tormented flesh, in irreverence
In communion with this parasitic host of virtuous divinity
This imperious creed bears testament to the failures of our morality
Righteous durance is our cross we bear in stations
In stations of the lost

Our will be done
Thy kingdom burn - thy kingdom burn
Our will be done

From your knees arise
By your own hand, your god you scribe
The earth shall inherit the meek
Your god is dead

Bound down, in God we're trussed, foul stature
Icons embodied in flesh, we nail
In servitude to deities fashioned in our self image
Shadows of eternal strife cast by those who serve
Serve a crown of pawns

###Carcass
###Ever Increasing Circles

Round and round we go,
Like a merry-go-round out of control
The same old tune, same old song
Again, again, and again

Round and round we go,
When will it stop, nobody knows
The same old chords, the same old words
It all sounds familiar, all starts to sound the same

Turn on, tune in, drop out,
Out of tune, dropped in, turned off
Who calls the tune?

Round and round we go,
Ever get the feeling you've heard this before?
Same old melody, rejuvenated,
Recycled again and again

Round and round, we go,
Never able to stem the flow
Same old notes, going round in cycles
Over and over again, and over again...

Turn on, tune in, drop out,
Out of tune, dropped in, turned off
Who calls the tune?

Who plays the fool?
As the circles ever increase

Round and round we go,
Like a merry-go-round out of control
The same old tune, the same old song,
Again, again, and again

Round and round we go,
Ever get the feeling you've heard this before?
Same old melody, rejuvenated,
Recycled again and again, again and again...

Turn on, tune in, drop out,
Out of tune, dropped in, turned off

Turn on, tune in, drop out,
Out of tune, dropped in, turned off
Who calls the tune?
Who plays the fool?

Who calls the tune?
As the circles ever increase

###Carcass
###Tools of the trade

Steel skin clips,
Forceps, grooved awl, retractors, needles
Gouges and saws,
Intestinal clamps, blunt dissectors,
Scalpels, pins, toothed directors.

Tools of the trade, forceps and blades
Skillfully lathed, for us to maim.

Bone levers, spikes, malleable scoops,
Plates and chisels, screws and spoons,
Drills, respatories, files and durettes,
Guillotines, gags and compression forceps.

Tools of the trade, ripping the rib-cage,
To remissly lustrate, so pleased to maim.

Retractors, mallets, rugines and benders,
Chisels, rods, sharps and catheters,
Trephines, undines, irons and styrups,
Depressors, tongues, sterile catgut.

Tools of the trade, stainless steel blades,
Painstakingly lathed, we're so pleased to maim.

###Carcass
###Pyosisified

The lingering scirrhus begins to harden
As the insides fall prey to putrefaction
Rotting tissue turns to mush and pulp
As your mind is torn by encephalitis

Your cavities rot with ulcers
Your infected inflammations torn
Your gizzards eaten by incursive decay
You're infernally rotten to the gore...

Juices digested from each pus-swollen pore
Insatiable hunger as I feast on the gore
Nothing gives me greater pleasure
Than a bowlful of chyme
Maggot infested kidneys
Are what I choose every time

The smell of plaguing infection
Is nauseatingly emetic
Prolonged spumescence of stale pus
Stinks like hot, purtid vomit

Your body is indurate
The insides are black as tar
Your innards gnawed by septic hate
Now a mass of empyaema

Your blood is caked
Dried and inconsistent
Your bloody rotten gore
Is now vitrescent

###Carcass
###Emotional Flatline

An emotional void, a cold empty shell
Embittered husk, a heart of darkness
Trace weak pulse, vascular eclipse
Numbed and sapped, emotional paralysis

Flatline, grievious bodily heart
Flatlined, sensitivity bypassed

No tears to cry
Stone cold emotional flatline

Emotional flatline
No tears to cry

With indifference touched of emotion drained
Cold bloody minded, caressing disdain
Pulsating life, only rhythmic dead beats
Terminal cardiac ridden with disease

Flatline, no tears to cry
The hard line, stone cold emotionless flatline

No time to cry
Stone cold emotional flatline

Emotional flatline
No time to cry
No tears to cry

###Carcass
###The master butcher's apron

The sun never sets
The blood never dries
The selfless sacrifice
Of the butchers maligned
The sun never sets
The blood never dries
Lest we forget

The sun never sets
Teardrops never dry
This deathless bloodshed
Of the whetted knives
For your sons you never wept
The fruitless sacrifice
Of the master butchers

Never trusted in the dark
Pecuniary villeinage
A decaying realm to rapine and plunder

Like maggots colonizing
Contagious disease contaminating
Expansionist plague to pillage & conquer

The union of cruciate & saltire
The callous cruciate & saltire
To beneficiate the graveyard of empire

In the name of his tyrannical majesty
To serve the imperialist tragedy
A cruel serving sovereignty
A subjugating murderous monarchy

Recollections of the past, revised, laundered, tainted & poisoned
But I'll raise a toast to the memory of those who served in the
West African squadron
Merciful overlords

In the name of diabolical oligarchy
In the kingdom of demise rules supremacy
Solipsistic crowned nobility
Stern reigning gunboat diplomacy

Recollections of the past, revised, condemn, taint & poison
But I'll raise my glass to the memory of the wretches who
Served in the preventative squadron

I salute
Those who tugged at the master butcher's apron strings

The sun never sets
The blood never dried
The fruitless sacrifice
Of the butchers benign
The sun it never sets
The blood never dries
Lest we forget
That the master butchers still whet their knives

###Carcass
###Unfit for Human Consumption

Seductive lymphandetitis
Delectable septic metritis
Tempting glanders jaundice
For human consumption unfit

Paltable melanosis
Aromatic mastitis
Saporous brucellosis
Cry havoc and let slip

Salivating
At the leash straining
The cadaver dogs
Devouring

Appetising
Diseased gastric dining
The cadaver dogs
In cold blood

Indulging in sarcocysts
Epicurean pericarditis
Cariosus tender and lean
After all you are what you eat

Unfit for human consumption
An appetite for bovine destruction
A manifesto for mutilation
Manifests in your own dereliction

The dogs of cruror released
On severed carnage feed
Cadaver dogs rapidly bay and seethe
Canine, ulunating, feverishly inhaling
the scent of human debris

Indulgent lymphandetitis
Aromatic mastitis
Corrosive carcase rotten and obscene
After all you are what you eat

###Gorguts
###Inflicted Maturity

A process of infliction
That make humans older mentally
Annoys cerebral evolution
But leaves the body like it used to be

Physically being like a baby
Who can not stand alone upright
But mentally already adult
To compute without trouble

This premature evolution
Is fastly and easy accomplished
By a painless stupid injection
Of a liquid in the nape
When the intellectual dudation
Has reached a too high level
Intelligence turns to insanity
Institutionalized, poor little baby

This process of infliction
That makes human older mentally
Upsets your mental situation
And brought you to perpetual insanity

###Gorguts
###Metempsukhosis

Every body wants to see
The other sides of misery
The best example they could get
Is when they take their last breath

There's a world, we had all wished to see
Far away in infinities
It's miraculous, you have been told
But for now you can't behold

Tell me why, why do we die?
You will answer me, because!
Anyways, I don't mind
We will never know the cause

Reincarnation is the most obscure thing
That we can't be sure
We shall all come back to accomplish
All the things we missed in the past

Metempsukhosis
Migrate souls
From one body to another
And gives them birth
In a new mother

###Gorguts
###Considered Dead

Back in the fourteenth century
When the world was plagued by horrid diseases
Discovered lifeless bodies were buried

Knowing very little about true symptoms of death
Those who stiffen in the stage of morbidity
Were then considered dead

Autopsies were unknown at that time
Unconsciousness could have been fatal to your life
Catalepsy, from this plague a lot have died
Ignorance sent to the grave people alive

There's no way to save yourself from this calamity
Life will be for you a simple memory

Faint! Now you're paralysed
Catalepsy soon will take your life
Try not to close your eyes
Cause death will be to life a deadly lie

When you're entombed Within your mind you wait and
pray if you could talk The only things that you would say
"I'm still alive, Please! I'm still alive, Don't bury me!"

What a sad way to end a mortal life
But it's better off buried
Than to be embalmed alive

###Gorguts
###Rottenatomy

I've been lost in a jungle
For an hour and fifteen days
Hopelessly searching for exits
In this lethal maze

Footsteps I have taken
Each one driving me insane
Always turning in circles
In this hostile jungle

Having dropped my last piece of food
The most vital thing I never wished to loose
I slipped and found myself in a dark place like hell
At the bottom of a pit where I had fell

Surrounded by a rancid smell
Of corpses that previously fell
Among bones shredded flesh and crawling maggots
Then I knew that I shall stay there to rot

Gashes appearing everywhere
Scars I'm wishing in despair
Before maggots devoured my insides
I'll commit myself to suicide

Above me I heard people talking
Having lost my voice, I was unable to scream
They had a look and saw me lying in my knees
Then went away thinking I was deceased

Below me no one is talking
If you have your voice, just once you're screaming
Have a fast look before falling on your knees
No hope is left when you are deceased

###Gorguts
###The Erosion of Sanity

Man's sanity has not provided
For an imminent derangement
Life won't be able to handle
The psychological sickness

Encephalitis' treatments are unknown
In a perpetual sleep, they're swallowed

A decrease in all capacities
Mentally you're becoming obsolete
Infection in your brain, it creates
A slumber that no one can awake

Nailed in your chair, you're living dismally

Sudden rise of lucidity
Your wretched life is complete
As before, now you can see
Walk and talk normally

How long will i be
Saved from my disease?

Unexpected relapse into sickness
Brought you back to an everlasting sleep

Back in your chair, you're living dismally

###Gorguts
###Orphans of sickness

In the tombs of pain and innocence
Forever were buried
Souls of those who've never asked to be
Scornfully immolated

The art of transplantation
Has saved a lot of lives
By frauding a child's adoption
I will be saving mine

In the name of science
They've claimed being our saviors
Money is what keeps busy
These medical butchers
Soiled with blood all over their hands
They've just killed for a couple of grand

Orphans of sickness were put to rest
Miserable adoption has torn their souls to shreds
Orphans of sickness now dwell in death
With nice tags on their organs, their existence will end

Children were dissected
By those sick, demented

In the tombs of pain and innocence
Forever were buried
Souls of those who've never asked to be
Scornfully immolated

To achieve my transplantation
I stole a lot of lives
Through the kindness of adoption
All those lives are now mine

Orphans of sickness were put to rest
Miserable adoption has torn their souls to shreds
Orphans of sickness now dwell in death
With nice tags on their organs, their existence will end

###Gorguts
###Nostalgia

Latest being drowned
In fictive degradation
Coming depression revolved
Around an Earth
Nostalgia excludes the whole

As spleen takes over me
Resound, the echoes of my threnodies
And then the fact of being
Has no longer meaning
The hymns of light
They'll sing once I'll be gone

Reverie appears cause
Existence collapse

Nostalgia
Sadness shall obnubilate

Sadness, feels, the desolated

Desperately lost within
Lament, pain and misery
The more lies burden lives,
The more I am dying
The realm of light
I'll reach once I'll

Latest feeling drowned
In lucid contradiction
Coming relation revolved
Around a heart
Nostalgia excludes the whole

Reverie appears cause
Existence collapse

Nostalgia
Sadness shall obnubilate

###Gorguts
###Clouded

Sad version of abject life
Enlighment feeds my decay
Sombre proper to ecstasy
Bring this dark day of frenzy

Shame while I fly high
Incite tears to my eyes
Hopeless mind, Pain Life creates
Above the skies of sorrow, I'm

Crawling, Crawling on the darkened shore
Seas of despair saturate my soul
Rising, Rising from this clouded land
Life of despair shall forsake my soul

Hopeless mind, Pain life creates
Above the skies of sorrow, I elevate
Shame while I fly high
Incite tears to my eyes

Fading, Fading from the mortal ground
Sad version of grievous soul 

Shame while I fly high
Incite teras to my eyes
Hopeless mind, Pain it creates
Above the skies of sorrow, I elevate

###Gorguts
###Colored Sands

Onward to reach the wheel of time
A path of solitude
Embraced humbly
Hands, face and knees against the ground

Prostrations for existence to come
Winds of perpetuity
Through sails of vacuity
Shores of enlightenment
Are wished and found

Sand Mandala
of the enlightened mind
Sand Mandala
Pure wisdom, one, shall find

Kalachakra
Disclosing mystic hands
Kalachakra
Splendors of colored sands

Soon of this work art shall be
In the hands of ephemerality

Dismantled, will be
The wheel of time
Quiet intensity
The sands are poured at sea
Waves of enlightenment
Are blessed and found

###Gorguts
###Enemies of Compassion

Clouds of fear
Roved the sky as the enemies
Chased the sun away from their land
Blacked, got, the snow
As the footsteps by enemies
Chased the peace away
From their land

Hope and light,
The Snow Lion brings
Through wisdom
Hate and lies,
Dragon infuses into freedom

The land of snow
Being invaded by enemies
Shrines and beauties dressed up in ruins
One can't believe
Any words said by enemies
Cultural invasion begins

Suspicious walls
Prison of glass
Freedom is now stuck
Behind the bars of past

Curse...uprising curse
Enemies of compassions
Despotic thirst

Waves of hate...undertowed
Tragic fate...sinking
Waves of hate...undertowed
Mourning braves...drowning

###Bolt Thrower
###Concessions of pain

No justice found
Beneath the blackened clouds of war
Attack in the darkness
No peace before the dawn

Killer instinct, sadistic tendency
Aggression breeding hatred, kill all enemies
Powersurge eliminates remorse for mankind
Hopelessness, domination freezes in the mind

Dormant hatre lies in state
Hands of death await your fate
Concession of pain, taste for power
Life awaits its final hour

Locked in conscience, strange mess of thoughts
Privilege of pain, gained the power sought

Mass enforcement, total control
Captives of command, fallen to our hold
Dark torment of the fear inside
Domination takes away your pride

Dormant hatred lies in state
Hands of death await your fate
Concession of pain, taste for power
Life awaits its final hour

No justice found
Beneath the blackened clouds of war
Attack in the darkness
No peace before the dawn

###Bolt Thrower
###Forgotten Existence

Storms calm neon skies
Still chilling winds roam the nulear wastes
Haunting the conscience of a forgotten existence
Civilisation's mistake

Peace at last takes it's grip on the land
For a moment time stands still
Existing in the debris of bygone wars
Hope breeds an incentive not to kill

Existence declines, extinction mankind
A lifetime of time slips away

Resurrect mankind sacrificed to power
From ruins to the birth of a new reality
Rising from the ashes of past destruction
Civilisations, new existence

Lost in a void without future or past
Shattered mind in the presence of pain
Domineering desolation
Controlling the solitary plains

Existence declines, extinction mankind
A lifetime of time slips away

Darkest fears dwell in man's mind
Insight to depths of what will be
Reclaimation from the paths of destruction
From ruins to the birth of a new reality

Construction from destruction
Bringing back life to mankind
Rebuilding an existence sacrificed for power
A future with hope to find

Existence declines, extinction mankind
A lifetime of time slips away

Existence - Declines
Extinction of Mankind
Lifetime - Of time
Now slips - Away

###Bolt Thrower
###Dark Millennium

You feel confusion and new torment as your mind decays
Devolution of your life - begins today - begins today

Hear the sircas scream in vain
Despair for your life
Hope is futile as missiles strike
A cruel twist of the knife

Those that dominate, direct their hate
Life obliterate, humans terminate

Hope for a future, is what you say
With your world in ruins, what a price to pay

As you crawl through the wreckage - you can't believe
Could mankind really be so naive
This world now twisted, brought to its knees
With the people in power left to oversee

A world totally deformed, no hope of being reborn
The heart from it now torn, this world now we all mourn

Look to the future, on your knees now pray
With this world in ruins, what a price to pay

Your world's now in ruins
What a price you paid

###Bolt Thrower
###Lost Souls Domain

Driven now by fetid winds, we came to this place of despair
Fresh visions of death filled my mind with disgust
Yet still we stood here and stared

A world steeped in torment
Where agony prevails
With cruel sadistic torture
All hope of life now fades

The time has come, you have no choice, now you face your death
Choke at your last breath

Your mind now screams
Could it be you're insane
To live your life
Within the lost souls domain

Lost souls domain

Plead for mercy
To your gods now pray
For in this place
You now shall stay
No way out
Tripped within
This reign of terror
Shall now begin

Shall now begin

City of the damned - hear the screams cry out
The agony within - untold without a doubt

Feel your life - slipping through your hands
A new reality - held now by this land

###Bolt Thrower
###Psychological Warfare

Psychological Warfare
Still bear the scars from a past war ceased
Neurological nightmare
Torture suffered holds the mind from peace

Can't face reality unrestrained mentality
Hiding from the darkness of your insanity
Driven to soul despairs
Madness in your mind tears
No escape from this mental insanity

Captive life, held in past
Deranged memories still burning in your brain
Thoughts of pain, darkest dreams
Self inflicted torture, eating at your mind
Punishment, no pain release
Captive to the darkness of this psychotic insanity

Tearing in deep mind
Madness dwells with pain
Destruction of your life
Renders you insane

###Bolt Thrower
###In battle there is no law

In the fight for existence and life
There is no law
And in the presence of eternal death
There is no law
And just the struggle for power the domination prevails
An arising slaughter
In revenging, every man for himself
As in battle there is no law

Countless numbers die in war's path
Armies falling to our wrath
Warriors of power marching to fight
Destruction, killing, all that's in sight

Raise the shield or be cast in to death
Take a final, look your final breath
Innocent victims of war
No turning back, in battle there is no law

Awaiting the slaughter, time stands still
Thoughts fade away, so does your will
Enemy close in, blood on their mind
You won't die, once die a thousand times

Raise the shield or be cast in to death
Take a final look your final breath
Innocent victims of war
No turning back, in battle there is no law

Soldiers of hatred, killing corps of war
Bodies litter the field, what was it for?
Stench of death, no victory for this night
Plead for mercy, you have no right

Raise the shield or be cast in to death
Take a final, look your final breath
Innocent victims of war
No turning back, in battle there is no law

No law
No Law

###Bolt Thrower
###What dwells within

An unseen force tears through your soul
Revealing memories past life unknown
Fervent emotions from deep within
Inner transformation now begins

Life before you cannot conceive
Thoughts repressed denial to believe

Precise identity you cannot tell
Existing inside this mortal shell

Summon the powers that dominate
Grasp your inner strength seize control of hate
A forgotten past a life of normality
This sudden transition redirects your destiny

Consumed with resentment hatred you now possess
Potency awakened from eternal rest
Through invocation to an existence you detest

What has become of your humility
Corrupted through change to anguish and misery
As man's preordained fate now doses in
You're a silent witness to what dwells within

As man judges all by outward impressions
Our status is classed through amounting possessions
Whilst shrouding the truth through delightful expression
Injustice presides by mass edacious obsession

###Bolt Thrower
###Profane Creation

Constructed with vengeful hate
The extinction of life, man's final plight
We strive until the end
Though none shall be taken alive
A killing machine, programmed for death
To destroy all that comes within (his) sight
Mindless, created insane
Mankind shall never survive
Never survive
Strength becoming weaker, as fear grows within
Faced with eternal damnation, the end shall now begin

Profane creation, the dawn of a new age
Technology's progression, over man machines reign
Enslaved without compassion, new masters of (the) earth we dwell
Human life is worthless, in this automated living hell

In the quest for perfection, life becomes obsolete
Humanity faces deletion, this nightmare world is complete
As we wait for execution, in silence we stand in line
The total extinction of the existence of mankind

Our futile life's now ended, free from the suffering and pain
Our systems (now) are loaded, we have been created profane

Profane creation, the dawn of a new age
Technology's progression, over man machines reign
Enslaved without compassion, new masters of (the) earth we dwell
Human life is worthless, in this automated living hell

In the quest for perfection, life becomes obsolete
Humanity faces deletion, this nightmare world is complete
As we wait for execution, silent we stand in line
The total extinction of the existence of mankind

###Bolt Thrower
###As the World Burns

Turn around and shield your eyes,
Don't look back as the earth dies
No tomorrow for eternity
The apocalyptic prophecy
Few shall survive the final war
Our futile lives shall be no more.
Innocent victims of the nuclear glare,
Are torn apart as they stand unaware.
The whole world is radioactive,
What's left of men now unproductive,
None shall escape the fall-out rain,
Our future life shall be steeped in pain.
Feel the chill of the nuclear winds,
Our planets downfall shall now begin.
No excuse for the vast destruction,
Caused by man with no comprehension.
Life expectancy now decreases,
As atomic warfare rapidly increases,
Our foolish games, what have we learnt?
No time for sorrow as the world burns.

###Bolt Thrower
###Graven Image

Words cannot explain
Darkest thoughts within the mind
Centuries of hatred
Now subside
Commencing the birth
Of new life
Rise from the wreckage of the past

Words cannot explain
The feeling agony within
Anguish summoned
Perception begins
All secrets now revealed
You cannot win
Searching in hope of a new age

All feelings put aside
Numbed by the vision
Nothing left alive
Facing devastation

Awakened in remorse
To rebuild from destruction
Recreate life's evolution

No chance for redemption
All life now ceased
Pleading for forgiveness
There shall be no peace

###Immolation
###Those Left Behind

I lift my soul joyfully
If not, my life will end painfully
Extol He who rides above the clouds
Majestic and glorious
Reigning victorious

Exalted to His name
Far above the Earth
But below is where I'll see
Unmoved by Your praise
High above the heavens
Resounding out His name
Far below are my beliefs

Your majestic light shines down upon me
I turn my face... and shut my eyes
For Your light casts darkness upon my world
A world I've not chosen... to dwell within
For those who judge me by Your standards
Say I'm unworthy... of Your grace

Enthroned upon their praise
Pethroned with my disgust
Unworthy of Your glory
You turn Your back on me

Yo are Jesus
You are Lord
Imperfect God
You are nothing to me
For this You say
I'll burn for eternity

Jesus Christ
You are Lord
You are God
But have You won over sin and death
Victory's crown shall be ours
For we are those
Those You've left behind

###Immolation
###Internal Decadence

Digression to an unknown fear, mortified
Soul embraced in a darkened grasp, path to hell
Infiltrate the weakened mind, succumb to death
Waste away, convulse in pain, dissolve within...

Twisted brain
Abstract world of pain
Anguish of the mind
Tortured afterlife

Bodily entombed... beckons internal grave
Paralyzed with fear... internal decadence
Submit to parasitic thoughts, drown in a mental haze
Extraction from reality, feelings now devoured
Dimension in hell, rotting mind, wastes away
Desire life, fade away, suffer endlessly...

Twisted brain
Abstract world of pain
Anguish of the mind
Tortured afterlife

Exiled from sanity... never to return
Mental paralysis... internal decadence

Twisted brain
Abstract world of pain
Anguish of the mind
Tortured afterlife

Noble ones perverse
Fulfillment of their lusts
Seeking innocense
To satiate their needs
Children for their pleasure
Abducted from the world
Adopted into hell
Punished for their births

Circle of Maniacs

Rules of their existence
Insane immortal laws
Desires are forbidden
Lusting for their flesh
Sickened evil minds
Manipulate to death
One hundred and twenty days
Sodom redefined

Circle of Excrement

Kneel down before the Lords
And taste the filth awaiting You
A noble feast for those enslaved
Enticing vows of defilement
Unholy palace of perversion
Unbellished with depravity
Embrace Your life, for now
It slips away

Circle of Blood

Commencement of their final trial,
Upon their final day
Trembling naked figures slowly
Marched into the courtyard
Tender flesh is seared and ripped,
Tides of blood released
The Masters watch in ecstasy
The orgies of the damned
A sacred ground of tragic deaths

###Immolation
###Rigor mortis

You're dying but you're still alive
Slow gradual decay
Doused with chemicals forever your cursed
To walk the earth as undead

Eating the brains the way to endure
The painfulness of death
Stiffening of your muscles
But you cannot die

Rigor mortis, settles in
Rotting corpse, blackened skin
Decayed bones, rotten flesh
Rigor Mortis, after death

But you are still a corpse beneath the earth
Rancid souls await rebirth
Acid rain brings them to life
destiny of strife

Lurking in the streets
Your flesh they need to eat
Feel the horrid chill
Knowing they can't be killed

###Immolation
###Relentless Torment

City in fear, tyrannical king
Rules by the dark side, terror he brings

Darkness has settled
Streets are all clear
Night guards are watching, your living in fear

Break the reign of the tyrants
We must form an alliance
Withstand the king and show defiance
Time has come for deathly violence

Rebellions the talk, amongst the crowd
Better keep quiet, don't talk too loud He rules from the throne, castle on the hill
All who oppose are tortured and killed

Relentless torment time to rebel
Overthrow the king
Break away from his hell

Ignorant fools, can't you all see
Unite and destroy and we'll all be set free

###Immolation
###Here in After

Alone
Without warmth
Without light
But how do I see in this darkness
Death feeds upon me
The condemned under my feet
Eternity has passed us by

Everyone is here
The ones I've loved and hated
All of us in pain... together

In a timeless void of anguish
Where sorrow is like breathing
and with every breath I hurt more and more

The fallen and trampled
Damned to spend eternity here

Constant burning souls
In a sea of writhing flesh
Endless plains
Of sin and deprivation

Those of wealth and might, of humble and weak
Those who gave way to uphold God's will
He who has conquered and he who has failed
The wicked and the holy in utter desolation
In this absence of being, misery consumes
Existing not living, I am dead yet I feel in total seclusion
I am left to ponder the empty promises of your shallow God

The sounds of anguish... so loud
Their sobbing... like thunder
Pierces through me... and crushes me
Again... and again... and again

So vast this pain
More unbearable it becomes
With every passing moment
I pray for an end

In a timeless void of anguish
Where sorrow is like breathing
And with every breath I hurt more and more

###Immolation
###I Feel Nothing

Your prayers,
I don't feel them in my heart
It is not hate
That I stare coldly at the son of god
I can not force the blood of Christ
To flow through me
God is love and his love is dead

Drown your sorrows in prayer
But your prayers will never change the world
I separate myself
From those who chase the spirit
I can't fall to my knees
And pretend like all the rest
This is a soul that doesn't need saving

Their paradise not mine; an illusion I will not believe
Divine presence of perfection, turns sour in my gaze
Why should I feel compassion for the suffering of your God
For all the pain he allows, I give him what he deserves

In the name of the Father,
In the name of the Son
Where is the Holy Spirit, I feel nothing
As I stare upon the crucifix, I feel nothing for a God I never knew
I refuse to embrace, and live by his word

I take not of his body
I take not of his blood
I don't need salvation
Or his forgiveness
I don't want his kingdom
My kingdom is here

###Immolation
###Failures for Gods

Have faith in their words
From your weakness they are born
Messiahs to the masses
But failures for all

Send millions to worship
Send millions to die
Devoted, they follow in blindness
Lost, they can not find their way

Eminent... immortal
Crowned by our hands

Bringers of terror, all will cower in fear
Bringers of war, their people perish and die
Bringers of plague, the faithful wither and fade
Bringers of famine, the hunger grows and grows
Cure not our ills...
Feed on our souls...

Promise eternity...
Eternity never comes...

Their lies will lull the chaos
While humanity falls around them
Impoverished, in droves they'll grovel
In confusion and fear they flourish

They've failed to lead the way out of darkness
their wourds man nothing, your gods are dead

Let them rape you
let them rule you
They will take you
You're failures for gods
No promis land
No love toward man
No perfect end
You're failures for gods

Can they not see the deception and thetyranny
So desperate they've become the victims not eh victors
Can they not see the tragedy in thier beliefs
The failures you worship are the failures you've become

Eminent... immortal
Crowned by our hands

###Immolation
###Unsaved

Shining with hues of magnificent splendor
Leading the way, revere him
The righteous, the saved
hand in hand, poised in rapture
Blissful delusion, believe in forever
Choirs of angels strike chords of transgression

How you are like your savior
With souls impure and vile
Rescued from our presence
your fall will be divine
Behold, the days of righteousness are coming
For wicked are the hearts of men and gods
Cleanse yourselves, step out of the light

Purge me of Christ... empowered, unsaved
Humble before him... the price for their saving

Don't pray for my soul for I'll rise above you
My hatred is my strength and through this I'll conquer
The fear and the weakness I see in your eyes

Touched by the divine
They hide in the light
Adorn me with his crown

###Immolation
###Furthest From The Truth

Son of highest
You are falling
You are falling
Not floating from out of the sky
You deceive us
You betray us
You will not lift our hearts to eternity
But leave a hole with despair
We waited and waited
Our crosses born
And still you did not come
And how does it feel
As life passes by
We will not know until we pass
that you are a lie
Will we receive the mark
Of those who did not believe
The temptations that are burning us alive
But you tell us that there's sin in what we think
For forgiveness we'll believe your every word
but will you show us what our souls cry out to see
No... No... No...
Son of man, are you the son of God
No... No... No...
did you die to cleanse this world of sin
No... No... No...
Will you return from the dead to
save the world again
No... No... No...
Has the blood you shed turned the darkness into light... No
Son of highest You are falling
You are falling
not floating from out of the sky
We waited and waited
Our crosses born
And still you did not come

###Immolation
###Fall From a High Place

Messiah or man
To me you gave this bloodied crown
And with it came such tragic folly
such strong devotion from those so weak
Lend me your soul... I'll fill it with fear
Carry you high to where you can see
The fall that awaits, so inviting and cold
From the high place we'll fall below
In death I am born
From man to God
Through blindness
Your suffering
Forced upon this cross... High above in shame
Forced upon this pedestal... High above the blame
Your blood holds my Kingdom high
A kingdom built on fear and lies
So sour has this bread and wine become
For I am not a God, a martyr or a king
I've bled as you bleed
I've cried as you cry
I've sinned as all of you
I've died, as you will too
But I see through your blindness
And I wait for your fall
Resurrected by your faith
But I'll never walk this world again
Hang me high above all and nail me to forever
Never let me fall from this highest of places

###Suffocation
###Seeds of the suffering

Lies, deceitful words of impatience
Futile words of evasion

The gods that have once spoken to me
Have abandoned me to my pre-destined state
A state in which there are no words, is no language
Only the language of the endless suffering

Suffering that brings me to appreciate my new found existence
One that spawns forth a new being
A being in which there is no appreciation for his fellow man
to see
Hatred and remorse unto those who have punished me
Punishment to cold to see
I don't see, I don't see
One that I have once created
Forced to change, I don't need

The path of abomination of all things

For I am now a seed, that will one day set forth a new race
One that will cleanse my soul
Anticipation of the weak-minded fools

One that my once beloved gods will not recognize

Race which feeds off the suffering
As the mortals cry out their new found god

The race grows strong
Until the day
The day of judgement

The race grows strong
Until the day

###Suffocation
###Habitual Infamy

Pray in homage under shadows of ancestry
Conceptual lords above bathing in your inquiry
Memorizing thoughts through hallucinations of despair
Imminence burns within, plunge yourself to disrespect
Battred visions, desolation drips into your eyes
A feeling of oppresiveness that vastly clutters life
Deviation scarred within, placed upon you from your birth
Engage with destitution, as it rips into your mind

Morally detrimental
Incapacitated existence
Ignorant false worship

Exit all that's insincere
Rendered never to beleive, never to place trust again
Deny the coss you bear
Resisting all religion, resisting infirmities
Habitual infamy
Malignant infatuation
Reduces your will to live
Illusive reality
Images shred your mind to pieces
Deception crowds you
An infection of thoughts that god is there for you
Condemnation
Self-inflicted betrayal provoked by others

Sink in deep depression
States of mental turmoil
Abdiction enters
Sanity depletes
Paralyzing conflicts
Fear of retribution
Catastrophic frenzies
Burns within your mind

Sifting through delusions
Comatose with anguish
Tribulation drowns all hope
To live on

Purge your soul in hate
You're realizing you can't afford
Brace yourself til all resistance ends
Cut yourself and release the blood

###Suffocation
###Mass Obliteration

Warfare, a promise to eliminate mankind.
The planet as we know it, taken by demented minds.
Warheads produced to exterminate the earth.
The sacrifice will lead us to our death, no rebirth.

No one has the power to declare this world to die.
Voting and electing the right to crucify.
Times of turmoil have decided what to do.
No need for common knowledge, we're through.

World explosion
Mass obliteration
... of a race.

Forced to live here day by day through day by day.
We dread the fear of living in the afterworld spirits of the dead.
Thoughts of nuclear holocaust that drive our world insane.
Woman and children forced and left to kill.

Through daily hibernation, manage to survive.
Sifting through, they must be found, extinction we provide.

purify - the unholy land
extinction - the so called master race
crucify - the preachers of this hate
liquefy - the minds of those they create.

###Suffocation
###Catatonia

Force fed immobilization
Man made liquid controlling my limbs
I want to die, no reason for living
Dealing with complications life brings
A corpse with no thoughts
No feelings or perceptions of life
The pleasures of death I foresee
Nightmares and day mares combining
To torture my being - This torture inhibits my life

The world is a graveyard of fools left to cope
With the torment and regret of man now deceased
Ghouls are released to destroy the race
Which we call human beings

Existence is torn from my soul
Perdition is what is believed to be seen
Suffering from the inside
Nefarious is the way
You choose to be - Left with no will to live
My intestinal wall begins to cave in
Trapped as they say
I begin to rot here as I lay

Time to take a look
At what has begun to pass before me
Die a slow death
It now begins to take it's toll

Catatonia

Scared as I lay here dead
From this infectious disease
I want to rise from here
To recover what is mine

Abdicate your position in life
Now that you lie deceased
Rising from the tomb you own
To take what is rightfully yours

Scared as I lay here dead
From this infectious disease
I want to rise from here
To recover what is mine

###Suffocation
###Depths Of Depravity

Why do you torment me?
You make me hate my existence.
You will soon surpass your own fucking life.
Now the time has come for you to see your death.
I cut your flesh.
I receive much pleasure.

As you start to bleed.
I no longer control my urges.
The feeling is so complete.
I'm finally at one with myself.

Now that I control the rest of your existence.
How does it feel to be in pain and misery.
For many years you made me feel that way.
I praised you for so long.
I'm now your God.

I cannot control my urges.
Now I must take my revenge.
I slice at you.
You begin to die.

The pleasure was all yours.
To have the strength to leave and not look back.
To give up completely.
No more will to survive.

Now that all is done.
My completed masterpiece.
This sinful life of mine.
Will not go to waste.
The pleasure's all mine.

To have taken your mortal life.
I am what you created.
To inflict my own pain and misery.

You manipulated my mind.
Filled it with your lies.
Feasted on my soul.
Destroyed my will.
Now there's nothing.
No reason for reason.
Now I must take life.
To repent my sins.

###Suffocation
###Suspended in Tribulation

Reality suspends my present life.
Curious thoughts, I confront my mortality.
Uncertain to the laws of the unknown.
I have no fear in facing trials of the mind one by one.
Sifting through ossuaries of creation.
Looking for a worth, is existence pointless?
Perceptive to the truth, I never may return.
Resistance falling short, I sever all my ties one by one.

Vanish into the unseen origins of infinity.
A pleasant swim in the seas of dormant ecstacy.
A state of being I could spend with all of eternity.
Suspended above the remains of what I used to be.

I can see things not capable of imagining.
The explanation of my mind has progressed me endlessly.
Things that once were illusions have become reality.
I perceive now what was never clear to me.

Unwelcomed kind.
No way to overcome, I'm disadvantaged prey.
My way back has been erased.

Torn from my bliss.
No longer bound in flesh, a dismembered soul.
Helpless to what I can't see.

Unwelcomed kind.
No way to overcome, a disembodied soul.
My way back has been erased.

I must focus on what I can't see.
Things done to me, I cannot explain.
Falling further from myself.
To give in would end all my pain.
Subconscious misery placed unto me.

Is their meaning to this life?
To break away transparent light.
The end is clearer.
Pass through the mirror.
I fade into the sky.

Hanging in the balance.
Drowning in the afterlife.

###Suffocation
###Devoid Of Truth

Your life has been planned since the day you were born
Affliction undefinable, condemned to suffer with the norm
Burden of despair - Traits of self denial
Raised and misled by life's light
I refuse let shine for me

Corrupted misconceptions of how life should really be
Shadowing existence in your plagued reality
Feeding off the error of the ones your emulate
Defection to deception and to mentally incarcerate
Devoid of truth

Monarch of deceit and lies
Plagiarism overrides
Devoid of truth

Captive through what's carved in stone
Bleeding is the moral throne
Beckoned to false entity
Betrayed by eternity
Devoid of truth

Writhing in the treachery
Face down in your misery
I feel not a thing

###Suffocation
###Despise the Sun

Pain - Infliction - Loathing ways
Excursions into harsh reality
Scorn - Diaspora - I'm now forced to be this way
Torrents of delusion - Placid winds erase

Torn away from the truth of my inner self
Life replaced, despise the sun that breeds disgrace
Wretched visions of a life that could never be

Gloom - Depression - Disarray
Conviction shrouded by malignancy
Visions scream forth - Corruption welcomes
Grasping at salvation in hopes of an escape
Retribution - Evoking rage
Resurgance through a lust for apathy
Cleanse - Unshackle - Pressure builds can't take the strain
Onward to defiance - Banish with disdain

Torn away from the truth of my inner self
Life replaced, despise the sun that breeds disgrace
Wretched visions of a life that could never be

Shatter illusion - Shed my confusion
Release possession to this regression
Permeate the rival, Glorified despisal
Dethrone conception, Sever intention
Release possession to this regression
Shatter illusion - Shed my confusion
Release possession to this regression

Pain - Infliction - Loathing ways
Excursions into harsh reality
Visions scream forth - Corruption welcomes
Grasping at salvation in hopes of an escape
Retribution - Evoking rage
Resurgance through a lust for apathy
Cleanse - Unshackle - Pressure builds can't take the strain
Onward to defiance - Banish with disdain

###Suffocation
###Souls to Deny

Souls, souls to deny 
Oppressed to a promised place 

To desire a place for you to die, unbeknownst to you thoroughly denied. 
Expectations of a fruitful way to live, ungodly not to be achieved by you. 
Evil lies, death denied 
cursed to walk this pitiful existence 
To be taught a certain way to be, 
let down by the powers consuming me 

Souls, souls to deny 
Oppressed to the promised place 

God has abandoned you pain and misery a gift to you. 
How do I deserve all this despite this unholy place 
Infliction of desires purging thoughts realized 

Souls, souls to deny 
Oppressed to a promised

###Suffocation
###Surgery of Impalement

To dissect the mind impaled of visions a delusional 
state from which one neglects 
Incise the flesh with delicate precision 
as to not disrupt such artistry 

To dominate a feild of iniquity undeserving of many. 
One must realize a painful demise deeds of tranquility. 
Inflicting misery, an instrument of morbidity thrust deep on you. 
Conflicted desires will transpire justify what's right. 

Impaled upon a structure dear to you 
Blood soaked hands drip insistently 
Organs deemed venemous to you 
Surgery of impalement 

The blood drips from my hands 
Your flesh is warm upon my face 
Impaled with a collection of sickness 
To desire that what you recieve 

Impaled upon a structure dear to you 
Blood soaked hands drip insistently 
Organs deemed venemous to you 
Surgery of impalement

###Morbid Angel
###Maze of Torment

Life betrayal - a warping rage
Evil ripping caverns through your mind
Immolation - in blood you've signed your soul away
Sickening life ends but the horror has just begun
Vultures moaning a funeral dirge
Walls await to cradle you and rip your soul apart
Incessant screams echoes through the maze
Insanity approaches - imminent demise

Maze of torment...
Maze of torment...
Maze of torment...
Maze of torment...
Maze of death

Stricken from the holy book - deliverance to pain
Effigy of jesus christ burning in your mind
Voices cry out to bid you welcome
Locked within the dungeons of darkness - no escape!

Passing through corridors embedded with
Scars of those who have gone before you
And left their marks

Warning comes too late to save you now
Visions of suffering stab from the inside

You pray for death
Mourning does no good as you can only die once

Souls are being raped by the maze
Lost in these halls... endlessly

Maze of torment...
Maze of torment...
Maze of torment...
Maze of torment...
Maze of death

###Morbid Angel
###Bleed for the Devil

Come to me, lord of filth
Hear my cries princes of nightmares
Touch us with your morbid lips
Let us taste your foulness

Bleed for the devil
Impious mortal lives
Feel the enticing power
Fill the chasm of your soul

Fill the air with the smell of death
Grace us with your magic
Fill the night with the stench of evil
I summon forth the beast

Bleed for the devil
Impious mortal lives
Feel the enticing power
Fill the chasm of your soul

Cold look in his eyes
He holds the gleaming knife
Girl cries as he cuts way the
Strips of flesh

Bleed for the devil
Impious mortal lives
Feel the enticing power
Fill the chasm of your soul

###Morbid Angel
###Abomination

Churning sea of Absu
Place of weeping death
Tiamat, dark serpent
Lord of the morbid priests
Enraged with hate for god
The priests of chaos chant
From the book of the worm
They burn the symbols of christ

We spit on the virgin lamb
And mock the words he spoke
His ways not worthy of me
We choose to burn in the pits of hell

Wreakers of death and havoc
Inflicting never ending pain
Sing the words of emptiness
Formulas of death
Call the queens of death
And the god of the dead
The sea of Absu rolls
Rising spirit of Nar-Marratuk!

Bow down before the master
And pray the defeat of God Dog
Prayer of the ensnarers
Blind fiends of chaos rule

Rise up o powers of the sea
In the name of Absu I call
Come and carry my curse
To the ones who cause me disgust
May they burn in my cauldron
For they are as molten wax
Burn consume thy powers

Liars in wait, priests of the night
Make images to burn by the moon
Robbing the spirit, breaking god's law
Send up our hate to burn heavens gate

###Morbid Angel
###Angel of Disease

Your plastic souls melt within cauldron's burning bright
Chanting to the Ancient Ones, chants of broken lines
Kneel before the altar, sacrifice is made
It is pleasing to the ones most ancient of the days

They call the prince of disease, messenger of the Absu
Carry through icy winds our curse upon their church

Hanging helpless above the pentagram
Sacrifice swings within the leather noose
Sing the ancient hymn that makes the Absu roll
Raise the rusty knife and let loose the blood of Kingu

Sudden death throws off the balance that's within the sky
Priest calls forth infernal names to the ones beyond the gate

Angel of disease one who shuns the light
Shub Niggurath goat with a thousand young

Praise the beast, the chanting grew
Praise the beast with virgin blood
Praise the beast with soul and mind
Praise the beast and do the sign

Bind their kings in iron chains
Execute the judgement for them
Come and taste the earthly pleasures
Orgies of endless time

Beneath the rolling fog hate ignites their minds
From their graves the dead will rise to answer Nammtar's call
Upon a twisted cross the virgin corpse hangs
They blacken out the sun and burn the elder gods

Priests of chaos calling forth
Abominations of the pit
Cthulhu meets in the void
Ancient Ones rule once more

###Morbid Angel
###Thy Kingdom Come

Restless minds beneath the ground
Through ghostly winds I hear the sound
Crying forth in ancient tongues
Eternal quest of vengeance
From tombs of scorn cadavers rise
Angered fury in their eyes
Solemn rage, a need to kill
Feasting on holy hordes

Evil curse is carried forth zombies rage
Burning holy images in life they were
Forced to hail
Eternal flames have purified their souls
Born again in blasphemy, thy kingdom come

Twisted oath nodebliwith
Preying on those who seek the cross
Let none be pardoned for their crimes
Feeble race will die
Scripture burns in infamy
Tortured souls have been set free
Taunting he who sits on high
Pray thy kingdom come

Evil curse is carried forth zombies rage
Burning holy images in life they were
Forced to hail
Eternal flames have purified their souls
Born again in blasphemy, thy kingdom come

Banished from the living
Bodies long decayed
Mass of resurrection

Sepulchers abandoned
Insurgent souls arise
Disseminating evil

Curse of devastation
Implored by hell's command
Darkness rips the land

Morbid priests serenity
Sing praise
Thy kingdom is at hand

Twisted oath nodebliwith
Preying on those who seek the cross
Let none be pardoned for their crimes
Feeble race will die
Scripture burns in infamy
Tortured souls have been set free
Taunting he who sits on high
Pray thy kingdom come

Evil curse is carried forth zombies rage
Burning holy images in life they were
Forced to hail
Eternal flames have purified their souls
Born again in blasphemy, thy kingdom come

###Morbid Angel
###Brainstorm

Gods transform me
The storm will cleanse me
Civilized I shall not be
By this holy strain of laws

I fall below the earth
I smell the ancients' breath
The fiends encircle me
They speak my name in tongues

For I'm no human now
I burn the ways conform
The gods are pleased with me
They speak my name in tongues

I am the seer
I know the texts divine
Thunder words
Demons race into my eyes.

Azazel
Lend to me your wings of twelve
I shall fly into the storm
I, son of fire, in anger become
The lightning bolts that strike the earth

I am the seer
I know the texts divine
Thunder words
Demons race into my eyes.

###Morbid Angel
###Curse The Flesh

Being has overwhelmed the space between the silence of eternity
Vision has intruded upon the light that pours through me, my energy
Substance has veiled, the pleasures long lost, the beauty of emptiness
This very flesh confines, and spoils this demon's seed

Waiting to light, A dead sky aflame
To suffocate, to rejoice in your misery
This waiting it seems, for so long I've yearned to see
the burning flesh of your humanity
Your withering flesh, I've longed to see

May you fall to never again arise
May you cease to ever again be
May your soul eternally be, in seas of pain
Pleading, churning, drowning
Pleading, dying, burning

The Treachery Returns to the Betraying Eyes
Your Betrayers cries, fall to unyielding ears
And oh how it came to be, That you would pray to me
That you would beg to me, that this curse not come to be
That you would plead. That this curse not be released

May you fall to never again arise
May you cease to ever again be
May your soul eternally be, in seas of pain
Pleading, churning, drowning
Pleading, dying, burning

###Morbid Angel
###Praise The Strength

Remnants, From the ash arise the allegiance
Martyr's unforgotten lives, immortal
Heretics, gods of the Dawning time... Vindictive

Praise this source of strength
Seize this time and heed
Embrace the strength and heed
The fallen behind me

Tyrants, stand before the task, Impeding
Mortals, In the wake of Gods, Beneath Kings
Tyranny, Fall away in shards, Demise
Leaches, Clinging to their shite, Die Blindly

Praise this Source of Strength
Seize this time and Heed
Embrace the Strength and Heed
The Fallen behind me

A way forsaking, Waste, Unhuman
Infected reason, infected being
A new time Dawning, Our time Beginning
The Reign of Leaches, it now ends...

Praise the Strength and Praise the Being
Sing these Words and Dance to Victory
Praise the Force that None can Conquer
Embrace the Strength, the Sacred Power

Praise the Strength and the Dawn Of Reckoning
See the Wrath Fall on those who Oppose This
Be One in Voice and Chant the Mantra
Feel the Force and Know Gods beyond Man

Praise the Strength, and Praise the Dawning
Embrace the Wake that Flows behind this 
Grasp the Light of the New Reign Rising
Stand with Kings, Fight Undying...

Praise the Strength, And Praise the being
Sing these Words and Dance to Victory
Praise the Force that None can Conquer
Embrace the Strength

Remnants, From the ash arise the allegiance
Martyr's unforgotten lives, immortal
Tyrants, stand before the task, Impeding
Mortals, In the wake of Gods, Beneath Kings

Praise this Source of Strength
Seize this time and Heed
Embrace the Strength and Heed
The Fallen behind me

###Morbid Angel
###At One With Nothing

Omniscient are the eyes that see beyond
what we choose to see
transcending of beliefs, that limit man's being
the dogma that feeds the listless
has thrived uncounted years
impeding on ones perception
of what is to be

Awaken to see
A god of a desertion
A god of lies

enlightened by a way, deceiving
only truth to the blind
the salvation that you seek is empty
no god of light
the venom that has fed your faith
you except with ease
but the sights that lay before you
destroy your beliefs

Awaken to be
At One with Nothing
Now all will be seen

the seeds of the weak destroy
the lies told of forgiving, exposed
the ignorant, thrown to the wake
your calling names of gods,
they are only shrines
the waves of the truth, enslave
slaying the blind

Awaken to a light of knowing
all your truth was lies
and the faith which you embraced
has left you blind
deceived like the fools that surround you
it came with ease unfulfilled were the days of your being
but now you will see

###Morbid Angel
###Opening of the Gates

These chains that have choked existence,
have fallen away
this veil that has blinded eyes has been lifted
and now it is gone

and like the ways of the sheep
the flock has been to only receive
led to the gates of their enemy
led to the slaughter of their beliefs 
and now their gazing eyes have turned
turned to see us laughing

these fools who have thought
us to be as they are,
have never truly seen
guided by limiting the ways that they think,
they thought us blind and obscene

but now the sheep are wailing
cries to a god they never see
and as the gates are closing
down upon the all they have believed
and now their pleading eyes have turned
turned to see the eyes of the laughing

the ties have bound these fools
to the ways of the blind,
is ignorant bliss
lies that were fed to the slumbering mass
they've grazed upon it
and all that awaits men failing to see,
is the sight they've despised
the gates have opened,
your religion has died

###Cannibal Corpse
###Born In a Casket

Enter the crypts of hell, to impregnate the dead
Fresh burial sight, my hunger grows tonight
Undying lust for cadaverous molestation
Sights of death building my sensations
Ferocious need for decomposing bodies

Sex with the dead now I must breed
Within the stiff corpse planting my seed
The taste of formaldehyde, smell of the rot
Suck out the goo, feast on her crotch

Raging fires of hell, burning through my soul
My love for a dead fuck, I cannot control
The child soon will rise, all evil will survive
Birth through death

The newborn needs a feast, its mother is the meal
Chomping on her flesh, his teeth tearing her skin
I love to fuck the dead, demons in my head
Tearing at my brain

Bleeding sores beginning to stench
While you lick the festering stump
Green infection discharging pus
Devour the putrid afterbirth

Sex with the dead now I must breed
Within the stiff corpse planting my seed
The taste of formaldehyde, smell of the rot
Suck out the goo, feast on her crotch

###Cannibal Corpse
###Rotting Head

A quivering pile of useless flesh, locked in a padded cell
Hidden from the prying eyes of curiosity
Experimental surgery made him what he is today
His head is rotting but his body lives on as a worthless vegetable
Unknown to mankind, the incredible power of his mind

Hideous heredity, genetic imbalance, resorting to cannibalism
A feast begins as the patient's skull is cracked open like a walnut
Brains devoured in a frenzied slaughter, thrist for gore nothing more
Bile is dripping, pus from wounds, as the coroner drinks it down

The sights before your eyes you can't describe
A trip through this living hell will rot away your skull

Genital lacerating, anal asyphyxiation
Blockade of bowel passage, defåcation, hemmorage
Cadaverous mutilation, metamorphial radiation
Devourance of arteries, decapitated extremeties
Cranial excavation, cerebral liquidation
Brain turned to soup, ears are dripping goop

Slimy, cozing, dripping pus, torn out fingernails starting to fuse
Shredded cartilage victim lies, eye sockets, but no eyes
Miles of intestines strewn all about, facial features strickened with gout
Hanging bodies dripping with blood, the blackened fluid sinks in the mud

A quivering pile of useless flesh, locked in a padded cell

###Cannibal Corpse
###Rancid Amputation

Torsos hang from their own intestines
Raped of all bodily extensions,
Stumps wreathing in sludge like infection
Suffering through a Rancid amputation
A pulsating artery accompanied by some veins,
Slit with no restraint
Sacs of pus develop
My muscles tighten as I feel the rush

I look at your body starting to gush
I slice through the limb, a human dissection
Portions of half-eaten flesh in my mouth
Starting to chew your now bleeding stump
I will swallow your pus
Your own rectal slime I'll force you to drink
Vessels explode as needles injected

Uncontrollable, my brain tormented
Slit from head to toe, die through the torture
Disease engulfs you, internal rot
Fresh cut wounds, beginning to clot
Ripping through flesh is what I do best
Tear off an arm, amputated neck
Eyes removed, cranium smashed
Decomposing remains, severed in half

Dying slowly never to rest,
Nerves are quivering as I rip

Removal of life on the blade of my knife
Inserted in your spine, smashing through bone
Feel my hell, I feed on fright
Rape the limbless cadaver

###Cannibal Corpse
###Innards Decay

Rotting alive
Tearing my way through the meat
Driven to kill,
My brain twitching for guts
Devoted to evil
Severed arteries gush
Hungry for the blood
Life is to decay
Victims meet my blade, carving out organs
A world of pain and terror
Visions of the future
Premonition of the evil,
Forthcoming eve of darkness
The chosen one will come

Eyes torn out, bodies cut in half
Twisted corpses hang from broken necks
Demented madman, unholy rampage
Impaled cranium beginning to drain
Sodomize the carcass, chew the anal rot
Sewn within the body the dark becomes my light
Live inside the shell, feed upon infection
At one with the dead

I rip my way through easy prey,
Disfigured bodies decompose
Chewed limbs drip with pus,
Intestinal strangulation
Humans left ripped apart
Lap up the dripping goo
Wretched chunks of bleeding flesh
Internally you rot away

My need to kill induced by hate,
Betrayal of trusted ones
My mark left on this earth,
Victims of my slaughter
Souls of my dead, murdered by my hand
Blood on my face, innards decay
Snapping necks chewing flesh
Insatiable thirst for blood
Slicing throats viciously
Uncontrollable insanity
Tear out the beating heart
Engulf the quivering spleen,
Chew the meat
Death is my life
Life is to decay victims
Meet my blade carving out organs,
A world of pain and terror,
Visions of the future
Premonition of the evil
Forthcoming, eve of darkness
Eyes torn out bodies cut in half
Twisted corpses hang from broken necks,
Demented madman, unholy rampage
Impaled cranium beginning to drain.

###Cannibal Corpse
###Absolute Hatred

Never leave your nest unguarded
Next of kin the first to go
Absolute hatred cast upon the family
Payback for the hated one

I am the judge, jury, executioner
And pallbearer all in one
Process of elimination
Affirmative action has just begun
Expectorate upon your soul
Malicious devilry is unleashed ten fold
You cannot hide

Witness of my stopping power
Reaction time is not enough
Psychological torment tearing at you sanity
it has to be, it must be done

Hatred flows, uncontained, feel my wrath
Through the death of your entire tribe

Hatred flows, uncontained
I must archieve my revenge through hatred

I've regained my pride
Victory's mine
You cannot hide
The footsteps you hear are gonna be mine

###Cannibal Corpse
###Eaten From Inside

Dwelling inside was an anger, an anger that
grew into hatred
Grinding, churning inside of me
Seeking, finding the need to feed
On my soul, it now appears I've lost control
Of my mind, it's now begun to tear and grind
The pain, its destination my brain
Can't hide from being eaten
from inside - inside

Originating deep within, a heart
that is now cold and dead
Tearing its way through my organs,
leaving nothing but shreds
Ripping, tissue is torn away
Severing, parts and veins in the way
My insides are on the outside of me
My bones now shatter and explode
The pain, its destination my brain
Can't hide from beign eaten from inside

Left on the ground is my head,
waiting for the final blow
Brain violently corroding,
the end won't come fast only slow
Seeing what's left of my body
Drowning, blood is surrounding me
My skull melts revealing my brain
Exploding, my body's imploding
The pain, its destination my brain
I've died, I've been eaten from inside

###Cannibal Corpse
###Ecstacy in Decay

Immence oceans of gore, rivers of pus, mountains of bones
Rapture, fester in filth, abnormal wealth, immenced in a world of decadence
Ecstacy in decy, engrossed in deterioration
Penchant for extreme ordure 
Pervading of vicera
Rejoice in gristly disgust
Exorbiant reality
One thousand years of compiled waste, frenzy in muck intoxicates 
Ecstacy in decay, engrossed in deterioration
Penchant for extreme ordure
Pervading of vicera
Rejoice in gristly disgust
Exuberant castigation
Wading in bile, soaking in guts, ancient inards

Immence oceans of gore, rivers of pus, mountains of bones
Rapture, fester in filth, abnormal wealth immenced in a world of decadence
Mind altered, eternally fetid cadaverous empire
Squelched domain
Swamped ruins, dismal necrotic incarnate metropolis
Lost dwelling
Exorbiant reality
Obfuscated ossuary
One thousand years of compiled waste, frenzy in muck intoxicates

###Cannibal Corpse
###Coffinfeeder

Exhume the rotted casket
Robbing graves
But not for wealth
Cloaked in moldy rags
Hunting dead
Decrepit things from hell
Invade the sacred tombs
Search for food
Embalmed five days before
Ancient body stealers
Raid again
A fresh corpse beyond the door
From the ground they rise
Plundering the grave
When the faithful die
Its them, not God they meet
Consume the rotted body
And unt more
Craving maws ooze blood
Gray skinned coffinfeeders
Seekig carrion
Eat the old ones last
Fiendish ghouls are chewing
Scraps of meat
Found inside the tomb
Roy veiled messengers
From beyond, bring the parish doom

From the ground they rise
Plundering the grave
When the faithful die
Its them, not God they meet

Unholy creatures swarming the coffin
Fighting for mouthfuls of flesh
Invading the tombs of the recently buried, to feast
Starvation of aeons sated tonight
Foraging ghouls consume
Ancient hunger awakened again

Strengthened by blood the undead attack
Septic beats from the grave
If living approach they are devoured too
Fragments of corpses nourish the pack
Fresh entrails they crave
The coffin is torn open, the zombies start to consume

From the ground they rise
Plundering the grave
When the faithful die
Its them, not God they meet

###Cannibal Corpse
###The Wretched Spawn

Conceived through rape
Procreate
A vicious brood

Ravaging intercourse
Penetrate with force
Forsaken, nude

Spawn of the wretched, born of the rape
Dawn of the murdering beasts of hate
Spawn of the wretched cunt defiled
Pawn of the darkness, blasphemous child
The wretched spawn, inherently vile

Inherited traits
Reprobate
From birth, an urge

No chance to change
Born deranged
Violence will emerge

Spawn of the wretched, born of the rape
Dawn of the murdering beasts of hate
Spawn of the wretched cunt defiled
Pawn of the darkness, blasphemous child
The wretched spawn, inherently vile

Spawn of the wretched, bred from the damned
Gone are the instincts normal for man
Spawn of the wanton loins of the cruel
Spawned by brute force, used as a tool
The wretched spawn, violence will rule

Heredity dictates brutality
Doomed to carry the legacy
Genes of the butchers, a killing breed
Revel in making the helpless bleed

Scion of the murderers
A bloodline so profane
Born insane

Predestined to annihilate
Through sinister eugenics
Sworn to kill, they will

It was made to kill

Massacre the innocents
A slaughter without meaning
Bleed, screaming

Only one remains untouched
Her fate is violation
Vile
Impregnation

###Cannibal Corpse
###Cyanide Assassin

Staking out the residence
Of the chosen target
Entering the empty home
Lace the food with poison

The hapless victim never had a chance
Precise contamination killed him fast

Shocking news traveled fast
But I have traveled faster
The only clue that's left behind
Poison in the cadaver

Cyanide assassin is my trade
Exacting methods are my quarry's bane
Toxic killing tactics stop your breath
Precision dosage leaves the victim dead
Cyanide assassin

Life, my task to end
Death, I don't regret

Analyze the next assignment
Select the proper tools
Gas will be the most effective
That is what I'll use

Release the vapors in the victim's room
Sleeping chambers fast become a tomb
Calculated venting should work fast
Enclosed space filled with poison gas
Cyanide assassin

Life, it should end fast
Death, he now should pass
Gasping, he fights for air
Face, fixed with despair
But the end does not seem close
Misjudged the lethal dose
I must return, my work's not done
He's still alive, but too weak to run

A sloppy job must be finished
Can't leave him in a coma
With my mask I won't smell
The almond-like aroma
With syringe in hand I walk into his room
He's struggling with the damage from the fumes
I plunge the needle deep into his vein
Completion of the murder ends his pain
Cyanide assassin

###Death
###Denial of Life

In your dreams
The pain is so real
Before the dead
You'll have to kneel
Hear your future screams
See your epitaph
As you scream
The dead they laugh

Pain, growing stronger
Life, exists no longer
Welcome, to a world of pain
Death and despair

Denial of life, Vile denial
Denial of life
Denial of life

Created by your mind
To overtake your life
Sacrificial suicide
End it with a knife
Much too late
To change your mind
A bloody corpse
Is left behind

Pain, growing stronger
Life, exists no longer
Welcome, to a world of pain
Death and despair

Denial of life, Vile denial
Denial of life
Denial of life

###Death
###Regurgitated Guts

Suicidal preacher hangs himself
Unfaithful servant goes straight to hell
When he returns, your life will end
Down from the skies maggots descend
Least expecting his horrible face
Your decayed guts you soon will taste
Unholy feeling grows deep inside
Choking on your guts you open wide

Regurgitated guts
Satisfy his needs
Regurgitated guts
Now you're gonna bleed

Visions of death are growing clear
Life as a corpse is what you fear
Searching through the graves to be set free
From the curse of the priest that's come to be
So unaware of what's to come
Your guts are his when he is done
Reaching for your cross to end this pain
Your life and blood he will have drained

Regurgitated guts
Satisfy his needs
Regurgitated guts
Now you're gonna bleed

In his trance
Your eyes they bleed
Your guts come forth
For his own need

###Death
###Defensive Personalities

One mind divided into three, for every problem a personality
Each one trying to protect, for the crisis a person they'll select
With sorrow comes reassurance, with confusion there's ignorance

Deny who they are, a fantasy gone too far

Protecting the weak points of the mind
Defensive personalities
Violent one minute calm the next
Defensive Personalities

Passed down from generations, years of pain and complications
Darkness was a punishment, memories time cannot mend
Brutalized from the day of birth, to reality they can't return

Existing in a world of three lives inside of one

Protecting the weak points of the mind
Defensive personalities
Violent one minute calm the next
Defensive Personalities

###Death
###Within The Mind

Transforming your mind from the inside out
Overcoming fear that made you doubt
Observing what is stored in the subconscious
Trusting what you feel with your gut responses

See past the dark and use your energy
Learn from these images
Thoughts that we call dreams

This power lies within the mind
Gain wisdom through abilities
Change what's to come in future time
Avoiding pain and misery

Look through the fake from what is real
Making decisions by what you feel
Live for the future and not the past
The weak of mind will never last

Perceiving from visions that reoccur
Analyze your dreams to gain
A better perspective of your life
In control of your destiny with mind and soul

See past the dark and use your energy
Learn from these images
Thoughts that we call dreams

This power lies within the mind
Gain wisdom through abilities
Change what's to come in future time
Avoiding pain and misery

###Death
###Secret Face

There is a mask
That covers up one's true intentions
Once removed, things become very clear
Analyze behavior patterns to see beneath
The person that is presented to you
Vulnerable through trust
Life is a twisted maze of obstacles
Presented by people with a secret face

What's on the outside
Is not always all that is real
Live by caution, what I feel
When things are reversed
People are shown for what they are
The truth is revealed
Banish the false
Pacifying moments with an acquired disguise to obtain
The things they want
By the anguish of someone else
Materialistic motives are fulfilled
Cherish the true
Vulnerable through trust
Life is a twisted maze of obstacles
Presented by people with a secret face

###Death
###Lack of Comprehension

A condemning fear strikes down
Things they cannot understand
An excuse to cover up weaknesses that lie within
Lies
Laying your guilt and pain
On people that had no part in the molding of a life
That creates its destruction
Lies
Right before your very eyes
A reflection of the mistakes
To the end you will deny
Your part in the demise of a life
Lack of comprehension
Thriving on your cliché
Compelled by self-resentment

Reaching into the minds of those that created
The depression in which they
In which they drowned their flesh and blood
Lies
So easy to blame the
Everlasting guilt on a pathetic attempt
To justify the ending of a life
Lies
Right before your very eyes
A reflection of the mistakes
To the end you will deny
Your help in the ending of a life
Lack of comprehension
Thriving on your cliché
Compelled by self-resentment

###Death
###Nothing is Everything

Living like us and sharing our day.
In another world very far away
A different existence, yet virtually the same.
Aggression is sadness and laughter is pain
Look deep into their eyes for what they have to say
Emotions take control of life everyday.
Unpredictable variations of behavior,
Hold the key to the mental door
Where nothing is everything, and everything is nothing
Staring beyond the wall a thousand times over

Seeing a part of them that is real
Just imagine how it might feel
To be denied of what life has to give
Behind mental shadows they must live
Look deep into their eyes for what they have to say
Emotions take control of life everyday.

###Death
###Mentally Blind

You see your vision and no one else's
Your every word filled with sarcasm
Crucify people with invisible knowledge
Verbal destruction with each compulsion
We will see where you go
The future for you is nowhere
Every minute a cliche of your kind
Too much to say from a person with no respect
Your accusations you will regret
From the mentally blind come ideas that are poison
Take away the power, a shallow person you will find.

What would you do without your pathetic narrow-minded approach to life,
that reflects your lack of abilities
Your opinions are self-destructive
Despair is your gain, delight is corruption
Destined to fall prey to your stories,
creating problems for your consumption
We will see where you go
The future for you is nowhere
Every minute a cliche of your kind
Too much to say from a person with no respect
Your accusations you will regret
From the mentally blind come ideas that are poison
Take away the power, a shallow person you will find.

###Death
###Sacred Serenity

Wherever we go, whatever we do
Your shadow is not far behind our steps
And our breath
Protecting and watching all...
Observing spirits on the wall
What are they telling you?

Following all instincts that are pure
Oblivious to time that may be the cure

Sacred is the gift that they
have without knowing
Serenity is knowing it's safe
from destruction of time

Maybe we could take a step back
And discover what leads us to attack
Time that is short - distance unknown
For them, each day life has just begun
Observing spirits on the wall
What are they telling you?

Following all instincts that are pure
Oblivious to time that may be the cure

Sacred is the gift that they
have without knowing
Serenity is knowing it's safe
from destruction of time

###Death
###Without Judgement

Guilty until proven innocent
We condemn your soul and fate
Never mind the possibilities
Too busy for logic or to calculate

Take part in a diminishing breed
Where complex turns to simplicity
When pain is acknowledged
Frivolous calculations will be abolished

Without judgement what would we do?
We would be forced to look
At ourselves emerged in lost time
Assuming what may be
Without judgement
Perception would increase a million times

Distracted by imagination
That experiments with ease
If you could taste it, it might be addictive
Where life will crush those who defy

Take part in a diminishing breed
Where complex turns to simplicity
When pain is acknowledged
Frivolous calculations will be abolished

Without judgement what would we do?
We would be forced to look
At ourselves emerged in lost time
Assuming what may be
Without judgement
Perception would increase a million times

