###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###Welcome To The Family

We're finally alone at last
Oh how I've waited for this day to come
There's just something about you that rubs me wrong
You're not worth my attention
I built this with my own two hands
If you could spare me the time
Stop using me as your next misconception

I don't believe that everything
you've known about me is gone forever
And I won't forget the days
that we spent forever, it haunts me

I don't believe that everything
you've known about me is gone forever
And I won't forget the days
that we spent forever, it haunts me

It won't be long before you meet your end
You're nothing more than a passing trend
So keep those cameras rolling
You think I wouldn't remember?
You thought that I would lose faith in myself
You can spare me the lies
You don't believe in me
Your life's a contradiction

I don't believe that everything
you've known about me is gone forever
And I won't forget the days
that we spent forever, it haunts me

I don't believe that everything
you've known about me is gone forever
And I won't forget the days
that we spent forever, it haunts me

We draw the line at being in your life
Here's to the man of the hour
We'll cast out problems aside
Cheers to your future, may they bury you alive

Move!

I don't believe that everything
you've known about me is gone forever
And I won't forget the days
that we spent forever, it haunts me

I don't believe that everything
you've known about me is gone forever
And I won't forget the days
that we spent forever, it haunts me 

###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###If I Leave

Let's go!
In the beginning I was upfront
Nothing to think about, you'd always hear me out
We made a pact and never gave up, when everything would change we'd always stay the same
Something went wrong along the way, you come around and there's nothing left to say
It's like we're strangers anyway
What more could you ask of me

It's been a long time coming
But everyone's going to hear me out

If I leave bet you'll wish I stayed
Make you regret all the things you said to me
You know that time can't help us now
If I leave this, if I leave this way

I've always been a man of action
Never let anything keep ahold of me
Could always tell when somethings missing
Like I knew everything, except for you and me
I can't make you want to stay
God knows I tried, but this broke under our weight

I still gave it everything, I guess I'll never catch my break

It's been a long time coming
But everyone's going to hear me now

If I leave bet you'll wish I stayed
Make you regret all the things you said to me
You know that time can't help us now
You know that time can't help us now
If I leave I shall move away
And try to right all the wrongs we've ever made
Won't let your problems weigh me down
If I leave this, if I leave this (way)

Never thought you'd be the last one standing
Never thought that we would come this far
You'll always be there looking over my shoulder
I've come to terms with exactly what we are

Never thought you'd be the last one standing
Never thought that we would come this far
You'll always be there looking over my shoulder
I've come to terms with exactly what we are

If I leave bet you'll wish I stayed
Make you regret all the things you said to me
You know that time can't help us now
You know that time can't help us now
If I leave I shall move away
And try to right all the wrongs we ever made
Won't let your problems weigh me down
If I leave this, if I leave this (way)
Never thought I'd be the last one standing
Never thought that we would come this far
You'll always be there looking over my shoulder
When I leave this, when I leave this way 



###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###Life Lessons Learned The Hard Way

Life lessons learned the hard way.

Four people waited in a random white unmarked van.
Parked outside your hotel high rise garage.
To use a tire iron to break the bones inside your legs.
Too bad you never came outside, that's all right,
'Cause in the end you'll get wrecked.
Yeah, in the end, you'll get wrecked.

I heard a little girl killed herself today, that blood's on your hands.
It's on your hands, when everyone knows your face, nothing's safe.
You'll live your life as a fucking target.

You've earned my disgust.
You've earned my disgust.


###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###Same About You

I just felt a wave, an emotion
And right then I knew that everything had changed
A whole side of you that went missing's gone
And all I'd thought of you is wrong

Gotta step away for perspective
Need to take a chance to clear my head
Don't wanna understand your position
Oughta wash my hands of you and run

Think I lost my nerve like I lost you
Held trapped by what we were

No, I'll never feel the same
Same about you, same about you
No, I'll never feel the same
Same about you, same about you

Spent time today reminiscing
Think I learned a lot about who we are
Couldn't diagnose your condition
But now I see the signs you left behind

Think I lost my nerve like I lost you
And the truth remains unheard

No, I'll never feel the same
Same about you, same about you
No, I'll never feel the same
Same about you, same about you

Some roads you can't come back from
When you extract truth from the lie

No, I'll never feel the same
Same about you, same about you
No, I'll never feel the same
Same about you, same about you 

###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###Bullfight

What a waste, I see you now and then,
But mostly we pretend
We're not more strangers than we're friends.
Then we say, what we need to say,
To try and get away
From the tension we create.

Why can't we say the things, the things we wish we would?
Why can't we laugh the way, the way we know we should?
Fall under the weight of all the pressure that's misplaced
Flaws that I embrace

Everybody sees your head's hung low.
They don't ask, they don't wanna know us.
I'll be the one, I'll be your spark,
I'll be your light led through the darkness.
Everybody sees your head's hung low.
They don't ask, they don't wanna know us.
I'll be the one, I'll be your spark,
I'll be your light led through the darkness.

I get
I get
I get so misunderstood

Something changed the way we interact,
Now we can't get it back.
Another relic of the past. (Relic of the past)
Makes ya think, did I ever know you at all?
Follow until I fall
Vultures circling in the sun, the sun, the sun, the sun.

Why can't we say the things, the things we wish we would?
Why can't we laugh the way, the way we know we should?
Fall under the weight of all the pressure that's misplaced
Flaws that I embrace

Everybody sees your head's hung low.
They don't ask, they don't wanna know us.
I'll be the one, I'll be your spark,
I'll be your light led through the darkness.
Everybody sees your head's hung low.
They don't ask, they don't wanna know us.
I'll be the one, I'll be your spark,
I'll be your light led through the darkness.

I get
I get
I get so misunderstood

You can't just avoid the issue,
Ya should have learned from the things we've been through.
You don't know what you have until it's lost,
Till the hammer drops.

Brace, fall. [repeat]

Fall under the weight of all the pressure that's misplaced
Flaws that I embrace

Everybody sees your head's hung low.
They don't ask, they don't wanna know us.
I'll be the one, I'll be your spark,
I'll be your light led through the darkness.
Everybody sees your head's hung low.
They don't ask, they don't wanna know us.
I'll be the one, I'll be your spark,
I'll be your light led through the darkness.

I get
I get
I get so misunderstood


###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###End Of Me

I took some time away
For understanding of what brought us here today
Oh, you'll be the end of me

I'm never happy like we were happy
I'm never sad like we were sad
Oh, you'll be the end of me

You know me all too well
And I can't suppress the memories
You're gone and I can tell
That I've lost more than you'll ever see

Don't say that it's not fair
That you're not the person you wanna be
'Cause Oh, you'll be the end of me

I know I wasn't perfect, but I kept trying
Till I forgot why I stayed
Oh, you'll be the end of me

Yeah we lost all meaning
We lost the magic
So good luck to you on your way
Oh, you'll be the end of me

You know me all too well
And I can't suppress the memories
You're gone and I can tell
That I've lost more than you'll ever see

Don't say that it's not fair
That you're not the person you wanna be
'Cause oh, you'll be the end of me (you'll be the end of me)

I get it, no, I get it
Gave more than I took back, oh well (took back, oh well)
I get it, no, I get it
Can't help those who don't wanna be helped

You know me all too well
And I can't suppress the memories
You're gone and I can tell
That I've lost more than you'll ever see

Don't say that it's not fair
That you're not the person you wanna be
'Cause Oh, you'll be the end of me
You'll be the end of me... 

###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###Best Of Me

What'd you expect from me?
It's not my fault you'll never be happy.
Just cause you're right doesn't mean I'm wrong,
Our days were numbered and we knew it all along.
Can't you let things be?
Now all that's left is misunderstandings.
Spent my nights wishing I was gone.
My dad was right, we will never get along.

So I'm done, cause things could never be the same.
This is the last time, this is the last time you'll ever burden me.

I can't believe you got the best of me.
I can't believe I trusted every word you said.
Stretched myself out way too far,
Now I can see you for who you are.
I can't believe you got the best of me.
I can't believe I trusted every word you said.
It's all finally making sense,
You took what's left of my innocence. Oh no,
I can't believe you got the best of me.

Can't you act your age?
Is it that hard to say what you're thinking?
Lately my life's moving way too fast
You'd drag me down if I'd let you hold me back.
What a mess you've made,
And you hide from it at the bars you frequent.
Blamed myself avoiding time this cost,
But looking back you only learn from what you lost.

So I'm done, cause things could never be the same.
This is the last time, this is the last time you'll ever burden me.

I can't believe you got the best of me.
I can't believe I trusted every word you said.
Stretched myself out way too far,
Now I can see you for who you are.
I can't believe you got the best of me.
I can't believe I trusted every word you said.
It's all finally making sense,
You took what's left of my innocence. Oh no,
I can't believe you got the best of me.
I can't believe you got the best of me.

I will never be the one you want, no I will never be the one you want. (Oh-oh oh-oh)
Finally come to terms that I can't stop, no not this time. (Ye-yeah)
[x2]

I can't believe you got the best of me.
I can't believe I trusted every word you said.
Stretched myself out way too far,
Now I can see you for who you are.
I can't believe you got the best of me.
I can't believe I trusted every word you said.
It's all finally making sense,
You took what's left of my innocence. Oh no,
I can't believe you got the best of me.
I can't believe you got the best of me. 

###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###Better Off This Way

I wonder if you'll notice
If they lock me up and throw away the key
Gotta be open minded
You've got a lot to learn in the ways of me
You've always got to say something
I'm none of your concern but you won't listen at all
You know I'd rather say nothing
And just be proud of myself I'm tearing down these walls.

When you fall I'll be the only one who looks away
When you call I'll be the first to tell you I can't stay
It's all over, I found a better way
To help keep you from me, I'm better off this way

Wo-oh 
Wo-oh 
I'm better off this way
Wo-oh 
Wo-oh 

You gotta keep this coming
Tell me like you know it but you don't know nothing, your call.
We can settle this like gentlemen
Or meet me at the back to end it all and start again.
My whole life's been waiting
Ever since I can remember been anticipating your fall
And God let it be a long one
I can't let go of my life till I know you're done.

When you fall I'll be the only one who looks away
When you call I'll be the first to tell you I can't stay
It's all over, I found a better way
To help keep you from me, I'm better off this way

Wo-oh 
Wo-oh 
I'm better off this way
Wo-oh 
Wo-oh 

You want it, you got it
You've always been such a waste of time
You want it, you got it
A friend of yours is no friend of mine
You want it, you got it
When will you act your age
You want it, you got it
You're the reason things have to change

Wo-oh 
Wo-oh 
You're the reason things have to change
Wo-oh 
Wo-oh 


When you fall I'll be the only one who looks away
When you call I'll be the first to tell you I can't stay
It's all over, I found a better way
To help keep you from me, I'm better off this way

Wo-oh 
Wo-oh 
I'm better off this way
Wo-oh 
Wo-oh 

I'm better off this way 

###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###Homesick

Everything around me seems so much different than where I'm from
And at this rate I think my fate's been sealed
This life's so unpredictable
We'll go continue to live a life that no one knows
Where's this gonna go?

Right here, right now
This is the beginning of the end
And I won't sing one single thing until we can get this right
I'm moving on
I'm moving on

Hey mom, I wrote you some soft songs
And tell dad I'm just fine
We had to choose
We made our moves
And now we got to go, go

Everything about me seemed so much different when I was young
I couldn't wait to take my place
Five years have passed
Good god have I been gone?
So why, I've never felt so alone in my whole life
Times not on my side

Right here, right now
This is the beginning of the end
And I won't sing a single thing until we can get this right
I'm moving on
I'm moving on

Hey mom, I wrote you some soft songs
And tell dad I'm just fine
We had to choose
We made our moves
And now we got to go

And why's this make me so nervous?
Why does everything go wrong?
Why's this make me so nervous?
Why does everything go wrong?

I'm holding on to a fairytale
We're moving forward but we're not there yet
I'm holding on to a fairytale
We're moving forward
we're moving forward

I'm holding on to a fairytale
We're moving forward but we're not there yet
I'm holding on to a fairytale
We're moving forward, we're moving forward

Hey mom, I wrote you some soft songs
And tell dad I'm just fine
We had to choose
We made our moves
And now we got to go

And why's this make me so nervous?
(You make me so, you make me so)
Why does everything go wrong?
Why's this make me so nervous?
(You make me so, you make me so)
Why does everything go wrong? 

###A DAY TO REMEMBER
###Fast Forward To 2012

We welcome you to the second chapter
thanks for turning the other page
We acknowledge you as the only reason
for the progress that we've made
You're a constant reminder
we came, we saw, we conquered
Everything has come so far
From where we were before
Well keep this short and sweet so I'll
get to the point

My friends come first it's the bottom line
My friends come first it's the bottom line
My friends come first it's the bottom line
My friends come first it's the bottom line

That's the bottom line
Here's to the future, never getting older
when the tables do turn, where will you be?

Pick up your feet.

###REMY ZERO
###Life In Rain

I once had marigolds for eyes.
That seem to fade on sunny days.
When it's cold as the rain outside,
well then, so am I.

So when it comes down,
you'll know I'm with you.
And how could I show you?
It feels good to know.
It feels good to know you.

We once had oceans left to fly,
now the trees and the river
have parted ways.
When it seems like the fun has died,
well then, so have I.

So when it comes down,
you'll know I'm with you.
And how could I show you?
It feels good to know.
It feels good to know you.

And how will you know?
We storm from a small, thin line.
We're torn from the old frames.
There's no one here to pull you back again..

So when it comes down, you'll know.
Mmmmm, you'll know.

Helena? pulled to the ground.
(how do I show you?)
Should've known
soon she would come down.
Words were the first thing to go,
(it feels good to know)
the lie they would never show,

Helena...
(and how will you move?)
Helena...
(and how did I show you?)
Helena...
(I couldn't show you)
Helena...

It feels good to know.
It feels good to know you.
It feels good to know you.

###REMY ZERO
###Perfect Memory

Remember how they always seemed to know
We had the forest in our eyes but the earth was in our clothes
They thought we'd fall
Not at all

So look back on your treasured days
When we were young in a world that was so tired
Though it's not what we wanted before
Even the saints had to crawl from the floor

Summers when the money was gone you'd sing
All your little songs that meant everything to me

And I'll remember you
And the things that we used to do
And the things that we used to say
I'll remember you
That way

Remember how they tried to hold you down
And we climbed those towers and looked out upon our town
And everything you hoped would last
It just always becomes your past
It hurts

But summer's when the money was gone you'd sing
All your little songs that meant everything to me

And I'll remember you
And the things that we used to do
And the things that we used to say
I'll remember you
Always

But then how this world slipped through my fingers
And even the sun seemed tired
I still cared
As they lowered you down my heart just jaded
In that moment the earth made no sound
But you were there
You helped me lift my pain into the air

I still miss you
God I still miss you
I know that you are waiting there
I always thought that you'd come home

And I'll remember you
And the things that we used to do
And the things that we used to say

If it don't hurt you it won't hurt me
If it don't hurt me it won't hurt you
If it don't hurt you it won't hurt me that way 

###REMY ZERO
###Impossibility

As the earth swung
This golden hum
Seemed to wash over me
As the bells ringed
I heard you sing
And it called me out
To sea

You said how did you know
That fine living makes you slow
How could you know I was the one
And how could you see
Impossibility
As far as you know
I am your sun

See I woke up frail and perfect
See I woke up tired and warm
As the old man stands to judge us all
I believe I am reborn

You said how could we know
Fine living makes you slow
How could I know you were the one
I said how could you see
Impossibility
As far as I know I am your sun

I swore
Forever more
I would stand up
Bright and clear
As we rise above our
Doubts and fears
Singing out so all may hear 

###REMY ZERO
###'Til The End

I always thought that we'd carry on 'til the end
And I'd always be your friend
But I should've known, lonely as I was back then
That I'd never see you again

How could you walk away?
Leave it all damaged, torn, afraid
Well just go away
And it's okay

And I guess it's true that all that you give is returned
For all that you've burnt, you'll burn
And now that you are hoping that they'll let you in
Just tell them it's your best friend

And how could it walk away?
Leave you there damaged, torn, and afraid
There's nothing here
And there's nothing left to say

I think of the times you said you'd never go
Think of the words when you said so

And I always thought that we'd carry on 'til the end
And you'd always be my friend


###REMY ZERO
###Over The Rails & Hollywood High

Television
Is the condition of my connection
To the machine
And in its warm glow
We watched the flames grow
Till the bones show
Till it stripped you clean

Well I had it bad
We were barely on the screen
With the trips I had
Swallowed everything
Except for you

Now the last great hollywood high
Stole right over the rails
And I'm
The last great hollywood high
After it shows who knows
Where it will go?

Halloween dust
Came between us
It always seemed just in the way
Its the decision
Your script revision
All the stars evolve
But the story's the same

Well I had it bad
You were barely on the screen
With the trips I had
Swallowed everything
Except for you

Well I've had it bad
I was barely on the screen
With the trips I had
Swallowed everything
Well I had it bad
Except for you

###REMY ZERO
###Glorious #1

All alone in the traffic
All sense of the game is long gone
Mouth twisted up and lips like coal
Tired of spinning you get anything you want

We don't have to be lovers
We don't have to be friends for no one
Black souls in the desert
Heads spinning you get anything you want

I'm back down to the glorious #1
My prints all over the smoking gun
Back down to the glorious #1
All lines to the living are now undone
Back down to the glorious #1

Her fingers felt like a fire
Her skin's shifting
The words are so clear
Left a burning desire
One flash will get you anything you want


###REMY ZERO
###Gramarye

(Here they come, here they come
Here they come and they might as well
Too many birds in my confusion now
Now they'll circle over this house till we take them in)

You show me a sign to rise up from the world we know
And she's strung out on life
He soon rolls his teeth
Spilling out from a mouth fit to overflow
Back into me

She moves and it's fire
fire underwater
Speaks of its flame
she speaks my name
Well they all really want you
If only you had wanted them
Lights move in the chalk lines
Chains that define who I am
Here we are again
how could I have seen?
Always she's driving
how could I have known?
Right through the strangest calling
I should have known
Straight through the sound
gramarye, I've found
See how she's driving me down

Straight from the sound
She's seen as a bright sun to anyone
Hollow and mined
With the weight of the world
Trailing out till the last train
Discovers me
Alive on Vine

She moves and it's fire
fire underwater
Speaks of its flame
she speaks my name
As you move in a chalk line
Change in the dream that I am
Here we are the same

I used to see something in the idea
But only once did my hands reach
Anything beautiful
Now she's turned away
And I...

We move in it's fire
show me a sign
fire underwater
Speaking its flame
it speaks my name
She proves
soon roll its teeth
the liar
On every one of them
we are the same
Lights move in a chalk line
Change in the fire who I am
Here we are again
How could I have seen?
always she's driving
How could I have known?
right through the strangest calling
Straight through the sound,
Gramarye, I have found,
See how she's driving me
Always she's driving
Back through the strangest calling
Straight through the sound
Gramarye, I found
See how she's driving me down 

###REMY ZERO
###Hermes Bird

Your sad songs rain in heaven
Here's a call for you
So don't let it fall into your
Frail dreams of horror
Life, lies, and shattered blows
Calling out you're famous

So hold to your permanent bliss
In the time that it takes to exist
From the hours to the fall of it
It's all right
You're all wrong

And it's a dangerous thing to ignore
It's so easy when the world has it's way
Well, then you're gone
Life, limbs, and shattered blows
Crawling out you're famous

So hold to your permanent bliss
When you barely know that you exist
From the hours to the fall of it
All right

Alright, I never said
to just cast them out
Leave it till the morning
Then you're gone.
So long
Cast them out
Now you're alive

So hold to your permanent bliss
In the time that it takes to exist
From the hours to the fall of it
It's all right
You're all wrong

It's so, it's so easy 

###REMY ZERO
###Shadowcasting

Run for our home.
You lie tired and faded
by the old engine light.

So long.

I think it's over now.
As a song tomorrow,
I sat in hollow sounds.

And all I said is fading slow,
and no one cares.
To rain I've known
to overflow.
No one ever believes.
It's all decieved.

Run. You know I'm left for fire.
Just start a new rising sun.
But, you know I'm all right.

I'll never call you back.

So look out your window
as the sun comes down.

And all I've said is fading slow,
and no one cares.
To rain I've known, it's
never happened before.
No one cares.

No one ever leaves.
It's all the same. 

###REMY ZERO
###Temenos (Here Comes The Shakes)

Downed in the room
where I live,
scored some broken glass.
Breaking up, losing force.

Hold my fingers up to the lightwell,
and the light is strange,
but I'm alright.
It's strange, but it's all right.

It is the tri-coloured fields
and my dream.
And all the people lean
to the sun all the time.
I saw you there.

My eye plays
camera tricks again.
The shutter clicks,
camera tricks.

I fade, I fade.

Doot doot doo doot doot...
Doot doot doo doot doot...

I tried to find something.
Well, I only found nothing.
There go the roof, here come the sky.
Let in the sun, here come the shakes.

Here come the shakes! 


###PHOENIX
###Lasso

Where would you go
Not long ago
I’ve been thinking out loud
Was it suddenly?
Do-do-don’t you know?
Don’t do it
What you do
Oh what you do to me

Forever is a long long time
When you lost your way
Trying to follow your ideal
Oh sorry but your so-called life
It is such a waste

Wear your real eyes
No you don’t realize
What you say yes to
But you say yes too

Where would you go
Where would you go
With a lasso?
Could you run into
Could you run into
Could you go and run into me?

Where would you go
Where would you go
Tied up to a lasso?
Could you run into
Could you run into
Could you go and run into me?

So lonely so pretty such a lack of diplomacy
You can’t get out
Do-don’t you know don’t do it
What you do well you should do to me

Far-out so far-out
Such a fall-out
Not only that you're lonely
Doesn't matter if you're not so well
No you're not so well

Where would you go
Where would you go
With a lasso?
Could you run into
Could you run into
Could you go and run into me?

Forever is a long long time
When you've lost your way
Forever is a long long time
When you've lost your way 


###PHOENIX
###Second To None

Second to none, I wouldn't seriously get involved in a thing
Bored of all the talking, you know it didn't change much
I doubt your intentions are to make me feel any better today
I even doubt tomorrow will be as easy as it was

I've changed
you've changed
it's not the same
Tell me what 's the difference if I go back to normal again?
Right away

I should have known I'd look at you
with opened eyes the morning after
Did you cut your hair? Did you change anything these days?
I heard a "liar" then I heard a laughter 20 calls a day it makes no difference at all

Last year
Last call
You lost your ways
Tell me what's the difference if I go back to normal again?
Right away

I thought I heard a lie
I thought I heard a "liar"

I doubt your intentions are to make me feel any better today
I even doubt tomorrow will be as easy as it was I've changed
You've changed
It's not the same
Tell me what's the difference if I go back to normal again?
Right away

I thought I heard a lie
I thought I heard a "liar" 


###PHOENIX
###Lost And Found

So you've got your own little story to tell
Some girls they ask to put them on your knees
Slowdown, it's hard enough to get along
Slowdown, we'll never ever get along
That ain't what you had in mind
No that ain't what you had in mind
You don't know what you're doing

Let go
It's so hard to fill me in
You'd better run as fast as you can
When your eyes are getting low
Tomorrow'll say if you're lost and found

Walking around thinking the same again
To get to you I'll go down on my knees
Last night I swear it wouldn't be the same
Last night I swear it never was the same
Two is for a while but then one has got to leave
That's it! I ain't lying and I won't ask you please
I'll tell you what I have in mind

Let go
It's so hard to fill me in
You'd better run as fast as you can
When your eyes are getting low
Tomorrow'll say if you're lost and found

I'll tell you what I have in mind
It's so hard to fill me in
You'd better run as fast as you can 

###PHOENIX
###Consolation Prizes

It started all in early September
When my godgiven little became a lot older
Goodbyes seal my broken heart
Hold on to your teardrops, you got a long way to go

Did you get older doing nothing today?
Don't you wanna stop complaining?
If one is easy then hard is two
No one knows where you're heading to
Once my private collection, always betting on you

No consolation prizes
Spit out your lies and chewing gum
Cut off your hair—yeah that's it!
If you look like that I swear I'm gonna love you more

I thought about this for a long time
Never had the chance to try and make it better
My heart is waiting for a new you
And there's no other option on the schedule

Love like ours should never die with years
Once you start you can't ever go backwards
'Cause if dark is one then bright is two
No one knows where we're heading to
No matter what it takes, never give up on you

I want you to change it all
I am gonna make it better

No consolation prizes
Spit out your lies and chewing gum
Cut off your hair—yeah that's it!
If you look like that I swear I'm gonna love you more

No consolation prizes
Spit out your lies and chewing gum
Cut off your hair—yeah that's it!
If you look like that I swear I'm gonna love you more

More more more... 

###PHOENIX
###Alphabetical

Everybody says
i'm a lonesome kind of guy
i've been defeated by them all
if they can find me
i'm done

Everybody knows
that it really doesn't matter at all
all the good things that i've done
i'm up against the wall
how come
my file has been deleted

if this is what they want
i can tell you
that the order's alphabetical
don't you get it
sooner or later
i'll be recruited by someone

Everybody knows that it really doesn't matter at all
everybody says
i shouldn't mess with you no more
if you see me on my own
drive on

if i were dismissed
i wouldv'e gotten much more
if i wasn't that kind
i wouldn't care at all
sooner or later, sooner or later
sooner or later
i'll change my whole perspective

if this is what they want
i can tell you
that the order's alphabetical
don't you get it
sooner or later
i'll be recruited by someone

isn't it better
sooner or later, sooner or later
sooner or later
i'll change my whole perspective
i'll be recruited by someone


###PHOENIX
###Victim Of The Crime

Come, Come
Dropping off the radar
Come, come
Dropping off the radar

Lost illusions
Try the best that you can do
You might get another chance
Burn my leather coat
I need to change my suit
You don't listen to a single word i say

Lies+ hidden codes= what they do
and you're the victim of the crime

Come, Come
Dropping off the radar
Come, come
Dropping off the radar

Lately I'm not expecting you
Please forgive me
For stuff I didn't do
I sure was gonna...

Come, Come
Dropping off the radar
Come, come
Dropping off the radar

There're too many fingers
On the trigger
Guess how to play this game
Before you lose it
Theres nothing I can do about it

You're starting to fall...
Fall in a deeper state...
Watch out 

###PHOENIX
###Run Run Run

Business calls me
Trouble down the waterfront
You know, I tried to
But now i'm running outta lies
It's a clear view
When all you are is gettin' paid
No more favors
I know what we can do about it

I think I'd better run, run, run, run
I think I'd better run, run, run, run
You didn't catch me fallin'
Fallin' fallin' fallin' fallin'
Fallin' fallin' fallin'

Contradictions
Get me everything i want
I'll let you know
But i think it's gonna take a while
It's a clear view
No one's waiting at the door
A million letters
They couldn't make me change my mind

I think I'd better run, run, run, run
I think I'd better run, run, run, run
You didn't catch me fallin'
Fallin' fallin' fallin' fallin'
Fallin' fallin' fallin'

How you want it to be
Sittin' by the waterfront
I should be drifting
Far enough to reach the shore
It's a clear view
Don't you underestimate me
No more flavors
I know I can live without it

I think I'd better run, run, run, run
I think I'd better run, run, run, run
You didn't catch me fallin'
Fallin' fallin' fallin' fallin'
Fallin' fallin' fallin'
(If you got to play the game
you got got to do it well)

I think i'd better run, run, run, run
And leave those things for someone else
But i like it
I don't even care
If you got to play the game
You got to do it well 

###PHOENIX
###Funky Squaredance

Hopeful days and stormy nights
I ain't got much to win, not much to lose
Under the burden of my loneliness
It feels so hard to win, so hard to lose
I won't enjoy my collection of stamps
When I'm six feet under the ground

Lonely streets and dusty roads
Lord it's a long way to go back home
Under the burden of your heart of stone
You shrug your shoulders as I decompose
Please keep a eye on those red haired boys
Someday they'll play drum with my shinbones

Now your chewing-gum on my coffin
Take me where I long to be

I can't believe that you want me to wear
The evening tails that will fit my corpse
I don't need a tuxedo
There's no bouncer in the after world
I only just left my dying bed and
Your making curtains out of my shroud

Don't you dig my grave with some excavator
Use a blood stained sword and a snow-white horse, please

A last ride in the city's hearse
Few miles away from heaven above
A few more minutes 'till they bury me
A few more weeks 'till worms lick my bones
I won't enjoy my collection of stamps
Now I'm five feet under the ground

Stormy days and lonely nights
Lord it's a long way to go back home

All the boys raise your hands up in the air (yeah)
Now all the girls raise your hands up in the air (yeah)
Everybody one more time (yeah)
Let's all have a real good time together
One, two, three, let's go

Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance

Tonight's the night girls, yeah
Come on, let's get all antsy

Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance

Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance

Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance

You seem so glad my place is free
Now you're dancing on my grave
What a cruel way to treat a friend

Live my life in dignity
Well I must confess
Looking for a place

Everybody has to demonstrate
And everybody has to see you wait
Thinking of a real way to see

What matters is the love that you give
Remember all the thing that you've seen
Does another go and never seen

Nothing in my forgotten years
Life got a little serious
Give me real self-esteem

It's buried in my P-A-S-T
Give a lot, a whole lot recieved
Heaven-sent T.N.T.

Uh, can't go further, losing

I cant go losing my mind
Remember all the game have I tried
Buried in my P-A-S-T

We call love late at day
Late at night I dropped in hate
Dropping in a heaven fantasy

Heaven knows what I'm gonna do
Living in a lonesome avenue
Done in the P-A-S-T

Go without the love I receive
K-A-R-I-E E-L-E-I-S-O-N
Mmm, everybody, has got to demonstrate

Everybody has a T-I-U
He has things you'd never do
Thinking in a real avenue

What matters is the love that you give

Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance
Funky squaredance, funky squaredance, funky squaredance 

###PHOENIX
###Party Time

Summertime is gone
And I don't wanna lose you
I don't wanna see you any more
Forget about the sun
I want my city
I want what's pretty too
Party time Party time
Party time Party time
Take me to the place
That makes me happy
I think I'm ready too
Don'tcha know my name
I knew it yesterday
We don't have much to say
Party time Party time
Party time Party time
Summertime is gone
And I don't wanna lose you
I don't wanna see you any more
Forget about the sun
I want my city
I want what's pretty, too
Party time Party time
Party time Party time


###PHOENIX
###Too Young

Baby when I saw you turning at the end of the street
I knew a time was gone and it took me like ages
Just to understand that I was afraid to be a simple guy
I tried my best to smile but deep inside my heart
I felt it was shouting like a crowd dancing
I guess I couldn't live without the things that made my life what it is

Can't you hear it calling oh yeah
Everybody's dancin' oh yeah
Tonight everything is over
I feel too young

I can't lie on my bed without thinking I was wrong
But when this feeling calls this world becomes another
Nighttime won't hold me in your arms again
I got a very good friend who says he can't believe the love I give
Is not enough to end your fears
I guess I couldn't live without the things that made my life what it is

Can't you hear it calling oh yeah
Everybody's shakin' oh yeah
Tonight everything is over
I feel too young

Oh rainfalls and hard times coming they won't leave me tonight
I wish I knew what I was doing
Just do let this spirit survive
Everybody's dancing oh yeah
I guess I couldn't live without the things that made my life what it is

Can't you hear it calling oh yeah
Everybody's dancing oh yeah
Tonight everything is over
I feel too young


###MASTODON 
###Crack The Skye

Blessed visionary cut me with your sun
The rivers ran in blood
Spark fueled to fire

Deep withing the endless void
Searching for a sign
The vessel forged inside me
Watches over like the death
Of the moon

Strike the shepherd
Sheep will scatter
Mountains of despair
I can see the pain
It is written all over your face

The screaming arrows tear through my soul
In the dawn your face is haunting
White ghostly dreams

Weight of worlds is on your shoulders
Hear the voice of gold
I can see the pain
It's written all over your face

Desperate heathens flock to sirens
Guard your heartache well
Momma don't let them take her
Take her down

Please tell Lucifer he can't have this one
Her spirits too strong
It's written all over your face
I can see the pain
You can make it all go away 


###MASTODON 
###Divinations

It's gone away
It's gone away
It's gone for good
Animal spirits come calling me home
Through the tunnels of brilliant light
The magnet of wisdom is pulling
Burrowing faster the fabric of time

No escape
Binding spirits
No escape
Trapped in time space

Rapid descendants
The wormhole is empty
The center of Khlysty surrounds me
The fire is dancing in a silvery sheet of breath
Black robe
Necromancing
Summon the soul of the spectre

No escape
Binding spirits
No escape
Trapped in time space

Fire in the eye
Realm of mystic majesty

No escape
Binding spirits
No escape
Trapped in time space

Fire in the eye
Realm of mystic majesty 


###MASTODON 
###Slick Leg

Slickleg!
Praise mammoth
I lie trapped in ice
Bright cold shield my eyes
White cruel stone
Can't move
Hide so far from truth
Blood floweth
Crawl into unknown
Does time heal all wounds
Why's this been so long
Line of descent gone
Reign down
Reign down  

###MASTODON 
###We Built This Come Death

Now you see all this time
Work nine to five
Monday through Friday I'm singing
I sing the blues for you
Now I'm standing in the pouring rain
My feet are cold but I cant complain
And I wonder how you have been
I need you love I miss you so
I know it's right but it's always strange
How I scream
All this life's worth all the while
Heartache and slave driving pain
I sing the blues for you
Now I'm standing in the pouring rain
My feet are cold but I can't complain
And I wonder how you have been
I need you love I miss you so
I know it's right but it's always strange
 

###MASTODON 
###Pendulous Skin

Yeah
Float away

Known so low
You run away
Desolate us
Desolate all

No love is lost
You know we're weightless
Climb
Under my wing
Climb

Known so low
You run away
Desolate us
Desolate all

No love is lost
You know we're weightless
Climb
Under my wing
Climb

Known so low
You run away
Desolate us
Desolate all

Grown so slow
You run away
Desolate us
I'm sailing away  

###MASTODON 
###Colony Of Birchmen

This forest is growing faster than I can tell
Cell structure eats away at a massive swell
Seems however I'm a victim of circumstance
Hunt for ogres and dwarfs
Lion slicer
Run with death
Run with death
White faces coming closer with every step
Earth envelopes taking breath without happenstance
Carve my teeth out ripping through the sheep's head curse
Hunter gatherer
Ridden from the cave
Run with death
Run with death
Gone away
My heart's gone away
Taking everything
My heart's gone away
Take it now
Hunt for ogres and dwarfs
Lion slicer
Run with death
Run with death
Gone away
My heart's gone away
Taking everything
My heart's gone away
Take it now
 

###MASTODON 
###Megalodon

Myth or legend
Nymph tale washed ashore
Near the kraken sleepeth stirs coral and bone
Infinite city
No sexy sneer
Hideous creation
Human and animal
Banter songs of rudeness to be adhered
Not on rocks that glisten
Harps to listen
Comb hair
Tear right to pieces
Left to recess a watery grave
Sensing the blood of prey
Swimming in fear for life
Rolling over
Falling into jaws
Teeth that chatter
It distracts them all
The Fiji mermaid
She will let it know
Time is coming to feed and knaw  

###MASTODON 
###Blood & Thunder

I think that someone is trying to kill me
Infecting my blood and destroying my mind
No man of the flesh could ever stop me
The fight for this fish is a fight to the death

White whale - holy grail

What remorseless emperor commands me
I no longer govern my soul
I am completely immersed in darkness
As I turn my body away from the sun

White whale - holy grail

Split your lungs with blood and thunder
When you see the white whale
Break your backs and crack your oars men
If you wish to prevail

This ivory leg is what propels me
Harpoons thrust in the sky
Aim directly for his crooked brow
And look him straight in the eye

White whale - holy grail  

###MASTODON 
###Trainwreck

Life's changed
yet remain the same
basking in an afterglow
i did not know
i am here
in shadows island

lying
hopeless wondering
all questions exhaust me

running screaming chanting
for all this land I've seen its worth
helping all for times sake
it brings me work
pinned to this world  

###MASTODON 
###Crusher Destroyer

Lesson
the honoring instinct of animal
pressure
no blame on the red bull
throw fury at him

aim gorge and win

less contenders on the way today
let them pay
nothing lost
nothing gained

listen
here lies the warning for matador
blackout
blood running the dirt floor
won't bleed by accident

burn your game plan
 
###Killing JOKE
###Land Of Milk And Honey"

Land of - better change your tune now
Milk and - oh so negative
Honey - and we're so content now
Land of - Land of Milk and Honey

And you never even know when it's standing right before you
'Cos always watching the detective film about
How it's not on 93rd Street always misses golden opportunities

Land of - better change your tune now
Milk and - oh so negative
Honey - and we're so content now
Land of - Land of Milk and Honey

One up three to go, all the hidden motives
Like daytime airplay - hah - cocktail Saturday
And the silver disc upon the wall means success
So they tell me

Land of - better change your tune now
Milk and - oh so negative
Honey - and we're so content now
Land of - Land of Milk and Honey

Change the tune now, sales go dwindle
Change the subject next new single
Change the tune now, sales go dwindle
Change the subject next new single

Land of Milk and Honey
Land of - Milk and Honey
Land of. 

###Killing JOKE
###Harlequin

I am a child of folly
Now I want my way
And I don't know good or bad
But I dance all day
And my sense of humour
Getting out of hand la-la
And the diamond's sharp you know
All the harlequins they go go

Such a lovely colour
So the nasty taste won't show
And when I'm seeing bitter
Then the carnal feelings go
So if you guess my next move
Then that's more than me
So when I start to smile
Then the harlequins will go go

I am a child of folly
Now I want some fun
So I don't need good or bad
And we've just begun
Ao if you guess our next move
Let your sense of humour show
And the diamonds are forever
All the harlequins will go go 

###Killing JOKE
###Chapter III

Attack behind attack
A war behind a war
Wise thoughts to broad horizons
A nation, the very least
Such simplicity, advance to find myself
He didn't see such simplicity

Hope is for the loser
Certainty to be
Pleasure of the winner
Certainty to be
Take now or stay the same!

Attack behind attack
A war behind a war
Wise thoughts to broad horizons
A nation, the very least
Such simplicity, advance to find myself
He didn't see such simplicity

Hope is for the loser
Certainty to be
Pleasure of the winner
Certainty to be
Take now or stay the same!


###Killing JOKE
###We Have Joy

Idle toying, worship the whore,
Forbidden was bidden,
kiss turned to gnaw
Indolent minds, broken rules
The grey land is falling,
Laugh at the fools
We have Joy - We have Joy!

We was drunk, intoxicate
No time for doubt, no time, no late
I saw the laughing one - this was the West
he said "take your spear and puncture the flesh"
We have Joy! - We have Joy!

We was drunk, intoxicate
No time for doubt, no time, no late
Brandish the weapon, Sound out the din
We feeling red now - time to move in
We have Joy - We have Joy!




###Killing JOKE
###The Hum

Slowly, slowly all fall down
A blindfold dance and a 1,2,3
No mistake where they always emphasize security
Draw the curtains, shut the door, the heater's on
I couldn't ask for more
I pull the sheets right overhead
Snuggle, snuggle safe in bed

Take the weight right off my shoulder
Misery claims much too late
Bow the head or grip the sabre
Vermichten regenerate
Bright eyed young inherit all
Treading down upon the fallen
They was drawn towards the Hum
Plenty more where they come from.

Slowly, slowly all fall down
A blindfold dance and a 1,2,3
Swarm upset the gentle lamb
A hive don't hold no humble bee!
Slowly, slowly, out it came,
Tendencies that weren't the same
And they were drawn towards the Hum
Plenty more where We come from. 

###Killing JOKE
###Who Told You How?

Who told you how?
Who told you how? 

###Killing JOKE
###Butcher

Watching the decoys of all description
Sparkle of colour creating diversion
The liars are out - they have all the assets
Crawling for oil they were bleeding for gold
Fruit tasting bitter and lead in the air
Butcher the womb and expect her to bear

Forests are falling there's smoke in my throat
Machine over man and the mass over mind
Re-assurance from face on my screen
Appointment with destiny for those who will run
Out of the virus immunity comes
Out of the virus immunity comes

Watching the decoys of all description
Sparkle of colour creating diversion
The liars are out they have all the assets
Crawling for oil they were bleeding for gold
Fruit tasting bitter and the lead in the air
Butcher the womb and expect her to bear 

###Killing JOKE
###The Fall Of Because

Look at the faces
Whose is the meaning
Forget the passion
Feeding the dead
The fall of because

Look at the faces
It's cold outside
You're on your own
Staying indifferent
The fall of because

It's cold outside
Losing my fear
No more passion
Passion is fed
Because
The fall of because 

###Killing JOKE
###Primitive

Primitive feeling
Primitive way
Getting closer
To the primitive day
Intuition
Wherever it goes
The primitive day
The primitive way

Primitive feeling
Primitive way
Getting closer
To the primitive day
Follow the feeling
Wherever it goes
The primitive day
The primitive way

###Killing JOKE
###The Wait

Motives changing
Day to day
The fire increases
Mass decay
I look at the river
White foam floats down
The bodies poisoned
Gotta sit tight

The wait

After awakening
The silence grows
Screams subside
Distortion shows
Mutant thought
Of bad mouthed news
It's just another birth
Of distorted views

The wait


###Killing JOKE
###Requiem"

Man watching video
The heart keeps on ticking.
He doesn't know why
He's just cattle for slaughter.
The requiem
The requiem
The requieeeeeeeeeeeeeeeem
When the meaningful words
When they cease to function
When there's nothing to say
When will they start plotting against you
The requiem
The requiem
The requieeeeeeeeeeeeeem
Only a hint of religion
Uncensored truths for the novelty.
the sound of breaking glass
this is a reflection
The requiem
The requiem
The requiem
The


###HOLE
###Forming / Hot Chocolate Boy

He's always waiting
Gotta make the move to tell her
Hot chocolate boy
He's never met one
Hot chocolate wet one
Hot chocolate boy
Deep, sweet, and bitter
Spoon out a place for breakfast
Hot chocolate boy
Hot, frosty, creamy
He was only dreaming...

Hold me down, hold me up
Tell them that I'm your gun
Pull my trigger
I'm bigger than
I'm bigger than you
Tell them what it means to be on top
Pull them down, hold me up
Tell them that I'm your gun
Pull my trigger, I'm bigger than
I'm bigger than, I'm bigger than...



###HOLE
###Pale Blue Eyes

This is an original new-waver...

Some...
Sometimes I get so sad
Sometimes I feel almost heavenly but
Baby, I mostly feel mad
Yeah, lately I just feel bad
Linger on your pale blue eyes
Linger on your pale blue eyes

It was good what we did yesterday
And I'd do it again
The fact that you're insane
Only proves that you're my best friend
Well, I will never fuck anyone else again
Linger on your pale blue eyes
Linger on your pale blue eyes

Thought of you as my mountain top
I thought of you as my peak
Thought of you as everything that I had and I couldn't keep
Yeah, that I had and I couldn't keep
Linger on your pale blue eyes
Linger on your pale blue eyes

Yeah, you explode inside of me
Yeah, you explode my heart
I never had nothing anywhere
So the end is where I start
'Cause I'm real and that's all that matters
Linger on your pale blue eyes
Linger on your pale blue eyes



###HOLE
###I Think That I Would Die

He's stupid
I'm smarting
He's stupid
I'm smarting

I want my baby
Where is the baby?
I want my baby
Who took my baby?

Rose white, rose red
Rose up in my head
Rose white, rose red

Yeah yeah
I want some
Yeah yeah
There is none

I want my baby
Where is the baby?
I want my baby
There is a baby

There is no milk!
There is no milk!
There is no milk!
There is no milk!

Rose white, rose red
Rose up in my head
Rose white, rose red

She lost all her innocence
Gave it to an abscess
She lost all her innocence
She said, "I am not a feminist"

It's not yours - fuck you!

There is no milk!
There is no milk!
There is no milk!
There is no milk!
There is no milk!



###HOLE
###Credit In The Straight World

And I will await your highness
I'm so high I cannot walk
And I will await
You cripple, you take away my time
My peace, my empathy
No babies sleep on atrophy
Your unborn love and fetal stress
Hard bitter candy, legless caress

Go for credit in the straight world
Look a dealer in the eye
Go for credit in the real world
Won't you try?

I got some credit in the straight world
I lost a leg, I lost an eye
Go for credit in the real world
You will die
Yeah

It's the credit in the straight world
Leave your money when you die
Lots of credit in the real world
Gets you high
Yeah

I got some credit in the straight world
I lost a leg, I lost an eye
Go for credit in the real world
You will die
Yeah



###HOLE
###Asking For It

Every time that I sell myself to you
I feel a little bit cheaper than I need to
I will tear the petals off of you
Rose red, I will make you tell the truth

Was she asking for it?
Was she asking nice?
If she was asking for it
Did she ask you twice?

Every time that I stare into the sun
Angel dust and my dress just comes undone
Every time that I stare into the sun
Be a model or just look like one
Wild eye rot gut do me in
Do you think you can make me do it again?

Was she asking for it?
Was she asking nice?
If she was asking for it
Did she ask you twice?

If you live through this with me
I swear that I would die for you
And if you live through this with me
I swear that I would die for you

Was she asking for it?
Was she asking nice?
If she was asking for it
Did she ask you twice?

Was she asking for it?
Was she asking nice?
If she was asking for it
Did she ask you twice?



###HOLE
###Violet

And the sky was made of amethyst
And all the stars look just like little fish
You should learn when to go
You should learn how to say no

Might last a day, yeah
Mine is forever
Might last a day, yeah
Mine is forever

When they get what they want, they never want it again
When they get what they want, they never want it again

Go on, take everything, take everything, I want you to
Go on, take everything, take everything, I want you to

And the sky was all violet
I wanna give the violet more violence
Hey, I'm the one with no soul
One above and one below

Might last a day, yeah
Mine is forever
Might last a day, yeah
Mine is forever

When they get what they want, they never want it again
When they get what they want, they never want it again

Go on, take everything, take everything, I want you to
Go on, take everything, take everything, I dare you to

I told you from the start just how this would end
When I get what I want then I never want it again

Go on, take everything, take everything, I want you to
Go on, take everything, take everything, I want you to
Go on, take everything, take everything, I want you to
Go on, take everything, take everything, I want you to
Go on, take everything, take everything, I want you to
Go on, take everything, take everything, take everything, take everything



###HOLE
###Clouds

Bad boy

Rows and flows of angel hair
And ice cream castles in the air
And feather canyons everywhere
I've looked at clouds that way

Moons and Junes and Ferris wheels
The dizzy dancing way you feel
As every fairy tale comes real
I've looked at clouds that way

But now they only block the sun
They rain and snow on everyone
So so many things I could've done
But clouds

Angel dust gets in your eyes, your hair
On acid stars you're getting there
My body's assembled into
A little itty-bitty gift to you
When you die, I've looked at life that way

But now it's just another show
You leave 'em laughing when you go
So, so don't let them inside, don't let them know
Don't give yourself ohh away

But now my friends are acting strange
They shake their heads man, they say I've changed, well
Well, something's lost, rearranged
From living every, every, every, I've

I've looked at clouds from both sides now
From up and down, and still somehow
It's just illusions I recall

I really don't know, I really don't know
I really don't know, I really don't know
I really don't, I really don't clouds at all
Why are we here...terrified, terrified, wow



###HOLE
###Loaded

Black lung coat and your little crown
That's the crown that you get for falling down
Hey baby, let me look in your eyes
I see you standing in a weird red light
The pump and grind that I call my head
The suck milk nebula I use instead
The sweet cream clot and the sweet cream udder
The weird red light that pulls you under

Open my scar, let out my stars
Slut me open and suck my scars

And now I'm loaded
Yeah, now I'm loaded

Put on your coat and your little crown
That's the crown that you get when you fall down
Hey baby, won't you wave goodbye
As you go off to fuck your weird red light?
Rotten sun spits on your raw hide
As you dance to the sound of a suicide
Oh yeah, you laugh as you try to to hide
That you're the rat poison daughter of a suicide

Slut me open and suck my scars
Better open your eyes when I come down

And now I'm loaded
Yeah, now I'm loaded

Don't blush when I rip you open
Don't blush when I rip you open
Hey baby, let me look in your eyes
As you go off into your weird red light
The pump and grind that I call my head
The suck milk nebula I use instead
The sweet cream clot and the sick milk udder
The weird red light that pulls me under

You open and suck my scars
Better open your eyes when I come down

And now I'm loaded
I just get loaded
I just get loaded
I just get loaded
And now I'm loaded
So am I, So am I
And I, I just got, I just got I just get, I just get, I just get loaded
I just get loaded



###HOLE
###Sassy

We're rolling, you guys
Why?
Why?
Why?
Why?
Why?
Why?
Why am I here?
Why am I there?
I don't care
CARE!
Oh, why I'm old
Sit back down
Sit back down
Sit back down
'CAUSE I SAID SO!

[Inger Lorre:]

"You're so stupid
I would have done anything for you
Honey, your reputation is shit in this town
You're so stupid
I would have done anything for you
Honey, your reputation is shit in this town"

Oh, why?
She's sassy
She's walking tall




###HOLE
###Teenage Whore

When I was a teenage whore
My mother asked me, she said, "Baby, what for?
I give you plenty, why do you want more?
Baby, why are you a teenage whore?"

I said, "I feel so alone and I, I wish I could die"
I've seen the things you put me through and I, I wish I could die

When I was a teenage whore
The rain came down like it never did before
I paid good money not to be ignored
Then why am I a teenage whore?

I've seen your repulsion and it looks real good on you
Denying what...what what you put me through

...of my house...get out of my house!
Get out of my house...get out of my house!

When I was a teenage whore
My mother asked me, she said, "Baby, what for?
I give you plenty, why do you want more?
Baby, why are you a teenage whore?"

I've seen your repulsion and it looks real good on you
I don't want to live what you had...you have put me through
I wanted that shirt and I, I wanted those pants
It's all the lying put me through and I
I never...whoa! 


###GLASVEGAS
###I Feel Wrong (Homosexuality, Pt. 1)

Confused desires since my teenage years
I'm the same homo my family fears
For my blue eyed boy there's a long distance longing
My behind closed doors fantasies going on
And I feel wrong

Forgive me father for I have sinned
I must confess it's brothers with my eyes that I undress
Once a day I think about killing myself
I can't carry on I must be strong even though it hurts as I sing this song
That I feel wrong
And I feel wrong

God it's only love, it's only love
God how long will this go on?
God for how long will I feel wrong?

And I feel wrong
And I feel wrong
I feel wrong
And I feel wrong 



###GLASVEGAS
###Stronger Than Dirt (Homosexuality, Pt. 2)

Tougher than tough
Toughest when we are together
Thoughts of me and you forever
The rest can go to hell
Yeah I'm lost, but so are you
Just like little lost lambs us two

They say we're sordid 'cause the way we walk and talk and flirt
They say we're dirty
I'm stronger than dirt

Absolutely novice
We're absolutely new to us
No less if we are not his 'n' hers
Our love is as valid as their love is
I'm going on... can we stay together?
Is it me and you forever?
Can the rest all go to hell?

They say we are sordid 'cause the way we walk and talk and flirt
They say we're dirty
I'm stronger than dirt
We're stronger than dirt

Love, stay with me
I'll keep you from harms way and hurt
Stay with me
Love, stay with me
I'll keep you from harms way and hurt
Stay with me

They say we are sordid 'cause the way we walk and talk and flirt
They say we're dirty
I'm stronger than dirt
(Stay with me)
I'm stronger than dirt
(Stay with me)
We're stronger than dirt
(Stay with me)
I'm stronger than dirt
Stronger than dirt
I'm stronger than dirt...



###GLASVEGAS
###Shine Like Stars

I see the black fade to grey
I feel forwards as the only way
Yesterday all my happiness seemed so far away
Now it looks as though it's here to stay..

Shine like stars
Shine like stars do

Cast a wish to the moon afar
Spare a thought for the ones who matter
If we could only mend the breaks
Open up our arms to fate, sweet fate.

Shine like stars
Shine like stars
Shine like stars do

I see the black fade to grey
I feel forwards as the only way
Hold on tightly and hope it all lasts
Celebrate the future
Forget the past.

Shine like stars
Shine like stars do
Shine like stars
Shine like stars do 



###GLASVEGAS
###Pain Pain, Never Again

Pain, pain, never again
A never having existed emotion called pain
A home where tranquility lives and prevails
The bluest of blue skies and the most angelic of all angels
Casablanca type ending all tales
Where over the cruel, the kind heart reigns
Like a backdrop fitting of a soulful Kurt Cobain
I'm overcoming the obstacles of the ubiquitous demon named 'shame'
Denise Denise, look at the swan that sails and sails and sails
A triumphant me and you again and again
The end credits naming us as the majestic escapists of cocaine
Pain, pain, never again. 



###GLASVEGAS
###A Snowflake Fell (And It Felt Like A Kiss)

The breeze from the graveyard keeps murmuring death
Too much time harbors thoughts in heads
Now I'm compelled to care
About a future that's going nowhere

As I stand here all alone in the cold wondering where I'm going today
Then a snowflake fell and it felt like a kiss
Now I'm okay

The ringing from the bells keeps screaming out love
As snow fell from heavens above
Directionless no more
Emptiness no more

Now I don't feel so all alone in the cold wondering where I'm going today
For a snowflake fell and it felt like a kiss
Now I'm okay






###GLASVEGAS
###Fuck You, It's Over

I gave you all the love,
A boy could ever need,
And in this world there's only one of me,

And all there is left,
Is the realisation,
That we we're never meant to be,

Fuck you,
Fuck you,
It's Over,

Fuck you,
Fuck you,
It's Over,

I've been lost since I woke up,
Broked since we broke up,
Vanished by your heart,

Remember it when,
You promised me how,
This time this christmas things would be different by now,

Fuck you,
Fuck you,
It's Over,

Fuck you,
Fuck you,
It's Over,

Middle Eight
All I wanted was to be,
Where your heart is,
But that's all changed now,
Now you're dead to me,

You're dead,
You're dead,
You're dead,
You're dead,

Fuck You,
Fuck You,
It's Over,

For You,
For You,
It's Over,

Fuck You,
For You,
It's Over,

For You,
For You,
It's Over,
Ahh 



###GLASVEGAS
###Ice Cream Van

There's a storm on the horizon
And for that I can't see the sun
For I'll keep a waiting on the pavement
For the ice-cream van to come

Its die hard hate to follow
And I'll not follow that
The marching people running round my head
Running round my head I don't know why

Why can't we see
Straight through the powers that be
Who keep us breaking each others hearts
And keeping us apart, keeping us apart

Destroying the ground where gruesome lays
Sectarianism and the hurtful racist ways
Bring back the glory days
Active citizenship
And pure community
Freedom of faith

There's a storm on the horizon...




###GLASVEGAS
###Daddy's Gone

How you are my hero
How you're never here though
Remember times when you put me on your shoulders
How I wish it was forever you would hold us
Right now I'm too young to know
How in the future it will affect me when you go
You could have had it all
You, me, and mum y`know
Anything was possible

I wont be the lonely one
Sitting on my own and sad
A fifty year old
Reminiscing what i had

I wont be the lonely one
Sitting on my own and sad

Forget your dad, he's gone
Forget your dad, he's gone

All I wanted was a kick-a-bout in the park
For you to race me home when it was nearly getting dark
How I could've been yours, and you'd be mine
It could've been me and you until the end of time
Do what you want, when you want
Be as fucking insincere as you can
What kind of way is that to treat your wife
To see your son on Saturdays
What way is that to live your life?

I wont be the lonely one
Sitting on my own and sad
A fifty year old
Reminiscing what I had

I wont be the lonely one
Sitting on my own and sad

Forget your dad, he's gone







###GLASVEGAS
###Lonesome Swan

Lonesome swan
Tell me what is wrong?
So you feel that we've all moved on
And you're feeling so alone?

Kids can be cruel
You know that's fair to say
But remember when the kids once said
You were queen of the waves upon the ocean bed

You were the dream boat pedalo
But now that's all in the past
But let me tell you that this loneliness will pass
And be a part of the past also

So for now dust down your weary sails
For tomorrow is a bright new day
With someone waiting in the wings
To pedal with you upon the ocean waves







###GLASVEGAS
###Flowers And Football Tops

Baby
Why you not home yet
Baby its getting late
I wish you would be home by now.
Door bell rings
Who could it be at this time
Police on my left and right
My son's not coming home tonight

Baby, they don't need to show
Its over, I know
Baby, they don't need to show
Flowers and football tops, I know
Baby why you?

No sweeping exits
No hollywood endings
Flowers and football tops
Don't mean a thing.

My baby is six feet under
Just another number
My daughter without her brother

Baby, they don't need to show
Its over, I know, I know
Baby, they don't need to show
Flowers and football tops, I know

My baby is gone...

You are my sunshine
My only sunshine
You make me happy
When skies are grey
I hope you noticed
How much I loved you
How could they take my sunshine away 



###CHRIS CORNELL
###Time"

We don't talk like we used to.
The perfect present is no longer the future.
And I can't find it, trust me I looked around.
Seems like all the sand is at the bottom now.

We gotta know, know when to fight, know when to hold, and when to let it go.
I hope we survive because it's passing by,
I won't be surprised if it all up and blows.

Time time time (If it all up and blows) time time time time (I wish we could rewind)
time time time (I wish we could rewind) time time time time (I wish we could rewind)

We are the shore, the wave is rising
We are the dust made out of diamonds
When metal rusts, we are all drowning
Island of man, we are surrounded

We gotta know, know when to fight, know when to hold, and when to let it go.
I hope we survive because it's passing by,
I won't be surprised if it all up and blows.

Time time time (If it all up and blows) time time time time (I wish we could rewind)
time (time, time, time, time, time) time time time time time time (I wish we could rewind)

Make a little love, make a little war, tell me how it feels dreaming without a future
have a little laugh, have a little cry, each moment gets us closer to saying goodbye
Make a little love, make a little war, tell me how it feels dreaming without a future
have a little laugh, have a little cry, each moment gets us closer to saying goodbye

Big hand keeps getting closer to the little hand all good things come to an end and turn around again
The big hand keeps getting closer to the little hand all good things come to an end

We gotta know, know when to fight, know when to hold, and when to let it go.
I hope we survive because it's passing by,
I won't be surprised if it all up and blows.

Time time time (If it all up and blows) time time time time (I wish we could rewind)
time time time (I wish we could rewind) time time time time (I wish we could rewind)

Time time time (If it all up and blows) time time time time (I wish we could rewind)
time (time, time, time, time, time) time time time time time time (I wish we could rewind)

I wish we could rewind



###CHRIS CORNELL
###You Know My Name

If you take a life, do you know what you'll give
Odds are, you won't like what it is
When the storm arrives, would you be seen with me
By the merciless eyes I've deceived

I've seen angels fall from blinding heights
But you yourself are nothing so divine
Just next in line

Arm yourself because no-one else here will save you
The odds will betray you
And I will replace you
You can't deny the prize; it may never fulfill you
It longs to kill you
Are you willing to die

The coldest blood runs through my veins
You know my name

If you come inside, things will not be the same
When you return to my night
If you think you've won
You never saw me change
The game that we have been playing

I've seen diamonds cut through harder men
Than you yourself
but if you must pretend
You may meet your end

Arm yourself because no-one else here will save you
The odds will betray you
And I will replace you
You can't deny the prize; it may never fulfill you
It longs to kill you
Are you willing to die

The coldest blood runs through my veins

Try to hide your hand
Forget how to feel
(Forget how to feel)
Life is gone with just a spin of the wheel
(A spin of the wheel)

Arm yourself because no-one else here will save you
The odds will betray you
And I will replace you
You can't deny the prize; it may never fulfill you
It longs to kill you
Are you willing to die

The coldest blood runs through my veins
You know my name
(You know my name)
You know my name
(You know my name)
you know my name!
You know my name!
You know my name!


###CHRIS CORNELL
###Finally Forever

On the silent night so out of place
I almost lost my nerve
When I saw you walk into my space
A woman like you I could not replace
And it took some patience to catch your eye
Patience to win your heart

Now it feels like I don't have to worry at all
It's finally forever

There's no hill I would not climb for you
No bridge I wouldn't cross
Not a moment passes in my life
That you're not on my mind
Together or apart
And it took some patience to catch your eye
Patience to win your heart

Now it feels like I don't have to worry at all
It's finally forever

Anytime you're lost
Anywhere you're found
Anytime you want
I will be around
Anywhere you seek
Anywhere you stand
Anytime you fall
Anywhere you limp
Even if you break
Anytime I can I will be there for you
I know that you'll understand
You'll understand

Now I never would have imagined this
So I thank my lucky stars
As I see you in your wedding dress
Never would have guessed you'd fill my open arms
And it took some patience to catch your eye
Patience to win your heart

Now it feels like I don't have to worry at all
Yeah it feels like I don't have to worry at all
Yeah it feels like I don't have to worry at all
It's finally forever
Finally forever


###CHRIS CORNELL
###Killing Birds

I learned long ago
'bout a better way of killing birds
And what it means when they die in my hands

Like a strangled heart
It never made much sense to me
Why I'd need to know the best way to do that

But you have to love the murderer I've become
As I'm standing here in front of you
Standing right in front of you
Standing here in front of you
Killing birds

I've spent my youth
Breaking down the walls my father built
Just like he did to his father before him

But then I had no home
So I tried to make a better one
It looked just like his, so I burned it down again

No there ain't a long parade of idiots
As I'm standing here in front of you
Standing right in front of you
Standing here in front of you
Killing birds

You don't have to love the murderer I've become

If I could spin a web
I would sit and wait for you
I wouldn't need a stone, I'd just poison you and tie you up

And you would be a bird
A beautiful cresent one
And your eyes would beg
But i'm just doing my job

Standing here in front of you
Standing right in front of you
Standing here in front of you
Standing right in front of you
Standing here in front of you
Standing right in front of you
Standing here in front of you
Killing birds


###CHRIS CORNELL
###Safe And Sound

Think of a time
When morning will come
And you will wake up without the feeling
That half the world has gone insane
You'll open your eyes
Reading your paper, a drink from your cup
No one was burning down time while you were sleeping

I've never seen but I believe
In a promised land

Why can't we pull this together?
One and all, now and forever
Why can't we pull this together?
We can say we finally found a world that's safe and sound

Think of a place that you could believe in whatever you want
Not keep it secret
Have to risk your life just to be yourself
A place where you'll walk safely no matter your color or age
More than the greed of you and me
Decides the fate of the day

I'd never seen but I believe
In a promised land

Why can't we pull this together?
One and all, now and forever
Why can't we pull this together?
We can say we finally found a world that's safe and sound

I'd rather see you setting free than watch the curtains coming down

Think of a life you won't take the breath from somebody else
One where you're seeking more than yourself

Why can't we pull this together?
One and all, now and forever
Why can't we pull this together?
We can say we finally found a world that's safe and sound

Why can't we pull this together?
Now and forever
Pull this together
We can say we finally found a world that's safe and sound

I'd rather see you setting free than watch the curtains coming down... 

###CHRIS CORNELL
###No Such Thing

I saw the world, it was beautiful
But the rain got in and ruined it all
Then I tried to be invisible
It was impossible
Even for me
I laughed at love
It was a big mistake
In the absence of
I filled it with hate

Cause there's no such thing as nothing
Yeah there's no such thing as nothing at all

I had the brains not to think at all
But the rain got in
And I thought too hard
On the world, and as usual
I slumped too far into the void
I tried to make everything meaningless
But the rain got in and made it a mess

Cause there's no such thing as nothing
Yeah there's no such thing as nothing at all
Yeah there's no such thing as nothing
But my finger's on the trigger
And I'll turn off the world

So what gives me the right
To think that I could throw away a life?
Even mine
And what makes you believe
That you could get away with getting old?
Overlapping me
Maybe to lose or to save your soul
Is a choice of how you fill the hole

And the rain got in

Cause there's no such thing as nothing
Yeah there's no such thing as nothing at all
There's no such thing as nothing
But my finger's on the trigger
And I'll turn off the world 

###CHRIS CORNELL
###Steel Rain"

And so we start another day together,
You and I and the million miles between.
I train my moods to bloom like flowers unfolding,
instead of fluttering around.
And slowly drowning in the...

Steel rain, it's taking over 
Steel rain, it's taking over 
Steel rain, it's taking over 
Steel rain, it's taking over 

The sky is open and the drones are pouring out.
The day inhales in a contagious yawn.
And there you smile as though the sun were bouncing in the...


Steel rain, it's taking over 
Steel rain, it's taking over 
Steel rain, it's taking over 
Steel rain, it's taking over 

Here in the little world, the tiny world spins for me,
All's well in the tilted world but there's something falling down,
in the...


###CHRIS CORNELL
###Sweet Euphoria

Sweet Euphoria,
mine is the heart you own.
You lost the grace of the hands that harmed you,
in the daze of a thousand yawns.
Lost my love,
as it is I'm truly gone.
In your morning I will sleep,
Fire on an open palm.
Death for Jesus and plastic armies,
Wouldn't bring me back again.
Sweet as ether eyes I'm blind to them.

Gone are you dandelions,
falling like mine -
Falling on land-mind, pillows.
Tired angels save my love for the lasting one.

Sweet Euphoria,
mine is heart you stole.
Touched and broken are the things you love,
using stars to light your candles.
Warms my face but I can't remember yours.
Gone are your dandelions, falling like mine,
falling like daydream mangos,
diving swallows.
Save my love,
save my love,
save my love,
for the lasting one.
Sweet Euphoria.



###CHRIS CORNELL
###Mission

Pulled through you and drowning in your swirl.
Circling, unfolding in your will.
I'm gonna glide on the winds of your breathing,
and alight on your gaurded heart,
I'm gonna tear all your temples down...

I'm on a mission now,
I'm on a mission now, 

Smoldering down inside your mood.
Slithering, and fanning in your eyes.
I'm gonna dive through your crying and sleep in your hair,
Rise from your ashes and kneel in your prayers,
tear all your temples down...

I'm on a mission now,
I'm on a mission now, 

I have nothing but then, the have is not as good as the want...
I'm gonna glide on the winds of your breathing.
Writhe in your calm and provide your release.
And reside in the heart of your strongest beliefs.
Tear all your temples down...

I'm on a mission now,
I'm on a mission now, 
I'm on a mission now,
I'm on a mission now, 
And I have nothing, but then the have is not as good as the want...


###CHRIS CORNELL
###Can't Change Me

She can do anything at all
Have anything she pleases
The power to change what she thinks is wrong
But what could she want with me? Yeah,
Wait, just, one minute here
I can see that she's trying to read me
Suddenly I know,

She's going to change the world
She's going to change the world
She's going to change the world
She's going to change the world
But she can't change me,
No, she can't change me

She has the daylight at her command
She gives the night it's dreams, yeah
She can uncover your darkest fear,
and make you forget you feel it.
But wait, just, one minute more,
I can see that she's trying to free me
Suddenly I know

She's going to change the world
She's going to change the world
She's going to change the world
She's going to change the world
But she can't change me,
No, she can't change me

Suddenly I can see everything that's wrong,
With me, yeah.
What can I do, I'm the only thing I really have, at all.

But wait, just, one minute here,
I can see that she's trying to need me
Suddenly I know

###CHRIS CORNELL
###Never Far Away

You are the road that I will travel
You are the words I write
You are the ocean I will swallow
You are the wind I ride

You are the cause to keep my head up high
I will survive
You gotta know I'll stay beside you
Right till the day I die

I don't want to change anymore
I've already paid
(Said, I've already paid)
I don't have to pray anymore
Because my soul has been saved

And now
Whenever I come, whenever I go
No, you're never far away, far away
Never far away

You're the blood that's in my veins
You're my second skin, skin
I'm a feather on the wind
You will bring me in

Every heart should have a beat
Every night a dream
Every king should have a queen
Every saint a sin

I don't want to change anymore
(I don't want to change)
I've already paid
(Said, I've already paid)
I don't have to pray anymore
Because my soul has been saved
(Been saved)

Whenever I come, whenever I go
No, you're never far away, far away
Never far away

When I go hot you make sure I don't break
Gimme life inside of heaven's gates, I know
(Heaven, heaven)
You taught me how to live like [unverified]
Gave me definition for the worst I know
That there ain't no space between you and me

Whenever I come, whenever I go
No you're never far away, far away
Never far away 

###SONIC YOUTH
###Death Valley '69"

Groooooahhh!

You're right

You're right

And now in the canyon
Out in the yonder
She started to holler

So I had to hit it

I got sand in my mouth
And you got sun in your eyes
Blind
And you wanted to get there
But I couldn't go faster

So I started to hit it
So I started to hit it
I started to hit it

Coming down
Sadie, I love it
Now now now
Death valley '69

You're right
You're right
You're right

I was on the wrong track
We're deep in the valley
How deep in the gulley

She started to holler
I didn't wanna
I didn't wanna
I didn't wanna
I didn't wanna
But she started to holler

Hit it
Hit it
Hit it
Deep in the valley
In the trunk of an old car
In the back of a chevvy

But you couldn't go faster

Hit it
Hit it
Hit it
Hit it
Hit it
Hit it
Hit it
Hit it

Coming down
Sadie, I love it
Now now now
Death valley '69
Death valley '69
Death valley '69
Death valley '69


You were right

And now in the canyon
Way out in the yonder

You got sand in your mouth
I got sun in your eyes
Blinded

I wanted to get there

You couldn't go faster

Hit it

Ieieieioooooaoaoaieeih! 

###SONIC YOUTH
###I Love Her All The Time

She comes into my mind
Twisting thru my nerves
I don't understand
A word she says
She's on my side
I love her all the time
I love her all the time
I love her all the time
I love her all the time

She comes into my mind
Twisting thru my nerves
I don't understand
A word she says
She's on my side
I love her all the time
I love her all the time
I love her all the time
I love her all the time 

###SONIC YOUTH
###Brave Men Run (In My Family)

Seven days and seven nights
I dreamt a sailor's dream at sea
Seven days and seven nights
I dreamt a sailor's dream of me
Seven days and siven nights
The world was made and lost again
Seven days and seven nights
Brave men run
In my family
Brave men run
Into the setting sun
Brave men run
Into captivity
Brave men run
In my family

Brave men run
Away from me 

###SONIC YOUTH
###Early American

Nothing but a savage blur
In your face, in your land
The weight of you is greater than
Forgot my pride
Forgot my side
Don't bother to leave
There's no room outside
Your sense of pride
Nothing here but a savage blur 

###SONIC YOUTH
###Kill Yr Idols

I don't know why
You wanna impress Christgau
Ah let that shit die
And find out the new goal

Kill yr idols
Sonic death
It's the end of the world
Your confusion is sex

Kill yr idols
Sonic death
It's the end of the world
Your confusion is sex

###SONIC YOUTH
###Protect Me You

Protect me from ravagement
I'm ten years old
I don't know what to do
Protect me myself
I'm fourteen
There's nothing to do
Protect me yourself
I'm sixteen
Protect me from starving
I'm eighteen
Protect me you
I don't know what to do
Protect me demons
That come at night
I don't know what they say
Their whispering
Sends the night air away
And makes me forget
I hope they come
Again and again

Here they come
Again and again
I hope they come again
Again
Again 

###SONIC YOUTH
###Making The Nature Scene

Going back to these origins
The city is a natural scape
Order in the details
Confusion uproar in the whole
In nature reality is selection
The tool of critical intervention
Fragmentation is the rule
Unity is not taught in school
You are an unnatural growth
On a funny sunny street
The city has forgotten you
It's symbols of the past
The meaning of its state
Its order of decay
Stand now in a column
And make the nature scene

Standing now in columns
Making the nature scene
Making the nature scene
Waiting to make their pay
There is no resistance to
The signs along the way
Standing all in columns
Waiting to make their pay
Making the nature scene
Waiting for the day
There is no resistance to
There is no resistance to
Salvation means to count on you
It just means to count on you
Make the nature scene

Making the nature scene
Making the nature scene
Making the nature scene

Going back to these origins
The city is a natural scape
Order in the details
Confusion uproar in the whole
In nature reality is selection
The tool of critical intervention
Fragmentation is the rule
Unity is not taught in school
You are an unnatural growth
On a funny sunny street
The city has forgotten you
It's symbols of the past
The meaning of its state
Its order of decay
Stand now in a column
And make the nature scene

Standing now in columns
Making the nature scene
Making the nature scene
Waiting to make their pay
There is no resistance to
The signs along the way
Standing all in columns
Waiting to make their pay
Making the nature scene
Waiting for the day
There is no resistance to
There is no resistance to
Salvation means to count on you
It just means to count on you
Make the nature scene

Making the nature scene
Making the nature scene
Making the nature scene 

###SONIC YOUTH
###The World Looks Red

Push it away
The world looks red
People with fish eyes
The ground sucks
Walk on my fingertips
Displacing the fog
The weight of my body
Is too mush to bear
The memory drained
The life from the dull
An ocean of insects
Worked like a sheet
The immovable fact
Buried my mind
In a horse-hair coat
In a pile
On the floor

Push it away
The world looks red
People with fish eyes
The ground sucks
Walk on my fingertips
Displacing the fog
The weight of my body
Is too much to bear
The memory drained
The life from the doll
The ocean of insects
Moved like a sheet
The immovable fact
Buried my mind
In a horsehair coat
In a pile
On the floor 

###SONIC YOUTH
###(She's In A) Bad Mood

She's in a bad mood
But I won't fall for it
I believe all her lies
But I can't fall for it

She's in a bad mood
But I won't fall for it
I believe all her lies
But I can't fall for it 

###SONIC YOUTH
###The Burning Spear

I'm not afraid to say I'm scared
In my bed I'm deep in prayer
I trust the speed I love the fear
The music comes
The burning spear 

###SONIC YOUTH
###Tom Violence

My violence is a dream
A 'real dream'
A skinny arm
A crush on living sin
My violence
Is a sleeping head
Nodding out to rising bliss
I left home for experience
Carved 'suk for honesty' on my chest
My violence is the number
Coming out of prayer
Find it in the father
Find it in a girl

There's a thing in my memory
Hoilding on for dear life
With a feeling of secrets
Beating up under my flesh
My tongue is tied
I'm sleeping nights awake
Tom violence is a dream
Coming out of a girl 

###SPIRITUALIZED 
###Broken Heart

Though I have a broken heart
I'm too busy to be heartbroken
There's a lot of things that need to be done
Lord I have a broken heart

Though I have a broken dream
I'm too busy to be dreaming of you
There's a lot of things that I gotta do
Lord I have a broken dream

And I'm wasted all the time
I've gotta drink you right off of my mind
I've been told that this will heal given time
Lord I have a broken heart

And I'm crying all the time
I have to keep it covered up with a smile
And I'll keep on moving on for a while
Lord I have a broken heart 

###SPIRITUALIZED 
###Stay With Me

Oh babe, I love it when you slide
Stay with me, slide all the time,
Don't Go
Love it when you smile
Stay with me, smile all the time
Don't Go
Love the it when you lie
Stay with me, hold me all of the time
Oh babe, I love it when you slide
Stay with me, slide all the time,
Don't Go
Love it when you smile
Stay with me, smile all the time
Don't Go
Love it when you lie
Stay with me, hold me all of the time
Oh babe, I love it when you slide
Stay with me, I love it when you're mine
Don't go
Love it when you smile
Stay with me, love it when you're mine
Don't go
I love you you're so fine


###SPIRITUALIZED 
###Ladies And Gentlemen We Are Floating In Space

Ladies and gentlemen we are floating in space

All I want in life's a little bit of love
To take the pain away
Getting strong today
A giant step each day
All I want in life's a little bit of love
To take the pain away
Getting strong today
A giant step each day
I've been told
Only fools rush in
Only fools rush in
But I don't believe
I don't believe
I could still fall in love with you

I will love you till I die
And I will love you all the time
So please put your sweet hand in mine
And float in space and drift in time
All the time until I die
We'll float in space, just you and I
And I will love you till I die
And I will love you all the time
So please put your sweet hand in mine
And float in space and drift in time
All the time until I die
We'll float in space, just you and I

Baby I love you today
I guess that's what you want
And I don't know where we are all going
Life don't get stranger than this
It is what it is
And I don't know where we are all going

I will love you till I die
And I will love you all the time
Everything happens today
And we're out here in space
And I don't know where we are all going
Baby I love you today
I guess that's what you want
And I don't know where we are all going 

###SPIRITUALIZED 
###Spread Your Wings

Oh babe
You know I'll take
Just a little bit more
Just a little bit more
And time
Time goes

Time goes slowly by
When I know that it can fly
C'mon spread your wings
Spread your wings

You can do anything, everything, anything


###SPIRITUALIZED 
###Let It Flow

Here it comes and then it goes
And that feeling takes me home
And I don't know where I'm goin'
Let it flow
All I wanted was a taste
Just enough to waste the day
Just enough to make me sick
Let it flow

And it takes up all my time
And it lays me back a while
Makes me feel like I'm a child

Let it flow
Let it flow

Here it comes an then it goes
And it hits me, takes me home
I don't know where I'm goin'
And I don't know where I've been
But I'd do it all again
All I wanted was a taste
Enough to waste a day
Just enough to make me sick
I can't get too much of it 

###SPIRITUALIZED 
###The Slide Song

Hey you know that I've been searching deep inside
And I'm not certain I will like the things I find
I don't know that you will understand but I have tried

I don't know just why I need to do the things I do
And I'd love to do these things without them hurting you
I don't know that you will understand but that's the truth

I'd give it up for you but let me finish what I got
I'd love to now but lord you know it sure does take a lot
I'll always love you honey but I can't be
What I'm not


###SPIRITUALIZED 
###200 Bars

I've been abused, and I've been used
I'm gonna lose my thoughts in 200 bars
You know I've tried, but I know I'm tired
I'm losing track of time 200 bars
I get confused, y'know I'm used to it
I'm gonna lose my thoughts in 200 bars
I've had my fix, too much of this
I'm losing all my thoughts in 200 bars
I'm losing track, out on my back
I'm gonna lose it all in 200 bars
Gonna get me blown, all on my own
I'm gonna lose my mind in 200 bars
I'm gonna lose my thoughts in 200 bars
I'm losing track of time in 200 bars
I've been abused, and I've been used
I'm gonna lose my thoughts in 200 bars
Y'know I tried, but now I'm tired
I'm losing track of time in 200 bars
'200'


###SPIRITUALIZED 
###Take Your Time

Take your time, and back up a little bit
C'mon now people, get yourselves out of it
No chains can hold me, no walls confine me
C'mon now people, c'mon and slide with me
Cos I'm blind, but not as blind as blind as you
I'm sick, there's not a thing I wanna do about it
I'm dumb, but now I wanna mouth off about it
I'm tired of it all, I guess that I am through with it all
Yeah I'm tired of it all, I guess that I am through with it all
Take good care of it babe
You know its goin slow but it's comin your way
You know we keep talking 'bout a revolution
But the air's so thin and you're still polluting it
You know we keep talkin but its so frustrating
Hell you know we keep talkin but theres no mistaking it
Take good care of it babe
Take good care of it babe


###SPIRITUALIZED 
###Run

They call me the breeze
I keep rollin' down the road
They call me the breeze
I keep rollin' then I'm gone

I ain't gotten me nobody
I ain't carryin me no load
You better run run run run run run run run now babe
You better run run run run run run run run now babe


###SPIRITUALIZED 
###You Know It's True

You know I've been here before
And I don't like it anymore
You know its true, but what could I do
You know I've felt this before
And I don't need it anymore
You know it's true, I love you
I love you, I love you




